Hot, hot Mike. Adam Curry Jhansi
devora December 17 2020 this is
your award winning chemo nation
media assassination Episode
13 104 This is no agenda
celebrating a th day and
broadcasting live from
opportunity's own 33 here in the
frontier of Austin, Texas
capital out the drone Star State
in the morning, everybody. I'm
Adam Curry from Northern Silicon
Valley where he had a gully
washer last night it's finally
raining no more fires. I'm Jesse
tomorrow.
Yeah, is it is it now also bad
weather there? Or is it just
just wet? I mean, is it like
horrible outside? Actually
today? Yeah, after they don't do
it. This is the series we've
seen this this weather in
California before where it rains
at night like crazy. And then
it's sunny and beautiful. Oh,
it's nice out it's cold. Cold
but it's pretty out and sunny.
Yes. Layers were layers when you
go out children wear layers in
San Francisco. Now it's crazy.
Got so you got fun. I got some
rain. crappy weather on the
west. The East Coast is Whoo.
This is a good one.
A lot of snow falling. Yeah,
sounds like it. Which is good.
Yeah, everyone has a real reason
to stay home.
Do we have a Zephyr yet? Do you
see anything come by? I'm
waiting cuz I'm stoked man. Did
you see Bitcoin?
This is crazy. Right now is
23,600 by now
get in while stocks last
everybody. Now I don't know yet.
GM shirt comes Oh, here we go.
3456 770 which is actually
eight. What do you mean actually
eight? Well, ever since they
went to the three a week instead
of every day. Yeah, they took
out the male luggage car. Ah,
okay Ladies and gentlemen, this
is your official Zephyr report
we have a stable economy things
are moving along just nicely
alert the guy to Squawk Box CNBC
let them know that we have a
seven cars that for usually
eight minus the mail car and
Bitcoin 23,650
Oh my god.
Meanwhile, the course sells me
there's absolutely zero
correlation between the Zephyr
and Bitcoin. Honestly, you say
that's what you say card number
goes up.
My God. I don't know. I don't
know. Meanwhile, we're all here
in a farmer controlled
biosecurity state and enjoying
it very much because we've got a
vaccine
but I don't know if if it's hard
to tell now with the mainstream
I mean obviously vaccine is
their is their number one story.
But this hack by cozy bear
this Russian hack that got into
email systems, I mean, that's
you think that will be a big
story.
Well, I think they tried to make
it a big story but but the media
in fact, I have a clip I thought
yeah, this one here. And I added
listen to this clip and because
it's the vaccine clip this by
vaccine side effects clip Mm
hmm. I hate to even tell you how
this is on this list is s Vax.
Yeah, I got it. I found it. The
S for side effects is over in
front of the vaccine. It's
jumping around the left when you
type. It's that devora keyboard
you got to get used to it. And
so this is the vaccine report
from NBC and it is very
interesting the way it's
structured. It happened in
Juneau, Alaska. 10 minutes after
receiving the Pfizer vaccine
yesterday, a health care worker
rushed to the ER with a severe
rash and shortness of breath,
her heart rate was elevated and
she had a red flushed rash over
her face and torso.
I was concerned about an
anaplastic reaction so gave her
the standard treatment of a dose
of intramuscular epinephrine.
And she responded immediately.
After a night in the ICU
receiving more medications.
She's stable now. Doctors say
she had no known previous
allergies, unlike two people in
the UK, who also developed
severe allergic reactions.
Tonight caution from Dr. Fauci.
If you have a history of a
severe allergic reaction, you
should either not take this
vaccine or if you do take it,
take it in the context of a
place where if you do develop an
allergic reaction, it could be
readily and effectively treated.
But 10s of 1000s of medical
workers have already been
vaccinated this week, most
reporting noses
effects like nursing director
Johnny Leonard at Methodist
Hospital in Houston, slept had a
great night last night woke up
this morning. She was going to
work, no symptoms at all.
Feeling very normal.
Through tomorrow 886 locations
will have received Pfizer doses.
vaccinations already starting in
nursing homes tomorrow and
outside FDA advisory panel will
decide whether to also authorize
Madonna's vaccine, if approved,
as expected, 6 million doses
could ship next week. Tom
Costello, NBC News, Washington.
Okay, what did you find
particularly odd about that?
Well, they started off with this
blast and you said they weren't
covering the Russian thing, or
that Russian Russians
various hack mysterious Oh, from
the, from the Snowden days that
you can make everything look
Russian according to the schemes
they have. So you can make
anything look a Russian attack
could be from anyone. And
I realized when I listen to this
thing a couple times, oh,
apparently these guys are on
Easy Street with this vaccine.
And they're not coughing up too
good for the advertising on NBC.
Ah,
there you go. That No, that
makes sense. It makes nothing
but sense they do this little
you know, we can you know, it's
Pfizer guy. You guys haven't
been you guys aren't up to your
normal pay out here for you
advertising What's going on? You
know, we can run a lot of these
that we can run nothing but
horror stories about the
vaccine. Yes. You know, in in
that context.
A lot of clips I got, which are
short ones. kind of explain the
context of these clips like this
one. Is there a difference
between modernas and the one out
from Pfizer, Dr. Ashish Shah of
Brown University tells ABC from
an efficacy safety point of view
there, they're nearly identical.
one's a little bit easier to
distribute doesn't have to be
kept frozen. That's the maternal
one. I doubt most people will
have a choice and it shouldn't
really matter. They're about the
same once it gets into your arm.
And Wednesday was the deadliest
day of the pandemic to date with
3656 American deaths according
to Johns Hopkins University.
So that's kind of like hey,
which one of you guys gonna
advertise Madonna Pfizer? I
don't know. I'd like to in the
arm though, that always makes me
feel good. Oh, the old stick
that in your arm at Bill Gates
though. This is this is the this
is the problem is the goalposts
are being moved. And we've seen
this happen throughout the past
10 months, where we start with
flatten the curve. Remember that
I even foolishly thought, oh,
April 7, we'll be done with
this. But now, since this is
apparently part of the big
reset, which in my mind can only
be now that we're shutting down
again, globally, can only be to
completely bankrupt the
economies. The economy is small
business, keep the big ones
open, especially the service
sector. Everybody invested
heavily to be able to weather
the dark winter and now Screw
you. We're just closing it down.
So that's done. That's that's
clearly what it's for. But now,
after being promised life, we'll
get back to normal after we get
the vaccine. Oh, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, that's not how
it's going to work. No, because
it was every single human being
on the planet is vaccinated.
You'll be wearing a mask Stan
home life lock downs and Bill
Gates went on CNN with Jake
Tapper to communicate to the
slaves to get my nation. When do
you think life will fully return
to what we thought of as normal?
Back in January, no masks, no
social distancing? No other
protective measures necessary.
Certainly by the summer will be
way closer to normal than we are
now. This laughs He does
irritates me a lot in this
particular clip. Why does he
have to laugh when he's giving
us really bad news. If we follow
it, life will get back to
normal.
No other protective measures.
This horrible, certainly by the
summer will be way closer to
normal than we are now. But even
through early 2022, unless we
help other countries get rid of
this disease and we get high
vaccination rates in our
country. The risk of
reintroduction will be there and
of course, the global economy
will be slowed down which hurts
America economically. In a
pretty dramatic way, too. We'll
have starting the summer about
nine months where a few things
like big public gatherings
will still be restricted. But
you know we can see now that
somewhere between 12 to 18
months and we have a change
Can we manage it? Well, to get
back to normal? And, oh, if we
manage it well, well, of course,
we'll, we'll mess it up Dr.
Bill, we know that.
But luckily, the vaccine is
here. So, stick with it, people,
it's still rolling out. More
than 30 million people in
California are right now under
brand new stay at home orders as
hospitals, their risk being
overwhelmed. There are a lot of
governors who oppose bringing
back these lockdown orders and
forcing businesses to close.
What do you think? Do you think
more states need to consider
taking that kind of drastic
action and the kind of drastic
action we saw when the pandemic
first began? Or can there be a
more nuanced approach? Well,
certainly mask wearing has
essentially no downside. They're
not expensive. bars and
restaurants in most of the
country will be closed as we go
into this way, then I think,
sadly, that's appropriate,
depending on how severe it is.
The decision about schools is
much more complicated because
there you know, the benefits are
pretty high. The amount of
transmission is not the same as
in restaurants and bars, so
it's all correct crap is
bullcrap. There's nothing going
on with restaurants and bars,
asking any restaurant or well,
bar, okay, Austin has some bar
issues, but restaurants, there's
no one that getting COVID in
restaurants, and Gavin nuisance
health official, what's the
guy's name?
golly, I guess he spelled it out
playing out. And oh, this is not
about not about people getting
infected at restaurants. Oh, no.
So the decision to include among
other sectors, outdoor dining,
and limiting that turning to
restaurants to deliver and
provide takeout options,
instead, really has to do with
the goal of trying to keep
people at home, not a comment on
the relative safety of outdoor
dining. And we have worked hard
with that industry to create
safer ways for outdoor dining to
happen to keeping tables farther
apart to ensuring masking
happens as much as possible to
create opportunities for air
circulation to continue. All of
those factors make sectors like
outdoor dining, lower risk. But
right now, with the levels of
transmission that we're seeing,
we advise against anything that
you can do in another way in a
lower risk way. that avoids you
either leaving your home or only
leaving your home in a way that
doesn't expose you and cause you
to mix with others. Right. So it
has nothing to do with
infectivity at restaurants. It's
just oh, you we don't want you
to have anything to do. So stay
home or go through the drive
thru. And with, as I suspected
with most of these public health
officials, they're just reading
the script. If you haven't seen
this, this is a hot my colleague
Mike hot Mike, from Ontario,
Canada's top health officials
just before they're about to do
one of their COVID updates and
briefings. I don't know why I
bring all these papers and never
look at
the numbers I do.
I just say whatever they write
down for me.
And we're sure that's true.
Yes, I just say whatever they
write down for me, oh, why? Why
would I do anything tough like
that. So the world is locking
down again. We have UK down
tight. And now we're talking
well into January. But the
people are getting somewhat
restless. And they're a little
tired of it. And this was a
great example, as the
Netherlands locked down on I
want to say Monday for five
weeks. I mean, tight, this is
locked down. You can't really
have you can go out you can go
to work if your work is allowed
to have you. But now basically
everyone's locked down. It's
done. So the Dutch Prime
Minister, he comes on live TV to
announce this and this comes
from the tower which we call the
door engine, which is in a way
equivalent to the Oval Office of
the Netherlands that he sit in
there. And the tower overlooks a
rather wide moat. It's a canal
but believe me it's meant to be
a moat. To keep the plebes away.
The plebs to the plebs are away
on the other side of this moat.
And they're so loud with their
booing and mainly whistling
which is always meant as an
insult in the Netherlands is you
know, if you ever watch a
football game soccer when they
whistle that's disapproval. They
could not drown out the sound of
people disapproving of what the
prime minister was saying. Have
a listen only to their cameras.
Nothing it's got to
pull it out
to Nick benna Nick Monica later
for Eastern tunafish to spark
hilltopper colonna optic Hilaire
Dotto for classified
as coronas you described
nostalgia oxetane don't buy
before covic maitake
down nylons from Peter Yoda from
the Edo Vivek in lockdown so
Netherlands is going into
lockdown for a period of five
weeks and then he says this may
launch heart opswat this is
interesting he says Natal on top
of slot the direct translation
would be the Netherlands is
being locked up, not locked
down, locked up close done big
padlock on the door and the
slaves are not having it.
Taken stuck for Allah blackish
lawgiver mentioned in Cooper
Sharma calm
he no shame on the family to not
have quit Spider Man subscribe.
I think he also lives in that
tower. I don't know if
it might be kind of annoying if
people are doing that all day
and all night.
But it's people are not really
happy with this. And in the UK,
they see ahead this
they've come up with something
new to justify this lockdown,
which a lot of people are saying
it's not based on science and I
tend to agree. Here's the health
secretary of the UK.
Matt Hancock, I'd like to update
the house on a new development
about the virus itself. Over the
last few days, thanks to our
world class genomic capability
in the UK, we have identified a
new variant of Coronavirus,
which may be associated with the
fastest spread in the southeast
of England.
initial analysis suggests that
this variant is growing faster
than the existing variants.
We've currently identified over
1000 cases with this variant
predominantly in the south of
England. Although cases have
been identified in nearly 60
different local authority areas,
and numbers are increasing
rapidly. Similar variants have
been identified in other
countries over the last few
months. We've notified the World
Health Organization about this
new variant and Public Health
England is working hard to
continue its expert analysis at
Porton down. Mr. Speaker, I must
stress this point that there is
currently nothing to suggest
that this variant is more likely
to cause serious disease. And
the latest clinical advice is
that it's highly unlikely that
this mutation would fail to
respond to a vaccine. But it
shows we've got to be vigilant,
follow the rules. And everyone
needs to take personal
responsibility not to spread
this virus. It is so bad in the
UK. And just everybody I know
who had a business is bankrupt.
Done.
Yes. It's not really funny. This
it's done that just completely
got there's nothing left. And
and this latest lockdown, which
I don't understand other than
you know, let's just scare
everybody and ruin everything.
It makes no sense. The numbers
aren't there. Although, you
know, now that the CDC has Ace
numbers are there Yes. But CDC
has combined the death numbers
with influenza and
pneumonia. So you have I think
it's p IC. Well, that's not
right. Well, that's how they
come up with a 3000 dead in one
day. Because people are dying
while they're dying of a lot of
things. It's just it's we
forgotten to question it. That's
That's how horrible this brain
programming has been this mind
control.
It's just crazy. Anyway, so
we've got the vaccine coming
out. And you know, the, the mind
control remains strong with
everybody on television. I love
this, this one America news guy
who was a total nerd. And when
he when he finally figures out
what he did here, he'll hate
himself for joining us now for
further analysis on this moment
is Adam glut. He's the president
of the media watchdog group
accuracy media. So, Adam, I want
to start with the Coronavirus,
actually because today we saw a
major development the
Coronavirus being shipped out to
frontline workers vulnerable
populations as well. It's really
a miraculous achievement within
itself. It's miraculous just
ship out the virus ship it out.
Did you even hear it? Yeah, you
know I can I can almost it's
almost unfathomable how often
this happens. Well, this is
truth wanting to come
documenting this for for a
month. Listen to this next one.
This is the first black nurse to
get the COVID vaccine.
Because there were a lot of
propaganda, a lot of promotion
of this on television as you
pointed out but
But we're not quite sure who's
going to spend the dollars. So
yeah, there was a lot of Oh, USA
Today had
a great article, or they say,
you know, there are some side
effects, you know, you might
blink with one eye slower than
you blink with the other eye,
you may lose control of some of
your facial muscle muscles,
which is temporary Bell's palsy.
But it's really not that bad. I
mean, that's in the USA Today
must have gotten in on some ad
by early. So now we're trying to
push it to the black and brown
communities and listen to what
this nurse says, and how and
when did you get selected to be
the very first in line? And why
was it important for you to do
so in public? So I volunteered
to take the vaccine, ever since
they were talks of a vaccine,
I've been telling my friends and
family, my colleagues that when
this does come to fruition that
I would be first in line, I
trust the science. And so it's
important for me to lead by
example, what I don't trust is
how I will be affected by COVID
backs COVID-19.
The whole point of the
interview, is to make black and
brown communities feel
comfortable about taking the
vaccine and then is how I will
be affected by COVID Max
COVID-19. Row. That's okay.
We'll have lots of black
celebrities coming to the
rescue. Dana bash knows all
about it.
What do you want to see from the
political figures in addition to
public health figures that
people are looking to for
answers and that people across
the country who might be
skeptical of the vaccine trust.
So I think there's an awful lot
of misinformation out there
about this vaccine, we're
hearing a lot of anti Vax
propaganda being turned into
talking points by people on both
sides of the political spectrum.
I would love to see politicians
from both sides, showing up
getting vaccinated, doing the
vaccine on TV on whatever
network is the most, of course,
I'd love to see them on CNN
getting vaccinated, but that
will help prove to the American
public that this is a
trustworthy vaccine, that if
they themselves see it as safe
and are willing to inject it in
their bodies, so should be
American on the street. I think
it's important also for
celebrities to do it. Yes,
particularly.
Celebrities, many, many
celebrities in their community
hero, we know that there's more
mistrust of the vaccine from
minority groups appropriately.
So it's important for us to
shift that I'd love to see Trump
and Pence get vaccinated just as
I'd love to see them wear masks.
Yeah, we want to see lots of
celebrities vaccinated with the
real vaccine. Not the phony
baloney stuff Barack Obama is
going to get and Mike Pence is
going to get and this brings me
to Tom Cruise.
Talking of the of the media
industry in Hollywood, which as
you know is completely owned by
China, the Chinese Communist
Party. I'll do the report and at
first I read this the wrong way
actually and the keeper she sent
me straight and I think to turn
out to be spot on with her
analysis. Listen to the report
from ABC.
This good this is Good Morning
America. Thanks so
listen to the Tom Cruise report.
Tom Cruise reportedly let his
COVID concerns be heard loud and
clear while filming the new
mission impossible movie in
England in an audio obtained
from the sun tabloid, which has
not been authenticated by abc
news crews was reportedly
furious with staffers for
ignoring safety protocols.
Work on the film had to be shut
down in October when 12 staffers
tested positive. I don't know
much of let's put this I have
not met Tom Cruise. But I do
know his former handlers if you
recall, we had the
Scientologists PR team living in
Austin.
And for this audio to get out.
Ah, that is not how Tom Cruise
or the Church of Scientology
works. They would be they are
extremely litigious. They would
be blocking this they would be
hammering this they would be
threatening any new station that
was putting this on the air,
maybe even calling it hack
materials but this was intended
to come out and if you listen to
that, I think the whole thing is
four or five minutes. My boy is
acting that is Tom Cruise acting
mad in every single movie you've
seen him act Madden as it first
He acts mad at first I thought,
Oh, he's not acting when he's
mad is just how he is. And then
Tina said, No, no, no, he's
going to get praised for this.
And yes, if you look at the the
Hollywood celebrities, they're
all like, Oh, yes. So right on.
Good job, Tom. You tell them
it's important because you are
you're you're keeping families
fed and you're keeping 1000s of
people at work. You're saving
the industry, which is China's
industry because they need
product. That's why not because
Tom Cruise gives a crap about
anybody in America. Disgusting
PR pro Hollywood, which is good.
Yeah, I never I just kind of
glossed that whole thing over I
never but now as you mentioned
it Yeah. Is it any is a good
actor Sure. He doesn't This is
his show his chops that much. So
he's acting You're right. Yeah,
he's so he's acting and this was
all about somebody not wearing a
mask or some stupid thing.
whatever it was. Yeah, yeah.
Someone broke the COVID rules.
Now did give us a number of good
ISOs to choose from possibly for
the end of show. So here's one
that's not good. How about this
one?
We have this one. bucket hold on
hold on. Oh, maybe this one.
I like producers.
And the final one I have no How
about this one? How about this
one?
Yeah, Sue Bumi. You're right. We
are the gold standard which
would have been good. It's just
too booming but you want to hear
a couple of mine while you were
first is an aside Yeah, sure.
Okay, this is a head so small.
So small. Why is this so small?
zatz pretty good. I liked that.
Wait a minute. We're doing an IC
o off How about this one?
buck, buck. I can't help it.
It's all buckety this what you
get from the news? This is very
good. I like the head so small.
Do you have any others? The only
other one is I have is a screech
that I picked off him off some
something I was clipping
now I think
it was it again. head so small.
Yeah, I think that's the one we
put in the spot. Why is this? so
small? Yeah. No, I think I think
you nailed it with that one.
That's a really good one. Well,
there's also one last one. Oh,
I just noticed that this this is
Kaylee. I have a Kaylee special
today. Oh, nice. After a break
would do it. A lot of clips.
Yeah, a fact fact check cailli
fact check. Back check false.
I think head so small is better.
Yeah, I think it is too. I liked
it. I liked the fact check
false, but not for this. Just in
time for the vaccine. The World
Health Organization has released
an important directive regarding
this is for IBD users. This
would be the tech technicians
who performed the PCR quote
test. And they are now saying
that
the purpose of this notice to
ensure users of certain nucleic
acid testing technologies are
aware of certain aspects of the
instructions for use the ifu for
all products description of
problem. World Health
Organization has received user
feedback on an elevated risk for
false SARS cov. Two results when
testing specimens using RT PCR
reagents on open systems. Oh
wow. And now so what they say in
this is you really need to make
sure you follow the directions
carefully because you know you
could be doing it wrong.
And they literally say here.
The design principle of PCR
means for patients with high
levels of circulating virus
relatively few cycles will be
needed to detect virus and so
the count value will be low.
Conversely, when specimens
return a high count value means
that many cycles were required
to detect the virus in some
circumstances, the distinction
between background noise and
actual presence of the target
virus is difficult to ascertain.
So they say please check your
cycles which in my mind means
lower the site calls we got the
vaccine
but not too much, jack. That's
exactly what it means. Yeah.
My comb was tested positive
according to one of these PCR
things so he's social
distancing, or whatever. Okay,
quarantine him.
Lock him up New York Times
pushing the freedom pass app.
Which now the ethics of that are
being discussed and it seems to
be totally ethical. So that's
good. That's good. Good on San
Diego, everybody. This is great.
I think we should try this in
Austin. I think this is a legal
loophole that can be used the
county releasing that late in
response to this judge's ruling.
And today in court, the lawyers
representing these two strip
clubs, they argued that if
people were allowed to shop and
things like shopping malls and
grocery stores, then live adult
entertainment should also be
allowed to continue indoors. But
what many did not know is that
ruling will also begin to
encompass all of San Diego
County's restaurants. We got the
yellow rose here in Austin.
It can be Wait a minute, you
tell Oh, that's right. This is
where all the the right wingers
like the pitcher button, I think
is a legitimate complaint, which
is that they leave the strip
clubs out, but you can't go to a
restaurant. Hmm. So now in San
Diego, that's sticking in San
Diego restaurant. stripper and I
yeah, now you're talking Yes,
Ripper in every restaurant.
That's the ticket, baby. That's
the way to go. Yeah, just put a
pole up.
Just like to go go days when
they just have a girl in a cage.
Or you can even get one of those
trans people who read library
books to children.
Bring them in? Yeah, well, that
would probably make people lose
their appetite. So that's
different. I don't know. I mean,
it doesn't matter as long as we
get around it. Well do whatever
works. By the way. You said Get
your poll up, which was pretty
good.
Yeah, get your poll up people.
Now there is some other breaking
news, which was broken by
Politico. And, you know, now
there's documents which have
been declassified or leaked, I'm
not quite sure how they got
ahold of them didn't read the
whole story, because I caught
chris hayes talking about this.
And that there was discussion
early on. Amidst the team. It's
not clear who said what exactly
but doesn't matter. It's people
familiar with the thinking and
the matter. And they have some
documents, that the whole plan
was to get everybody infected,
just let them go and get
infected. For that stupid
debunked herd immunity theory,
which, by the way, I think is
the whole theory of vaccine
vaccination strategy. But okay.
And Chris Hayes gunked. Up,
Chris Hayes took it to another
level. Good evening from New
York. I'm Chris Hayes. We want
them infected. Those are the
words of a top Trump appointee,
directing the federal government
to pursue an intentional
strategy from the top down to
get as many Americans as sick as
possible in an attempt at so
called herd immunity. It's a
strategy we have seen unfold
before our eyes. We've talked
about it here on the show. It's
been apparent to all of us
reporting on this and watching.
But we now have the smoking gun
evidence, emails obtained by
Politico, in which the very
people at the center of this say
what exactly they were doing,
that they wanted people to get
the virus. And this is the
result.
The National Cathedral in
Washington DC last night, it's
Bell totaling 300 times, one
ring of the bell for every 1000
Americans as we pass the 300,000
death toll. According to the
COVID for tracking project, we
lost another 3400 Americans that
have died since roughly when
those bells rang just last
night. And that is a new Daily
Record. We never seen it before.
No country has 3400 Americans
lost to the virus in just the
last 24 hours.
And it did not have to be this
bad. Okay. Yeah, there you go.
Didn't have to be I love the
death toll clock. That's great.
Do they know they won the
election? It doesn't have this
this idea of just, well, me this
battle is mismanaged. blabbity
blabbity blah, is they can they
get let that go? No, they can't,
because we have too much noise
out there. We have to
continuously bash this
administration. Because, you
know, they're still trying to
stay in, by the way. Well, you
don't hear a lot of I think
that's really the most
remarkable from the mainstream
these days. You don't hear a lot
of Well, we're gonna have to get
the military to kick him out.
Why is that? all he's doing is
saying I want I'm not leaving,
but I don't hear that anymore. I
don't hate I don't hear the Oh,
yo we have to have to go
With the with the military, to
smoke them out, shoot them out
whatever they were talking. I
don't think that I think maybe
it was getting offensive or
please. They know. They know
that the military is not their
side is what I'd say. Now let's
let's look at a little bit of
what the military was never on
their side when they first came
to the thing was just a meme.
They like to propagate, they get
the dummies to vote for Biden.
So they're not worried about it
now, or they never were? I guess
not huh?
Well, good, good.
Let's take it from the top only
a few things on what's happening
with the with the executive
order enacting of that or not.
So we'll run through it. And I
don't do you have anything on
this?
Any clips or anything? COVID?
No, no, I'm done with COVID we
got nothing left. You got she
got some from COVID I don't
think get anything from COVID.
I'm looking at a vitamin d3
study that might be worthwhile.
Well, that's kind of
interesting. This is a part of a
series of these things are all
scattered around YouTube by
various experts. And you know,
the profit with the d3 thing is
that people don't get any
numbers.
So the dual take a you know, 500
unit, d3 and think that's gonna
do something. And so this was an
interesting one. This guy talks
about d3. And it's, it's very
effective and keeping you from
getting COVID apparently. And I
said, apparently, that's one
Hold on. I also, you know,
Christina had a little COVID
scare, as she and two friends of
hers were feeling really weak
that migraines like okay, well,
you either have some flu bug or
you got the Rona. So they got
tested, which was dramatic
seeing as you you can't go
anywhere, you can't travel on
the
public transit transit to get to
a test with all these rules.
And, you know, so I, I was kinda
like, oh, man, I hope that
doesn't, nothing gets worse. So
I'm contacting Agent Orange,
and, you know, a couple of guys,
and hey, you know, if I need any
help on there, and they got back
to me military now is
recommending, even if you if you
have the symptoms, even if
you're right in the middle of it
doesn't matter. 12,000 micro use
of d3 a day?
Well, I've been looking at all
these things, and that's within
the range of some of their
theories than the average one
that I've heard them recommend.
is eight a day. 8000 terms of
Yeah, a day every day. But
that's, you know, again, we
don't give this advice out. But
we can play clips. Yes. We love
playing clips. Now. Just d3 is
not a vitamin, correct? It turns
out that when you really analyze
is it's kind of a hormone. Yeah,
that's what I heard too, that
it's Yes. It's really it's for
mamak Yes, it is not, not
really. But it's very different
from D two, for example. Yeah.
And you know, you how you make a
hormone. Oh, yeah. I've made
many more Mayer. You don't?
Yeah. Oh, okay.
Yeah.
You are the worst divorce wreck.
Okay, let's replay recent
vitamin d3 study. The most
recent study that's come out
though, was India titled short
term high dose vitamin D
supplementation for COVID-19
disease, a randomized placebo
controlled trial. This is also
known as the shade study. And
here, they looked at 40 COVID-19
positive patients and here they
gave 60,000 units daily for
seven days. And they gave 24
patients placebo. So the total
here was 16. Got the
intervention. 24 controls got
the placebo. And in terms of
their outcomes, they were
looking at how many of them were
SARS COVID to negative by day
21. And whether any biomarker
reductions and so the results
were that 62.5% versus 20.8%.
Were SARS COVID to negative by
day 21. In the intervention
group and those that got vitamin
D. Yeah.
Yeah, yay for vitamin D, d3, d3,
d3, d3. Yeah. Yay. Yay for that.
Well, you know, I've been using
that as a method ever since you
told me about it years and years
and years ago on the show, and
it's always done well by me.
Yeah, I've been using it for
over 10 years now and I have not
had a cold. And I only had a I
had a close call with the 2017
deaths. flu. Yes, which I did
pick up in London. I took the
d3. But I took I also jumped on
the
Tamiflu, and I ended it with a
minor case of the flu. Yeah. And
except for that I have had not
had a cold flu anything. A
decade. Nice to note that the
American Medical system
Association has reversed their
position on hydroxychloroquine.
Now that Trumps out, yeah, they
rescinded their request, the
doctors stop prescribing it. So
that's all good now and I even
read, there was a study about
some, I think they actually use
bleach as the term but
disinfectant being injected and
working. There's all these
different things that you know,
we're just reason to laugh at
the president. That's crazy.
That's crazy. Well, what else do
you expect? Okay, so let me give
you an overview of what I'm
tracking with Trump's last
stand. Clearly, I also have some
thoughts on what to fail with.
Yeah, what the fail I'm sorry,
how, how this whole thing fell
apart. But so I don't know if
it's falling apart. But I'll
tell you what I was seeing and
I.
Well, the legal thing is
totally, but I don't even know
if that was the plan here.
Here's your here's where we're
at. And this is a combination of
me analyzing what I love for
this all to happen. Yeah, you
bet. I wouldn't. I think you
would, too. But is it going to
happen? I'm very strong 1000s of
sealed indictments feeling at
this moment.
But
we're in this interesting
position, where people aren't
even talking about Trump winning
or losing anymore. And I'm
talking about alternative media,
podcasts, blogs, YouTubers, but
also Newsmax Bannon, one
American news, America's voice.
I've been watching it all for
you. So I'm deeply embedded in
this. And the basic thinking is
it's not about it's not about
Trump, it's about having fair
elections. If we don't figure
out what happened with this one
will net we've lost the
Republic, we can never have a
fair election again. If we don't
understand we don't get to the
bottom of everything that
happened. And alongside of that
comes the no I'm not on 4chan
troll room. I don't do that
comes with something you keep
hearing. Well, the military and
the president both swore an oath
to uphold and defend the
Constitution. So now it's come
down to the bottom bottom bottom
line, if it's about the
Constitution, and the way would
work is we have sufficient
evidence to show that China
meddled in this election, that
China compromised people who
were involved in the election
process, that that triggers the
2018 Executive Order, which then
allows the president to conduct
military tribunals and throw
people in jail and arrest them
and get to the bottom of this
and
change the outcome of
the 2020 election by having
senators contest multiple states
and the votes and, and have all
of this evidence to show for it.
So it's part media strategy.
It's actually a lot of media
strategy, blanketing alternative
media with as much as possible.
I mean, like crazy. Okay, I clip
this for you. Because this is
just too good. I have heard a
version of this story of this
little clip from this is from
monkey works who's a kind of a
prepper YouTuber, but has a lot
of tracking military stuff. I
have heard a version of this
story multiple times my
stepdaughter who works at a
functional medicine practice,
had people calling her and
saying well my appointment is in
five days but will you
appointments still go on when
they shut down the internet and
electricity? I mean, this is how
far this has gone. I have gotten
some intel from someone that I
definitely trust okay. A former
high speed guy, Navy high speed
guy if that says anything and he
talking with his buddies at our
current active in
you know operations. They said
Be ready to go into a lockdown
they're expecting about 10 days
and I'm just kind of giving you
that they said it could be a
week to two weeks we're just
kind of go with 10 days
because it seems like a good
even keel number okay. But they
said you guys need to just prep
make sure you got hat you know
you have supplies available, get
plenty food and water and just
be expecting it that that this
is
going to be a military operation
and it's going to be on a global
scale. So just take that with a
pinch of salt. That's Yes. Oh,
Going out there. But I've heard
this story from so many
different sources continuously.
Now back to reality. On January
6, something actually can be
done. That will be the final, I
think, piece that'll happen in
the government. And then I'll
get back to where we are at this
moment. So this is joy read with
Maxine Waters, you serve with mo
Brooks, you serve with some of
these Republican members of the
House, what do you make of the
idea that they're still not
done, that they're now planning
on holding what would basically
be a show vote and force a show
vote in the United States Senate
on January 6, it's shocking, it
is absolutely shocking, that
they would continue in their
efforts to do what I consider
the highest form of voter
suppression. We've never seen
anything like this. The
President of the United States
has gone to 446 courts that have
turned him down, that have said
you have no evidence. And so he
went to the Supreme Court, where
he has three members said he's
happy to get on the Supreme
Court, they turned you down.
They didn't even let him file.
They didn't let Texas attorney
general who is the head of this
amicus brief that he had, did
not let them file in the Supreme
Court. And they're still moving
forward with trying to somehow
invalidate the votes of millions
of people in four states. It is
just unbelievable that they
would continue this. Either.
They are so I'm so intimidated.
So bullied by the President of
the United States. They can't
stand up for democracy and the
constitution that is
hard to understand.
So again, the thinking is, Oh,
no, no, we're all going to get a
big civics lesson we're going to
understand and learn about how
the constitution really works.
The another great part of this
is the resignation of Bill Barr,
which is a resignation was he
kicked out, we don't know. More
interesting is his replacement
acting Attorney General.
The acting Attorney General is
from the 82nd airborne and was
alongside Mike Flynn in the same
unit. And he's all about toe
coercion. And we have to listen,
this is actually from earlier I
think this is from August of
this year. And finally to share
a little bit of advice we can
borrow from our historical
predecessors. To begin, I think
it helps to clarify a few
definitions to describe what we
mean by malign foreign
influence, as opposed to what we
might consider just legitimate
diplomacy, or candid expressions
of legitimate national interests
that all nations share with one
another in appropriate ways. One
definition, that's easiest to
remember, is what we refer to as
the three C's framework,
coercive, covert, or corrupt
activities by foreign
governments to influence us
policies, US political
sentiment, US public discourse,
or to interfere in our political
processes themselves. Under the
three C's framework, we
recognize that foreign
governments often have
preferences about us policies,
or even the outcomes of our
elections. Sometimes those
preferences are expressed
openly. Our government sometimes
has open preferences about other
countries to when the
preferences are open and
attributable. No one is
deceived, or misled. But what
we're concerned about is when
foreign preferences manifest
themselves through malign
foreign influence activities
that are again, coercive,
covert, or corrupt, whether
their aim is specifically to
influence our elections, or to
influence policymaking and
public discourse more broadly.
So everything is set up for the
big report, the big report that
is required, as per the exact
2018 Executive Order, where we
will find out exactly what went
on with this election. And if
there was one of those three C's
that took place, or all three of
them, then we can the president,
apparently, and I said it has
very strong powers, to do all
kinds of stuff, and we were
getting ready for it. We had the
Director of National
Intelligence talking to CBS to
the Pixie girls setting this up,
we were getting ready, he wrote
a piece for the Wall Street
Journal and you say China is
targeting members of Congress,
with six times the frequency of
Russia and 12 times the
frequency of Iran, what is
behind Beijing's aggressive
approach, so they want laws and
policies out of the United
States that are favorable to
China. And what they're really
trying to do is through
blackmail, through bribery
through overt and covert
influence, trying to make sure
that only laws that are
favorable to China are passed.
Have you been to Capitol Hill
and have you brief to spread
information to lawmakers, I was
so troubled by what I saw from
the public
as the Director of National
Intelligence, but I went and
briefed both the House and
Senate Intelligence Committees
on this information, which they
found surprising and troubling.
But that's part of alerting
members of Congress to the
threats that they're facing, and
that the American people are
facing in this broad campaign
that China has to replace the
United States as the world's
superpower. When did you read
those two intelligence
committees earlier this summer?
So we're all ready for it? We're
set because we're finally going
to be told that this is all
about China. And then all my we
have a huge security breach
breaching the Treasury
Department breaching parts of
the Pentagon, its solar winds,
they're everywhere. The Russians
are coming. We're following
breaking developments from the
White House. The National
Security Council confirms to NBC
News that they are investigating
a hack affecting the Treasury
Department and the unit of the
Commerce Department. And
tonight, we've learned Russia is
behind it. For more I want to
bring in NBC national security
correspondent Ken Delaney. And
can we have any idea what kind
of information was accessed? We
do not at least yet other than
the fact that a source familiar
with the matter told me the
right now there are no
indications that classified
networks have been breached. But
that same source, who confirmed
the Washington Post reporting
that the US government believes
that this was the work of the
Russian version of the CIA, the
SVR, that same source said that
it's believed that this is a
wider campaign, there may be
more government agencies
affected and a number of private
sector agencies. Last week, we
reported that the Russians had
hacked a major cybersecurity
firm called fireeye. And the way
they are reported to have
attacked Treasury and commerce
is through a network management
software that gives them
administrative access. So it's a
really devious method, and it
has given them access to, you
know, sort of unknown levels of
US government information. The
US government was so concerned
about it. Reuters reported that
there was a National Security
Council meeting about it on
Saturday, Alicia,
I don't know about you, but I
don't think this was China or
Russia. I think this was purely
the CIA.
And I base that on speaking to
multiple dudes named Ben, who
analyzed all of this and and
they said, first of all, if it
was Russia, we would know it.
The Russians are in and out, and
they don't leave any tracks. And
although
of course, according to the
reports, solar wind, this
monitoring system was used in 29
of 30 counties that had Dominion
voting machines.
No, I haven't heard anyone find
any vulnerable penetration or
because of these
vulnerabilities, even though
they all had to take down you
know, shut down the systems and
patch the software. This to me
sounds like CIA trying to
trying to get the Russia story
out there anything anything but
China? I mean, I don't know from
the Snowden era that the CIA has
tools to make everything look
like it was the Russians. Yes.
And the firewall is a good ploy.
Make the Russians blame the
Russians and the Russians have
nothing to do they must be very,
I don't know if you're laughing
up their sleeve in Russia what
they're thinking but they must
be annoyed by this at some
point. Especially cozy bear have
it there p owed. Well, man, we
don't leave tracks. What are you
talking about? But what is this
done? This has delayed the
report in we've received an
official notification from the
Office of the Director of
National Intelligence. This
afternoon, the DNI was notified
by career intelligence officials
that the intelligence community
will not meet the December 18
deadline, as set by the
executive order back to Pixie
girl What did Ratcliffe say
about election fraud and
interference? Well, DNI
Radcliffe leads the 17
intelligence agencies and he has
access to the most highly
classified information that is
held by the US government. And
he told CBS News that there was
foreign election interference by
China, or Iran and Russia in
November of this year. And he is
anticipating a public report on
those findings in January
in January.
This ain't gonna make it folks.
And now I'm thinking that
there's somehow there. There's
something going on when you say,
the intelligence agencies Well,
they seem to be pretty much all
anti Trump. So I don't know
exactly what we're waiting from
from them. Or maybe they they
did this hack to somehow now
they have to gather the evidence
to show that it was Russia. I
don't know but it seems like
this report is not going to make
it that's a very in my mind a
very bad sign. I could be
completely wrong. No.
Here is not going to make it
because they don't have a
report. They're cobbling
something together as
A quick aside spaceforce now,
PR executive or only hope has
has become an intelligence
agency, there was an executive
board or announcement about it.
spaceforce is now the space
force intelligence agency. And
they'll be working on nuclear
space propulsion so we can get
to Mars. I love these guys. So
the final rundown here, for
this is the only person I find
credible at all when it comes to
the evidence, but man, there is
so much they would there's clip
after clip of the Dominion CEO
saying that no, no, no, none of
this was connected to the
internet. And well, I don't
think you could stick in a USB
stick. I don't know. But I mean,
feigning honesty and probably
lying. But here is Sidney Powell
with one minute of her her
evidence that she feels is
enough to trigger the 2018
Executive Order. I don't know
exactly what she means by that.
I think the report triggers it.
But here we go. So they had
these warehouses of counterfeit
ballots in different parts of
the country, apparently, and
then shipped them in the area
light as needed to backfill in
the states where President
Trump's voters poured out in
such great number, that they
broke the algorithm they had pre
programmed in the computers for
dominion, to create the fraud.
That's why they had to stop
counting in five states. And
that's why it's absolutely
absurd to say that there wasn't
voter fraud here. We have
counterfeit ballots, we have
dead people voting. And by the
1000s, if not hundreds of 1000s
there were something someone
called Phantom voters, there
were just more manner and means
of fraud than any law abiding
American citizen could possibly
imagine. It's stunning. It's
absolutely stunning. And they
were so in our face with it. And
then to deny it is purely
Machiavellian.
And ironically, in 2007,
then vice president elect or to
be hopeful, Joe Biden was
worried about the voting
machines to keep it from us
being able to be in a position
where you can manipulate the
machines manipulate directors,
the one way to do that is I
think we should pass a federal
law, mandating that the same
machines with paper trails be
mandatory for every federal
election. In a nutshell, I think
we should be mandated, mandating
that we have a paper ballot with
a standardized machine
standardized requirement.
So I don't know about everything
else. But I completely believe
after having looked at all the,
quote, unquote, forensics, and
there's a huge report that came
out from the thing, it's the
Michigan machines, those
machines are definitely rig
rigged, and that that has to
stop no matter what. I think
everyone kind of agrees on that.
Well, here's what I've got.
This election was last in May of
2019.
When when
Trump put together his that
executive order in November
16 2018, he put together an
operation, which is now has a $3
billion budget, and they have a
big website, and it's kind of
kind of interested in is called
the cyber security and
infrastructure security agency.
And this was set up specifically
to prevent the any fraudulent
activity in the upcoming
election. And it was moving
along just fine. And it was
being run by this guy chris
chris, who is fired immediately
after the election because he
says they couldn't find anything
wrong with the election and he's
the one that headed up headed up
the let me put up this. Clearly
it's Sisa on the line for you.
They want you to shut down. They
want you to shut down your solar
winds, please.
While you're doing that, I will
play a creepy robo call. Here we
go. Creepy robo call of the day.
It's just a test call. Time to
stay home. Stay safe and stay
home.
Wow. Anyway, I got a couple of
new robots recently. Anyway, so
he set up this agency this began
he set up this agency and you
can go see it. It's a SCI fi.gov
It's a massive website and now
they even they're even producing
graphic novels have a link to
the graphic novel for
downloading the next newsletter.
I've seen that.
So, so this guy Krabs was
running the thing and everything
was going along swimmingly. But
what he
happened was. And if you look
into the background, this
agency, there was a student
government report that
discovered this, I'm going to
read it. In October of 2020
review for the Institute for
world politics, a student
journal active measures, stated
that C is a and by the way, this
is one of my pet peeves about
all these agencies, apparently
lacks an enforcement division,
which did have the federal
protection services, which
resorted until 2010, under the
US Immigration and Customs
Enforcement was actually working
for these guys. It was moved in
May 2019. From the CIA, NSA to
the DHS management directory
Directorate. So it was their
enforcement capabilities, which
means you can't find crimes if
you don't have inspectors and
and
virtual cops out there people
doing investigations if there's
no investigators, right? You're
not gonna find anything. And
they took the investigation of
capabilities away from this
agency to $3 billion agency in
May of 2019. And that's when the
election was lost. Well, how did
this happen? Well, if you look
into it, hmm. This is after
after Christian Nielsen quit.
Right. In April of 2019. They
moved in this in some guy who
last it was there for six months
only came and left on his own.
Nobody pushed him out. He came
in and in April and in May
implemented this removal of the
enforcement capability. Who is
this guy? Kevin McLean, and and
who is Kevin McLean. He was a
he's that old hack from Border
Patrol, but he was, let me just
read this from this from the
Wikipedia. President Trump
nominated McLean and McLennan
McLennan to assume the position
of Commissioner in a permanent
capacity.
McKenna's previous nomination
was supported by officials from
both the George Bush and Barack
Obama administration's old
rhinos in the Democrat Party.
A number of whom signed a letter
to Congress expressing
enthusiastic support for the
supreme Li qualified McLennan.
He says then and read on a he
says when he quit few months
later after he had done the
dirty deed of sabotaging this
agency by removing its
enforcement capabilities,
leaving them toothless so the
whole thing was a joke and this
was bound to happen and there's
no way they're gonna prove
anything did happen because they
had nobody investigating it. So
this reports coming up get
everything's coming up dead.
Everybody had anything to say
about this is full of shit. And
he and Bronwyn McLean and quits.
He says he felt he had
accomplished all he could
just walk to have more time with
his family. Oh, yeah. And that's
the beginning of the end right
there in in in 2019. So this
thing was pre done. It was a
done deal. The Bush faction of
the Republican Party, which is a
huge part of the party, Jeb Bush
got his revenge. And the whole
Democratic Party teamed up it
wasn't anybody else. It wasn't
the Russian the Chinese or
anything else. It was an inside
job. That's why nobody's gonna
stand up in Congress, because
the deals over and Trump is
done. And now we're going to
move on from there. And that's
it.
My friend Jean, surging to you.
He said something over
Thanksgiving, which I think is
very astute. We all know Trump
for his you're fired that that's
his brand. You're fired. What
the real issue is that Trump has
a hiring problem. he hires
really shitty people. Now he's
smart that he's able to fire
people and just get rid of him
right away or whenever it's a
problem, but even then, maybe
not. I don't even think Kevin
Ah, or Amy Kony Barrett might
have been good good choices for
him for what he's trying to
achieve.
Bar Well, we know bar was
although bar did a lot of strong
things. We always knew that he
still he and Moeller their
buddies, they they have 911
business that they don't want
anyone to know about and and him
resigning right at this moment.
He has a he has a real hiring
problem he has hired and maybe
the pool is just so it's just
nobody that can do anything that
isn't compromised these days.
That's possible.
But we shall see the executive
order. And the President came
out with a couple more executive
orders which weren't really
discussed the order of
succession with the Department
of Defense. So that keeps Trump
loyals or who he thinks as high
as hired as a loyal close to the
chest if there's some succession
issue. Now, there's also
triggers in there for the if you
recall the we talked about this
the continuation of the National
Emergency respectively.
serious human rights abuses and
corruption, which was his a
human trafficking, executive
order.
There's there's just a number of
different things. I mean, I hear
what you're saying.
I do see a lot of people very
looking very frightened about
what may or may not happen in
the next couple of weeks. Number
one would be just Layne Maxwell.
She is desperately trying to get
a, you know, she's trying to
cobble together $30 million in
bail. She knows what's coming.
If she stays in jail.
She knows she's doing anything
to get out. She's got friends
pitching in money to show that
you know, all these people
support me.
Then again, we'll we'll see. I
mean, now this report is not due
until January. I don't feel so
good about this. But, you know,
the people would counter me
immediately and say, trust the
plan. So we'll see what happens.
We'll see what happens. I am
still very open. And in my heart
of hearts, I am hurt by the fact
that we can have an honest
election not surprised. Because
Gee, we kind of figured there
must be some kind of gambling
going on there. But this level,
certainly of the digital, that's
something we can stop. We can
stop right away. Just stop that
bullcrap voting machines, you
can't trust it.
I don't think there's anything
to do with it. I think that's a
red herring. No, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, there's real. Let me
finish. The whole thing was the
mail in ballots. You send
ballots every time Dick and
Harry in the world, just send
them out by the millions.
They're all gonna vote Democrat.
Correct. I'm not disagreeing
with you. And if you heard
Sidney Powell, I know it's hard
for you to listen to her. She
said because the algorithm
didn't work with the amount of
votes that came in for Trump.
That's when they had to bring in
all these phony baloney ballots.
I believe that happened. That
makes sense.
Now doesn't make sense to me. It
doesn't know at this point,
because I regret revert back to
an old you're telling me 155
million people voted in this
election and often, and the
majority of them are valid legal
votes. Oh, of course not. But if
you get it, we had three or four
bows show up in our house that
weren't anyone here, right? We
didn't send them in, though. But
the point is, is that they were
harvested, they were harvested,
they were collected, they were
shipped all over. Do a mail in
Bell, this is what you're gonna
have to expect both sides can
cheat, right? Oh, and I'm sure
both sides cheated. But I find
that the voting machine evidence
undeniable, it's undeniable. I
think it's very deniable and I
deny it. Well, then you haven't
read the reports. There's
reports that these reports are
very sketchy to know this. Did
you see that?
Major ruse, and yeah, I'm sure
it happened here and there. But
unless they have this $3 billion
agency, sitting there that was
put together by Trump, and they
said, No, nothing happened and
the guy got fired the next day.
Yeah, if this agency is not
going to come up with anything,
then all this other stuff is
just a lot. It's just a lot of
noise.
The agency was put together to
stop this from happening. Yeah.
But john Oh, hold on a second,
as healthcare.gov was set up and
billions of dollars expense to
get health insurance going.
Since when are you surprised
that a government agency sucked?
As soon as they lost your
enforcement capability in 2019.
Thanks to Bush, the bush is and
the ball Obama is working
together. They didn't have
there's no way they could ever
investigating this stuff
properly. But but more that's
fine. I'm good with you there.
But you're saying it didn't
happen. That's what you just
heard you say.
voting machines is bullcrap.
That's what you just said.
There's no evidence. I mean,
they shouldn't have been put in
in the first place. The point is
that when the the state
governments, the way it's set
up, the state governments are
the ones who get to call who
gets to be the electorate, the
and they also broke, they also
broke the rules and the law and
the Constitution doesn't matter.
They their rules or whatever
they want to be if they're
breaking the rules as part of
their system, and they say, only
if done by the legislature, not
by the judges, but that debt. It
still got signed off by somebody
or somebody else. Of course,
we're not I'm not arguing but
you said, Look, I just say I'm
in Nevada, why are you arguing?
corrupt? Why are you arguing?
Because it's arguable. The point
is, is I'm in Nevada and I said
cuz everything's being ignored.
The mechanism is being ignored.
Yeah, it's corrupt. I'm a data
analyst.
Say, I've got a legislature
that's completely corrupt. Mindy
Robbins is always bitching about
this. And you have everybody
okay, we're gonna have a
election. Everybody vote Okay,
we all voted for Trump 100%.
Well, we're gonna send our
electors are dividing, we don't
care. That's their business.
Yes.
And so Biden gets the votes.
So whatever the mechanism
underneath the sign off the sign
off of the, of the electoral
college people, whatever that
mechanism is, no matter how
screwed up it is, they got to
take voting machines doesn't
nothing works, right? The belts
are all switched, is where they
sign off on. That's their
business. And so they sign off
on and Biden gets in. Right, in
the olden days are never used to
be a popular vote, they just
have a meeting and decide on
who's going to be president.
Right. But then
by that logic, then on January 5
of January 6, Vice President
Pence can also do stuff within
his purview.
Well, you should, then there's
this distinct possibility,
though, there's a lot of
alternatives that can happen.
I'm just saying there's not a
chance in hell, any of them are
even gonna show up. Okay. Good.
I think there may be one guy in
all of Congress, one, one of
these characters is going to
protest. And that's going to end
is just to be voted down. If
this is a done deal is over.
Well, I'm You may be right.
I don't think it's a done deal.
I think we still had there's
going to be a couple more tries
before it's a done deal or
before something happens.
But
I don't know. I I have to say
that there's so much in here
that even if whatever reelection
coup tries to do is attempted
here. We have serious problems.
We got we have a serious problem
with the administration that's
coming in, we have a serious
problem with our our voting
system is just I mean, it needs
real review and needs to be
looked at. Because it's the
combination of things that makes
it a problem and yes, mailing
voting.
And hopefully, we'll find out
exactly what went on if what I'm
led to believe we have records
of everything and everything was
being done. And that should come
out in this big report. This is
why I'm a little concerned that
reports not coming out or won't
come out in time. But meanwhile,
we do have some real crap going
down.
which you probably also won't
hear a lot about. Certainly not
if if you're right. The Biden
administration comes into into
office, we won't be hearing much
about China,
even though they're trying to do
stuff in the Senate and in the
house and Capitol Hill trying to
say Hey, you guys, we've got
China all over the place. We've
got China all over the Biden
clan 50 people associate with
the intelligence community
during the our after our hunter
Biden investigation. And the
revelations of the hunter Biden
computer said, Oh, this is, you
know, this is Russian
disinformation. Now we find out
that's real investigation by the
Justice Department. So it's just
galling, and I just have to
point out that the purveyors of
Russian disinformation, Hillary
Clinton's campaign, the DNC, the
steel dossier, the ranking
member, Peters, accusing Senator
Grassley and I of disseminating
Russian disinformation. That's
where the disinformation is
coming. That's where the false
information the lies, just stop
for just a second.
This?
Who is this guy, Ron Johnson, of
course, oh, it's Ron Johnson. I
didn't realize it before. If you
backed it up and started over.
He sounds just like like the
nutty Tom Arnold. Oh, that's a
good point. Hey, by the way,
where our Tom Arnold's PP tapes.
disappointing is that guy 50
people associate with the
intelligence community during
the after our hunter Biden
investigation. And the
revelations of the hunter Biden
computer said, Oh, this is, you
know, this is Russian
disinformation. Now we find out
that's real investigation by the
Justice Department. So it's just
galling, and I just have to
point out that the purveyors of
Russian disinformation, Hillary
Clinton's campaign, the DNC, the
steel dossier, the ranking
member, Peters, accusing Senator
Grassley and I have
disseminating Russian
disinformation. That's where the
dissertation is coming. That's
where the false information, the
lies the false allegations. I
can't sit by here and listen to
this. And say that this is this
is not disinformation, this
hearing today, this is getting
information we have to take a
look at to restore confidence.
In our election integrity, we're
not going to be able to just
move on without bringing up
these irregularities examining
them
providing an explanation and see
where there really are problems
so we can correct it moving
forward. Senator Paul. Mr. Mr.
Chairman, I gotta respond to
that. I mean, you're saying I'm
putting out right. Well, one I
didn't have nothing to do with
this report. You You lied
repeatedly and not you lied
repeatedly in the press, and I
was spreading messages Russian
disinformation. And that was an
outright lie. And I told you to
stop lying, and you continue to
do it. Mr. Chairman, this is not
about airing your grievances. I
know what I don't know what
rabbit hole you're
exactly what Senator Paul says
simply not what we're dealing
with. So Mr. Chairman, you can't
make a good start. And then drop
it there. Yeah, we can listen to
Tom Arnold about the PP tapes
back from back in the day. When
was this this was I love our
archives. We have is this from
2018 what is the power what is
on the tapes that you're gonna
release on on
Donald Trump? You know, he's
this this president, he's gonna
tape this substance available to
the public already should be
disqualified for, for a guy to
to rent a car for instance, he
started day one by calling it
faking his own voice to say his
father had given him his money
and he was really a billionaire.
And he's done. He's admitted to
walk into the Miss Universe
pageant to see them naked and
brag about that on howard stern.
So the stuff that's for public
consumption already is it's just
horrible that that and you know,
the tape that I heard he's uses
the Edward he calls his son,
Eric, the R word for people with
you know, it just just
discussing sex.
Yeah, that was about different
tapes. That was about the race
racist tapes forgot about Yeah,
that never got out either. So
now we do have one final report.
Regarding China and the Biden
crime syndicate from lou dobbs.
Today, Fox News obtained a
letter that further exposes the
entire Biden family's ties to a
Chinese energy company. For
details now we turn to Fox News
correspondent Mike Emanuel, in
Washington, Mike blue. Good
evening, Fox has obtained June
2017 correspondence between
hunter Biden and the chairman of
CFC China energy company, with
hunter offering Best wishes from
the entire Biden family and
urging Yeon Ming to quickly send
a $10 million wire to properly
fund and operate Hunter's joint
venture with the now bankrupt
firm by netted. We are all
hoping to see you here again
soon or in Shanghai, Fox has
told the $10 million transfer to
the joint venture was never
completed. Some allies of
President Trump are saying it
may be time for a special
counsel to look into hunter
Biden's business dealings
concerned by the administration
may not be interested in a
serious criminal investigation.
Also today, a prominent
republican called that big tech
for suppressing the hunter Biden
story, these giant corporate
conglomerates, censoring and
suppressing news directly
bearing on an election weeks
beforehand. The most powerful
corporations in the world.
Facebook, Twitter, working with
the democrat campaign to
suppress legitimize Stop, stop,
stop. I don't know if it's just
me. But this guy sounds like Al
Gore. He does a little bit. It's
the it's a young guy. I forget
his name. Haha, Holly. Holly, I
think is Holly. He's the guy
that's been anti Silicon Valley
forever. And I like him. I think
he's from Tennessee. I want to
say I think he's from Tennessee
almost done seeing news,
directly bearing on an election
weeks beforehand. The most
powerful corporations in the
world, Facebook, Twitter,
working with the democrat
campaign to suppress legitimate
reporting on hunter Biden, who
we now know is under a federal
investigation for criminal wire
fraud tax evasion. Other things?
No poor Hunter, he's going to
have to go away.
Thank Yes, I think it would be
funny. And I think this might
happen before the 20th that a
special prosecutors put in place
to investigate this by Trump or
his or his new Attorney General.
And they just leave him there
when they leave they they're
stuck with this guy you can't
get and they got either fire him
which will be a brouhaha over
that. Yeah. Are they gonna have
to do his thing? It's like it
this is ludicrous except for
Obama. Every one of these
presidents has been under fire
and and everyone went soft on
Obama. They let him do what he
wanted. And I did go I'm pretty
soft on Joe.
It has started yet. They won't
be soft on Joe at all right?
Yeah. If anything, I think this
is more
Move and you're seeing is how
fox is all over to move from the
democrats to get rid of Joe
don't want him out. Yes, they
can bring in the true puppet,
which is a comma. So the final
thing on the China update is
there's not a lot while the UK
is spending some time on the CCP
database with the 1.9 million
names of people who are
affiliated, or if not direct
members of the Chinese Communist
Party who are in companies all
around the globe. And we have in
the US, Boeing, Qualcomm,
Pfizer.
But my favorite was this one,
members of the committee of the
joint branch of the Shanghai
second Disney machine of the
Communist Party of China. I have
no idea what that committee
does. I know. Isn't that great?
Is that really the name? Yes.
It's in this database. Committee
of the
it's the committee again, the
Committee of the joint branch of
the Shanghai second Disney
machine of the community. Yes. I
know the machine it says Disney
machine. Now maybe this is a bad
translation. That could be but
I've received this from several
people. And it's in the database
with the database, we put in the
show notes. And there's a
translated version out there
too. So I don't know.
But they control a lot. So they
will continue and they've got
Tom Cruise on the front lines
and everybody working it out.
And China Joe, Beijing Biden is
almost in office, so I can't
wait. It's gonna be spectacular.
It'll be good for a laugh.
Yes, it'll be good. It'd be very
good for a laugh. Well, these
Chinese are they're they're
overstepping. They're, they're
they're overstepping their
something.
But what's the role phrase or
overstepping their boundaries?
overstepping the boundary, the
boundary? They're, they're
overdoing it. You're gonna be
sorry. Well, I hope so. I don't
know how they'll be sorry.
If Joe's in office, you think
anything's gonna happen, nothing
will happen.
You don't know that. And I'm
gonna just going to say up
front. Whereas I still have hope
in 45. Savin say saving the day
in the Constitution and the
Republic.
I have no illusions over what's
going to happen if he doesn't,
and moving forward, we're just
completely controlled by China.
Big tech everything.
Well, I'm glad we're controlling
coin all these locals around
here were controlled by Putin.
That's just California man,
Texas is different. And with
that, I'd like to thank you for
your courage. saying the morning
to you the man who really put
the sea in the sea is a Jhansi
devorah and Mr. Neal Mr. Adam
Curry also in the morning, all
boots on the ground in the air
subs in the water games in the
nights out there in the morning
to our trolls in the troll room.
Let's see how you doing on this
fine December day. 1918 is the
number. That's the trolls we got
hanging out. It's nice if we
cracked 2000 But okay, I'll just
have to let you slide for today.
You do on Thursday. It is hard
to have done. Yes. Hands up
trolls Hands up. Zoom meetings
instead.
Yeah, I'm sure they are. The
trolls are to be found. If you
feel like you're affiliated or
would like to learn how to
become one, go to no agenda
stream.com you can dive in
there. And there's a troll room
which is a chat room with
trolls. And there's a stream
which you can listen to
simultaneously listen to the
show live we do it on Thursdays
and Sundays many shows are done
live. In addition to that.
We have a social network which
you can ask for an invite. Don't
ask me ask the trolls. No
agenda. Social calm is where the
signal to noise is remarkably
high because it's a federated
social network that does not
utilize any algorithms you come
in, you start at the top. When
you read something you've read,
you've probably seen everything
you need to see there's no other
things flying around trying to
hook in is just there for your
pleasure and your enjoyment and
for usefulness. That is no
agenda social.com and then we
need to thank the artists who
did the artwork for Episode
Episode 1303 we titled that one
the Redneck herring. This was
the bumper car done by tungsten
nail who is no stranger to the
to the artwork. It wasn't my
favorite. You'd liked it right
off the bat you I gave in I
guess that Oh yeah. I didn't
come up. No, you had one that
you like but you didn't have an
you didn't have any argument
then which one was that? That
was the problem you didn't die
bail.
Well, you know as as just
witness, sometimes it just makes
sense to stop arguing with you
because you're right numb wrong.
So that's it.
I think that would be true most
of that's and that's usually how
I just ended it. That's the
easiest. Yeah, let's let's do
it. here's the here's the one
that that's I'm looking at these
now. I forgot which one you
liked. Yeah. The Tata nail one.
I you
I liked it for a number of
reasons. One it looked like a
slipper very comfortable
looking. And it was cute is a
cute little bumper car which we
had some thing and you didn't
really have a strong candidate.
And you finally gave it I don't
think you'd like you didn't
mention it. You didn't like the
best podcast in the universe,
emblazoned across the top like
that. No, I didn't like this as
the letters the fonts any of
that? No, I didn't really like
yeah, you were birthed about a
lot of this. Now the one I that
we kind of got passed over and I
had I'd used it for the
newsletter because it was so
it's such a good piece was
Riley's Santa Claus. Walmart
Santa yes we did discuss that
one and by the way you're seeing
all of this in your podcasting
2.0 app go to new podcast apps
calm
and I I missed one of the gags
unfortunately on this one I may
have actually promoted this more
if I had got the joke, which I
did I felt bad about and then
which one was this newsletter?
Which one was this? Well I
complain about what kind of a
Stan has got a blue hat on? Ah
yes, I recall the combo Yeah.
And I then I look back Oh, he's
wearing a Walmart costume.
Because he's a Walmart
employees. You see his name
there's a little name tag on his
shoulder so the Walmart color
was put instead of red for the
hat. And I didn't get the joke.
So I joined that got removed the
I did plug it on the newsletter
so yeah, I feel don't feel
totally bad about it. But there
wasn't really anything else I
don't think
No, I like China Joe and his
gang but even we both agreed
that wasn't good enough far but
it was good. I liked it. It was
funny.
That controversial You did say
to me though, at the end,
because you didn't like this
piece.
That I'm going to have to
explain it.
Yeah, public somehow somehow I
somehow remember there being a
lot more controversy then than
there is now. Really remember
why
put forth. Controversy was
simple. You didn't like the
peace but you had no alternative
alternative now. That's right.
I didn't like but I liked the
peace. I still I still like the
peace. I like it. I think it's
cute. I'd like to have a bumper
car that looked like that be
fantastic. Oh, so sweet.
This is only a part of the time
and talented people put into
into these shows. I want to
thank Neil who's been doing a
kick ass job of sending clips.
But we have so many people
who've really honed their skills
on making clips. Again, it's not
very helpful. If you say this is
an hour and a half, you'll
definitely get something out of
it. Yeah, yeah, I definitely
won't. I mean, because I get
five of those. You won't listen
to them five of those a day.
Also. And this is all said with
love. I'm your producer. So I'm
just you know, I'm like Tom
Cruise in you know, for a
second, except you won't get
fired.
If you if you got a hearing, for
example, don't send 15 clips.
Have you ever heard us play 15
clips of anything? Three max for
if it's crazy out there. You
have to kill your darlings make
your selections. That's how we
make the show even better.
Because you know, then listening
through 15 clips that are all
two minutes. That's another half
hour I just run out of time in
the day. I'm sure john you have
the same but but it's really
appreciated what people are
doing and we love when people
come in with their treasure,
which is the third leg of the
value for value stool. That's it
we're and we'd like to honor
these donors with their
appropriate titles of executive
producer and associate executive
producer of the no agenda Show
Episode 1304
indeed, and we're gonna start
with
sir Mecca. nudo dela paz in new
brown fells Texas. Yay. I wish
the New Braunfels barbecue
company was still in business
$1,000
and the Hondo grill one of the
greatest devices ever made for
cooking. Sat sir makan nudo de
la paz, I hit my wife Elizabeth
in the mouse two or three times.
And then about two months ago.
I found her repotting plants on
the back porch and listening of
her own volition who knows to
the greatest podcast in years
nowadays. She asked me about
segments of this show and we
discuss it on a regular basis.
You're saved.
Yes, yeah, I agree. Your
deconstructions have taken what
was already a match made in
heaven to a level of marital
harmony that I never imagined
She is an instant aim Yay.
I wonder is going to give her
the executive producer ship to
Dame sparkler of new Browns
fells please play the jingle
with the park Pink Floyd under
it. At first john thought it was
a dog but it sounds native to
me. Sounds native to me like
Navajo or Pawnee. I'm not. I
have no idea what this
references in any any event
putting Pink Floyd under it is
genius. We love you guys. Yes, I
think that he gets the executive
producer ship she gets the dame
hood. I'm fine with that. So
they can kind of split it up.
They are no agenda together
after all, and what he's
referring to is not something we
do. I'd love to take credit for
all these great jingles. No, no,
we can't do that. It's Yoko in
the Bulldog.
There you go. It's actually a
Friday. It's a French Bull
Terrier, I think is what it is.
It's labeled Yoko and the
Bulldog. So that's how I
remember it. Yeah, I thought it
was a Boston Terrier, right?
Yes, sir. 22 up Pacific
Northwest and Lake Stevens
Washington $500.
See the one somebody sent a note
in No. Make good No, not yet. I
know which one it is? No, no.
michael mansell.
333 ah Sir 22 the Pacific
Northwest there's a bunch of
people that went in Michael
wrote it I'll read it later.
Checking in not sure why my
notes from the last donation
never went through to your both
your emails but Oh, well. Since
the holidays are coming up. I
would like to wish you two fine
gentlemen all the knights and
dames and all the douchebags out
there and Merry Christmas and
Happy New Year. kinkos Can I get
a TPP jobs don't eat me Joe.
Don't enslave me camela and
Obama you might die.
Yeah, we can do that. We'll do
them kind of in those orders.
You might die.
You've got karma.
Douglas Proctor and Duncan
Oklahoma $500. Thank you for
what you provide us and wish you
a Merry Christmas.
Merry Christmas to you. We love
that note. Very nice. Thank you.
Nathan Joseph. Will Atlantic in
Manchester New Hampshire. 333.
Forgive me pot father has been
three years since my last
donation during the two for one
dealio please give me a D
douchey. an apostle is the shout
out
for
deducing first.
You've been
okay.
Okay, let's just start. Just get
this back together is pronounced
Vojtech. Yes. Vojtech weaponry,
my w OJTK. My business mostly
revolves around badass
adjustable gas blocks for ar 15.
So if you need to choke your gas
hole, look no further. No. I
gotta write this down. choke
your gas hole. That's just
something you want to say from
time to time. Look no further.
No agenda listeners get 12% off
of on my click adjustable gas
blocks with coupon code 33. So
order up. Nice. Thank you for
the
cute. Thank you for the great
show and amygdala maintenance.
Keep your powder dry. All right.
Thank you, Nathan. Appreciate
it. I'll do a man. I'll do Mandy
be here. This is from Mandy's
from Bennington, Vermont, comes
in with a sequential 234568 in
the morning john and Adam found
y'all via JRE and could not be
happier. Well, we definitely
need to throw in the Rogen
donation.
Making donation as a former self
proclaimed bleeding heart
liberal until April of this year
I've gotten quite the education
over the last nine months. It's
been a roller coaster of
emotion. There's been loss of
family and friends who might
change perspective. But for the
first time in 53 years, I stand
solid in my convictions and it
feels damn good. I enjoy
listening to your show because
it's not only informative, it is
entertaining. And since I
basically lost all desire for
anything Hollywood, it's nice to
still have something enter some
ate some entertainment value in
my life. I want to know where we
go here.
happened I just I want to thank
Adam for replying to my past
email and I'm curious if you
ever got to listen to my podcast
rerouted. Not sure if I did
I know it's mediocre at best
compared to you both but I enjoy
learning as I go since this is
my first donation in my quest
for Dane hood, I will need a dd
dd douche. This donation is a
late birthday present for myself
from 12 five and I'm happy to
contribute to the cause. I would
also like to request them health
Congress for my upcoming three
year post colon cancer surgery
songs chemotherapy on the 28th
but doc says the three year mark
is pivotal and I will only need
a once a year checkup if all is
going well going forward. Are
you know I'm fine but little
extra karma doesn't hurt to any
and all listeners Please take it
for me to get screened. I was
misdiagnosed for 10 years and
would not have needed life
altering surgery if I had if I
had gotten a colonoscopy. That
being said I am not have the F
cancer mindset as I learned how
strong light I am through all of
it and that is a gift. It is
also I could not care less about
COVID because something is
eventually going to kill me but
I'm not living in fear of
whatever it may be sorry to be
so wordy thank you for reading
this All the best to you your
families and the no agenda
listeners this holiday season
Merry Christmas Hanukkah Kwanzaa
and to all and happy new year as
well Mandy be yes, we got some
health karma for you man. dB
right here.
You've got karma.
Oh, I just realized that our
friend in Australia Michael is
came in late with his donation
it will not appear on today's
show. Kevin redacted $233.33
my annual birthday present to
myself this show has been
outstanding this year. Keep up
the great work. I also like to
give a shout out to my buddy
Josh at the acquired tasting
podcast
card tastings podcast Hmm. It's
a show about tasting wine, beer
and spirits from all over the
world and the foods that
compliment them. During the that
sort of thing. Check them out at
the acquired tastings podcast.
foamer karma, please.
Karma
I will check out that podcast.
Meanwhile, Scott pancake in
Guilford Vermont $200 in one
cent. Regarding the no evidence
for the UFO his comment I
suggest you search for a wind
mountain in New Mexico on Google
Maps is a flying saucer
refueling
it or is it a flying saucer
refueling on uranium crystals?
Okay, yes, the answer way is and
the answer is yes, it is. But
okay. Anyways, Adam is always
giving pennies away so I thought
I'd leave one for the jar. Oh
that's very sweet. So should we
just say any roads now let's
just move it over um so tickets
hired anyone any instead of any
ways any roads? Any roads Yeah.
Anyways, anyways any roads
Germania project disagrees. $200
from Alhambra, California no
jingles no no nothing.
Got it. We will not do we will
do nothing. You got it and and
means no nothing
to code monkey Baron of Dayton
Renner, South Dakota. $200. ITM
Love you guys. Merry Christmas.
Please wish my brother Zach is
on the list is Eisler a product
and a producer and listener the
best podcast and university
belated birthday as he turned 38
on Monday that for December 14.
Please send out a good karma for
everybody. Adios mofos All
right.
You've got
karma
Richard Guerin in Thunder Bay
ontario canada 200 bucks I
looked for his note he's sent
notes in before nothing appeared
under donations or under his
name. Farmer Todd
farmer Todd Tia Dalton t a.or
tie a dot and I'm sorry Tie a
Tie a dot okay. In wellsboro
Pennsylvania
Reverend Bitcoin jingle and one
five x speed it's sweeter when
is faster and do the 2016
Bordeaux karma he folks
greetings here is a some folding
money from a farmer who bought
the Bitcoin as a joke five years
ago, and I just sold it Wow.
Thanks g Jcd for the 2016
Bordeaux tip. Tastes pretty good
but my circle of friends now
think I'm slightly dainty. To
hell with them. It's gotta be a
drunk donation and it looks blue
stitute Yeah, there are no
agenda social on the SIR Spencer
the wolf calls it na s. I do
have a question which cabinet
position will Korean pop be
occupying if the seitan Biden
gets
In slidin Biden Many thanks from
the upper tie at cotton in
pensive Kentucky farmer Todd tie
a dot and pronounce tie a
cotton. Okay.
I think he had a little bit too
much of that Bordeaux. Bordeaux
Yeah, he was just finished. And
maybe you should put your player
on 1.5 speed because I can't
jack this up for you
all hell is gonna break loose
and you're gonna need a Bitcoin
you've got karma.
man if he bought in 2015 he's a
happy camper. Now couple. Yeah.
happy camper. happy campers
should all be so lucky. So I got
a couple of notes. I want to get
out of the way.
Our friend Matthew drop co sir
Matthew came in and met we had
sent a note in I put this
picture in the newsletter. He
apparently had his gallbladder
removed by a robot. Yes, we
thought we gave him karma for
that special on the last show.
He's got more calm recommend. A
Mike O'Reilly wrote in I think
we soliciting a note from him.
my beautiful wife donate and
executive producer credit to me
for show 1303 I was last show
for Thursday show to exchange
this gift for her game hood. I'd
like to exchange for Dame hood
and would like our feedback is
not quite a gift to the module
but it's close. It's even no boo
Oh Henry is they don't even know
who Oh Henry is anymore. I am
the slide whistle dad referred
referenced by Taylor, Tyler
Lewis and Episode 1295 and I've
been listening to show for a
while now my wife Jan Houghton
deserves to be a dame for
Christmas and I would like to
offer this accounting proposal
to make her a dame and he's got
a bunch of donations things that
he did and his combination of
stuff. So can we make put her on
the list?
Well, I guess it's not on the
list now I can do that sure.
donation Krista. Jan. So give me
the name. Big jam agenda damn
I'm trying to figure out what
our names gonna be to be a fair
amount I hope some standing yeah
Yeah, yeah. Uh I just did her
just
that's a good question he's got
no real name for her good didn't
get back to us so we can do it
all properly. I will you around.
We need round table stuff. We
need to know the name Come on
people. Come on. We want to do
this right.
And do we have any we have one
more here is the last one. in
the morning. It's been a year
just as I had been out I Ian
outed me as a douchebag. I'm
donating today to request a de
douchey to help reach
knighthood. Okay, this will be
later in the show but give give
Dillard ortego or Andre I guess
Andre would know last name. Give
him a D do Xing and we're done.
No
you've been know we're not we're
not going to waste a bunch of
make goods Now we do have a make
good. This is from Dred Scott
whose note was not read.
And
he's the Earl at large. I don't
know this has gone through so
many different times. I'm just
happy to read it make everybody
satisfied. Gentlemen, thank you
for the amygdala protection
protecting deconstruction twice
weekly on Thursdays your bi
weekly deconstruction has helped
me keep me mentally grounded in
these troubled times of media
induced hysteria and
disinformation. This note covers
two donations for today the
first 113 100 to mark this
story, Episode Number 1300. The
second is for $107.28 which I'd
plan to donate to support
Episode 1299 but got sidetracked
creating chapters for the
recently enhanced podcasting 2.0
compliant chapter markers for
Episode 1298 and 1299 of the
best podcast in the universe.
These donations combined with my
previous donations make me
eligible for a title change
until today, I've held my
protector in abeyance if it is
unacceptable to the peerage
committee and Sir David Foley
granduca, the United States of
my nation I'd like to put down
some roots and claim a
territory, I hereby claim the
territory of the Southern
California mug,
McGregor mega region, and
request the following title
change from Dred Scott Earl at
large to Dred Scott, Duke of the
Southern California mega region,
as defined by the book of
knowledge. The Southern
California mega region includes
Southern California, which
includes 10 of California's 53
counties, Imperial Kern, Los
Angeles, orange, Riverside, San
Bernardino, San Diego, Santa
Barbara, San Luis Obispo and
Ventura counties extending
northeast into Las Vegas,
Nevada, and South across the
Mexican border into Tijuana.
Thank you. I'm so happy I got
that information. Dred Scott,
proudly owner of the only known
item to be released from the
Dvorak archive vault, the
Microsoft Bob frisbee
So now you can put a, a memory
to the name and he will indeed
be crowned appropriately as Earl
at large Duke of the Southern
California he's the one who
bought the yes yes he well he
should there's good news it was
that I've put up a rash in my
daughter put up an Etsy site
called the devore x shop sh o p
p go look it up on Etsy and find
it wastefully it why with p p y
y devore x shop.com but we can
get direct shop pp.com so what's
on divorce shop calm but my
collection of photographs blow
ups miscellaneous items that I'm
getting rid of all the
photographs are signed and
they're not numbered because
they're one of a kind each one
but divorce I've shot price
appropriately Dvorak all one
word.
I don't know.
Where to go to Etsy and it is a
search engine on its
Etsy okay.
But yeah, I showed you balls
kinds of photos and big large I
haven't got into my blow up
giant, you know, five foot foot
things yet, but I'll put those
up to my goodness. I don't think
I've ever been on Etsy. devora
shop. Let me just see, I want to
eat your pee pee. Yeah, gotcha.
Gotcha.
Okay, I'm not finding it. But I
may not be a good Etsy or I
don't know if I'm doing that
right now. We'll figure it out.
I'll put a link in the
newsletter. We appreciate the
support, highly appreciate the
support from these producers,
who now can proudly display
their titles as executive
producer or associate executive
producer of Episode 1304 of the
no agenda show the best podcast
in the universe. Thank you so
much. Thanks for hanging in.
Thanks for bringing all the
things that we need and keeping
this show rolling, especially in
these times, where anything you
say is probably Russian
disinformation. So we have to be
careful too. We got to keep
moving ahead. Can't take any
commercials or corporate money
that's just never going to work
for us. If you'd like to
participate for the next
episode, which will be on
Sunday, please go to devora.org
slash and a and thank you again
for your time your talents and
your treasure and the value for
value model of the show. Our
formula is this. We go out
Shut up.
Okay.
So we have Kaylee.
Okay, this is something else you
want to discuss first? Um, well,
I was gonna kind of lead into. I
mean, I got a lot of
Joe Biden cabinet like stuff and
build back better kind of
things. Okay, let's do that.
First.
I do have a Biden clip. Yes, you
know, it's not a full on that
are true. gaff is kind of minor,
you probably have some better
material once you just run with
it. Well, what's your Biden clip
you set me up now?
where he's going on about he's
got he's talking to a bunch of
educators and he makes a stupid
comments. And the Biden does
under the bites the Biden clip,
first raid team that you would
all be proud of.
And we're all ready to go and
doing an awful lot of work right
now. But here's the thing that I
want to mention.
You know, there's already a
circumstance where nationwide
because of the requirement of
school districts,
county offices,
mayors, governors having to
balance their budgets.
They've already had to layoff
666,000 teachers.
666,000 teachers have been laid
off already since March. And,
and I'm worried, Tony, that I
know in Noblesville, you have a
force about 135 firefighters.
And
the question is going to be when
do we have to start laying off
because the counties in the
cities don't have the money.
They can't deficit spend they
have to spend based on balancing
their budget when the first
responders and the fire service
will be laid off? What was the
what was this recorded was the
context of this.
Talking to a bunch of locals
schmucks locals there, it's a
zoom calls some sorting is
666,000 nuts bullcrap, but it
turns out just look
good. The fact checkers could
find a way to rationalize it.
Because Joe Biden will never be
factcheck false. Yeah, but we
all heard the 666 we heard it.
We know what that we know what
the idea is. Even it was 666. I
would have said 6687. Just to
just to not say it.
Yeah, that's what I would you
know, I agree I would do, but
wasn't 666 Anyway, it was like,
some half that if not, if less,
it, that's all people involved.
It's just a number cobbled
together just nonsense. Yeah.
But why 6667 is a mark of the
beast. factcheck false. Yeah.
So before we actually earlier
this week, the vo Jaiden was in
Georgia campaigning because we
have this to run off races which
could determine
the power in the Senate and thus
the power being the United
States and the world. Quite
honestly, it comes down to too
to vote too little too little
runoff elections in Georgia.
Here's what Joe had to say. In
the meantime, Biden was in
Georgia Tuesday, where control
of the US Senate will be decided
by runoff elections next month.
You're voted as if your life
depended on it. Well, guess
what?
Now you're gonna have to do it
again.
Okay, so we know what to expect
as already 75,000 new registered
voters for this runoff election.
Amazing. Good work, Stacey
Abrams. And then Joe came out
after Tuesday, and claimed his
victory claimed his victory as
the according to him in the
mainstream media. It's all done.
It's end you john. It's all
done. It's in the can the
Electoral College has decided it
is.
So ladies, gentlemen, welcome to
your brand new president. Good
evening, my fellow Americans
over the past few weeks
in each state, Commonwealth and
district without regard to party
or political preference, he
slumming already right the
beginning here, listen to this,
this fantastic I can't I can't
get one sentence out maybe My
fellow Americans over the past
few weeks over the past few
weeks, okay. Officials in each
state, Commonwealth and district
without regard to party or
political preference of
certified certified winning
candidates.
Certified today, member of the
of the Electoral College,
representing the certified
winner cast their votes for
president and vice president
knighted states, and an act just
as old as our nation itself.
Once again, the American America
the rule of law, our
Constitution, and the will of
the people prevail. our
democracy pushed, tested,
threatened, proved to be
resilient, true and strong.
the electoral college votes
which occurred today reflect the
fact that even in the face of
the public health crisis, unlike
anything we've experienced in
our lifetimes, and now he's
really starts to fall apart.
We're only 16 minutes into the
speech, people voted a voted
record numbers were Americans
voted this year, and they've
ever voted the history United
States of America. Over 155
million Americans were
determined to have their voices
heard, and their votes counted.
Yeah, wait a minute. That's not
the falling apart. But it came
later, when he had to deliver
the message. The final message
for the New World Order got
under control and getting the
nation vaccinated against this
virus, delivering immediate
economic help so badly needed by
so many Americans are hurting
day and then building our
economy back better was in doing
so we need to work together to
give each other a chance.
Now, that was the public
appearances where I think
everyone kind of noticed that
the president elect the office
of the president elect was
coughing and stammering and was
not a great appearance. It was
15 minutes. just didn't feel
really jubilant even though that
was the entire reason for it and
to bring you COVID could be I
mean, this would be the this
would be about the right time
for him to die. A guy can you
imagine? Oh, no, I can really
imagine that. And again, it
would make a lot of sense,
because Camila is the puppet.
And Obama is the puppet master.
And he admitted this earlier
when he was on cobit. This was I
think this was I don't know when
this was
Obama admitted it won't listen,
it doesn't matter. He's still
admitting what he wants. Did you
miss you? Did you ever look at
something going on in the news
and go you know what the
situation needs for Barack
Obama.
Yeah, I've said this before I,
people would ask me, no one what
you know, now do you wish like
you had a sec, a third term?
And I used to say,
you know, what if I could make
an arrangement where
I had a, I had a stand in front
man or woman and they had an
earpiece in and I was just in my
basement in my sweats, looking
through the stuff, and then I
could sort of deliver the lines,
but somebody else was doing all
the talking and ceremony. I'd be
fine with that. Because I found
the work fascinating. Yeah.
Okay. They do like putting it
right in our face, don't they?
You know, I never heard this
before. I want you to take take
the clip of the day. Thank you.
I was kind of extending.
Yeah, yeah, pretty much. Yeah.
I'd be sitting in my basement
when I was a little intercom if
be good to go.
And it certainly wasn't
happening. When Joe had his
little, his his private zoom
conversation with
the Democratic Party, a lot of
progressives were on this call.
And, again, we have audio that
was leaked. I don't know if it's
on purpose or not, it does show
a very different side of Joe,
he's very assertive. Me, I don't
think he's cognitive. But he's
very assertive in what he's
saying. We'll start with
that people need to stop all
this negative talk. This is, I
believe, one of the progressives
on the zoom call, who was quite
upset because if you look
around, you'll see
the progressive wing, these
squad, ao C's, the Black Lives
Matter. The black and brown
community protectors, they're
not seeing any love from, from
Joe with his cabinet
appointments or anything. In
fact, I think people are waiting
for some money. But no, no, no,
Joe is going to push back real
hard. And he's going to remind
us that he is the office of the
president elect, because of the
one big lie detailed, a lot of
people in our community are
getting a little anxious because
they are not seeing enough of
the progress they thought they
would have seen at this point.
Let's not disappoint them. And
let's not get to a place where
voters in Georgia begin to
second guess. Okay, never mind.
I've got I've got to go. Let me
respond. There's a lot to
respond to here. Let's get some
straight. You shouldn't be
disappointed. What I've done so
far is more than anybody else
has done this far. Okay, number
one, number two. I mean, what I
say when I say it, all right. I
mean, when I say when I say, All
right, I'm the only person who's
ever run on three platforms that
I was told could not possibly
win the election. And I never
cease Trump won was on restoring
the soul of this country.
Because what I saw happen in
Charlottesville, I was in no one
else was talking about it. The
words the President's matter.
Nobody else no progressive. was
talking about? I did. Because no
one wanted to propagate that
insulting ly Joe. He's talking,
of course, about the various
people. So he's rather This is
really a terrific clip. Because
he's like, taking credit for
winning by pride, but he thinks
is still doesn't know what that
it's a lie. Is that stupid?
I think he's dead serious.
Ladies and gentlemen, your next
president.
Yeah, but there's more. There's
more, there's more. There's
more. He Joe was also not gonna
do anything.
Because now
now he has principles, his
principles are no executive
orders, because
I don't know, something
Constitution, the Constitution.
And so there's some things that
I'm going to be able to do by
executive order. I'm not gonna
hesitate to do it. But what I'm
not going to do is I'm not going
to do what Euston binita, you
probably used to get angry with
me during the debates, when
you'd have some of the people
who were forced on day one, I'm
gonna inject in order to do
this. Not within the
constitutional authority. I am
not going to violate the
constitution.
executive authority that my
progressive friends talk about
is way beyond the bounds. And is
one of you said maybe you were
ever ever now, whether it's far
left or far right.
There is a constitution. It's
our only hope. Our only hope.
And the way to deal with it is
where I have executive
authority. I will use it to undo
every single damn thing. This
guy's done by executive
authority. But I'm not going to
exercise executive authority,
where it's question right
can come along and say, I can do
away with assault weapons.
There's no executive authority
doing that.
So he's not taking away our
guns. He's not gonna override
executive orders. Wow, no, no.
He said he's going to override
all the undo everything Trump
did. And I'll bet money they
can't do it. Well, we know from
the Supreme Court ruling
regarding DACA, that most of
these executive orders will have
to remain in effect well into a
year or a year and a half into
the next administration's term.
It are structured that what's
the claim? Yeah. So I'm all in
on that. That sounds hilarious.
Let me just see if I had any
more build back bed. Well, the
great reset and kind of talked
about that.
Yeah, maybe we should get to
your special I've been very
excited about this. You teased
it in the newsletter. In fact,
you you you set the you set
yourself up for this on the
previous show. So everybody is
waiting with bated breath.
So I don't think you just may be
fearful that this will be a last
last class Kaylee. So I think I
made probably one, I probably
made too many clips. Or I've got
like, six. You look like a no
agenda producer.
Yeah, I do. Because I am. Yes.
Uh, now she got. She's more
combative than before,
which is good. But you did a
couple of things. Couple of
things are kind of minor. And
for example, I want to play this
play a couple of minor ones that
were no big deal. She took three
or four questions on Trump. Is
it gonna get a shot? Is he gonna
get a shot? Is he gonna go on TV
and get a shot? Why
isn't he go on TV and get a
shot? Or first answer was I
didn't clip which was, Hey, he's
had COVID. Why does he need a
shot kind of makes sense. So
this became he didn't want to
get into too much of that. But
he needs a shot. He's got to get
a shot on TV, according to these
people. And this is the calean
the Trump shot. This is a
classic answer. She gave it at
least twice.
Example for Americans to give
them confidence doctors, Dr.
Fauci as well as the month of
slowly folks that today that
they think President Trump
should get the vaccine is a no,
because for himself would be to
set an example. Will he do that?
Like why not do it just to show
Americans because he also wants
to show Americans that our
priority are the most most
vulnerable, there will be some
senior administration officials
taking it publicly to instill
that confidence. It is very
important. And the President No,
but you'll you'll learn in the
next few days who that is, those
individuals will be but they
will be taking it publicly to
instill confidence. The
president wants to send a
parallel message which is, you
know, our long term care
facility residents and our
frontline workers are paramount
and importance and he wants to
set an example in that regard.
Yeah, me, me, me, me. Me. Me.
Me. Me. Me. Yeah. So Trump, I
don't think Trump's gonna take
the shot out and think he's,
he's had COVID Why would he take
this shot? It makes no sense. I
mean, why would why would
anybody look at a celebrity or a
politician and think oh, yeah,
that's the real shot. I can
never think this How could you
ever believe a celebrate it? All
the time Tom Cruise. I think
that we believe him.
Yeah, I'm in half agreement
except the true believers down
in Hollywood and there's plenty
of them. Block stepped up. Rob
Reiner. Don't take the shot and
he'll take it real shot. I was I
was chatting with the with the
Zoomers.
And so the two highlights of so
far for them the past couple of
weeks has been not not not happy
Joe Biden got in but happy that
we got that horrible orange man
out. And that's the only day
like by me and it's like a merit
badge. It's like Haha, we did
it. I'm so happy. I'm so proud
of us is fantastic. We made sure
that he that horrible racist
scum of a human is not even
issues lower than human being
that he that he is not
reelected. That was great. And
then the next thing is, and
we've got a vaccine. I'm
scheduled for this week. How
about you? I'm so excited. Yay,
vaccine.
So they're all in big Lee. Yeah,
okay. Well, that's fine.
A, see what happens. It's one
way of testing the thing. This
whole idea, I think it's a great
way to test it. I mean,
true believers are going they're
getting
shot and see what happens
because this is not a normal
shot. And if you'd wanted, I'm
not advising people not to get
the shot, you need to know.
But I want to see what happens.
Yeah, I'll hang back.
Yeah, you can wait, what's the
rush? Yeah, well, you know, I
don't think there's any COVID
going around anymore. That's
just my opinion. Hello, that's
wrong. There's a new strain in
the UK. What are the new
science? science science? Okay,
so, here's another minor one.
This is Kate. Kaylee discussing
something that's not discussed
by the mainstream media. I don't
understand why not. But Trump is
gonna gonna veto the NDA.
You don't want to wait. You
don't know why the media is not
discussing the vetoes. It's the
media that you don't understand
why they won't discuss this
veto, which I don't understand.
Specifically, when the President
will detail the National Defense
Authorization Act, when he's
gonna send the paperwork over?
And why would he do that, given
the fact that passed on veto
proof majorities. And so he
still does plan to veto. The NDA
don't have a timeline for you on
that. But he does plan to veto
it. He wants to make every
effort to protect our military
men and women on and will
prioritize military funding and
the big omnibus bill, but he
also has other important
priorities. And I should say
problems with the NDA beyond
just the absence of Section 230.
repeal of and beyond the
inclusion of the war and
amendments on one of the
provisions of concern is troop
provisions about troop
withdrawal and deployment in
Afghanistan, South Korea, and
Germany. And so there are a
number of provisions that he's
gone China but no republican
agreement on that. Why does he
think
so by not including a section
230 repeal? What you're in
effect allowing is Twitter to
continue to not censor Chinese
propaganda. Recently, there was
a tweet by the US, the Chinese
Embassy in United States about
the shinjang province in
allowing all citizens to enjoy
the same rights, including
freedom of religion, that
clearly is not the case, as the
wiggers have been absolutely
tortured, in that province that
there was another tweet that
they allowed about the virus
originating in Wu Han, they said
it was not it did not originate
in Wu Han that obviously is
Chinese just information. And
the President's priority is to
ensure that that isn't
permitted.
So we've luckily talked about
this that I what I heard
initially is he wanted to
complete repeal of Section 230,
which I would for selfish
reasons would be against because
we kind of run on that. So Luke
comes to no agenda social calm,
we don't want we need some
protection over what what what
people will say over there.
I would like I would like an
enforcement or I would like a
modification perhaps.
Apparently, this thing was
passed in the House in the
Senate by enough people to be
veto proof as they have to have
was it two thirds of the of the
Senate has been as is necessary
for the override. I you know, I
thought it was 60%. But whatever
it is did this a lot different
than being veto? This, by the
way wasn't discussed, but it's a
lot different being veto proof,
and then actually overriding the
veto, because I got to put your
hand up? Yes, you do. And
what is that other thing that
they mentioned was also kind of
important. Shoot? Oh, is that?
Yeah, the troop drawdown This is
your so the National Defense
Authorization Act is what that
is. This is where a lot of
interesting things happen years
ago, the Smith mundt Act, which
forbids the American government
from property from using
propaganda on its own people was
repealed, which is a part of the
problem if you think about it.
That was so that
Voice of America and all of its
online, you know, the the
broadcast Board of Governors,
which is the propaganda unit,
Tucker Carlson, his dad was a
member
so that they can continue to
propagandize on the internet,
which some American citizens
might see, but now be probably
more targeted towards American
citizens. That was so that's
that kind of stuff does pass.
And then we have the troop draw
downs, which you know, it's I
have not read the entire NDA
this time around. Usually I get
to it, but you know, that they
don't want to draw down the
troops the way the President has
said that. He said, we're
bringing everybody home and they
go right into the nuts, the NDA
and they say now we're gonna
leave people here and the people
there will close that base. And
so they don't give a crap
Because ultimately, the not the
military itself, but the
military industrial complex
needs this bill. That is their
budget for the next year. What
are they going to get to spend
and on on what doesn't even
matter
but
How much money can they pocket?
How much? How much money Can I
grab? And and I agree that
propaganda certainly from the
Chinese Communist Party is
damaging.
So let's listen to what she has
to say about the Russian
hackers. Could you comment on
the Russian hackers breaching
several federal agencies? How,
how serious was this breach? And
is the Trump administration
considering retaliate? Look, the
US government were aware of all
of these reports, we're taking
all necessary steps to identify
and remedy any possible issues
related to the situation. As one
step in that process. Sister has
issued an emergency directive on
Sunday night for all federal
civilian agencies to review
their networks for indicators of
compromise, and disconnect or to
power down solar winds or Eon
products immediately. So we are
taking a hard look on this and
obviously, take any sort of
cyber hacks very seriously. And
just one more question on Russia
since Russian President Vladimir
Putin has congratulated
President Elect Joe Biden any
any comments on that from the
Russian president? No comment on
that. I leave it to the
president to react to that. He
spoken to President Trump Not
that I'm aware. Yeah, man flag
what you're doing.
Yeah, they always slip that kind
of thing. And now, fairweather
friends Vladimir Putin is
doing man.
So let's listen to Kay Kaley go
off on swalwell. This is Jim.
Yes, I'm sure she had a lot to
say about him unfortunate that
it doesn't give much coverage in
the mainstream media. But I
guess we shouldn't be surprised
because in the last 24 or 48
hours, there have been quite a
few stories that not gotten a
ton of coverage in the
mainstream media. As former
White House press secretary Ari
Fleischer said, bias is often
found in stories the press does
not cover. And last week, we
found out that democrat
congressman Eric swalwell was
infiltrated by an alleged
Chinese spy, the spy cozied up
to swalwell raised funds for his
2014 campaign and even planted
an intern in his office and that
relationship continued until the
FBI briefed him in 2015. And
that was some very good
reporting done by axios. But
after entangling with this spy
for years, swalwell
hypocritically went on to be one
of the lead instigators of the
Russia collusion hoax in the
impeachment. Sham swalwell wrote
this on his congressional
webpage, President Trump and his
team are directly and indirectly
tied to Russia. That was not
true. He then said in September
of 2020, the President has a
compromised relationship with
Russia on true April of 2019. He
said President Trump certainly
acts on Russia's behalf and acts
like Russia's leader, not true.
January 2019. Eric's walls that
it's pretty clear President
Donald Trump is an agent of
Russia not true and swalwell
shamelessly claimed Donald Trump
Jr. and Jared Kushner had an
eagerness and a willingness to
work with the Russians during
the 2016 election. Again, it was
false in 2019. He falsely
claimed this yet again when
inquired about collusion by
reporter and these baseless
attacks were false yet covered
breathlessly by the media. There
was no coverage, however, of
swalwell being the one
implicated but not Russia, but
China. In fact, the New York
Times website, as of this
morning had not one result for
Eric swalwell his ties to
Chinese spies, not one result.
And when the swalwell story
broke, guess how many minutes of
coverage it got on ABC, NBC,
MSNBC and CBS zero
What?
Nah, man
Where's Adam Schiff? He's got to
be on deck next for some of this
awesome stuff with him because
he's, I mean, this would be his
moment of triumphs You know,
we've beaten him orange man bad
here I am. Everybody's up. Yeah.
There's a lot up with China that
are next year is gonna be great.
No matter who's president. We're
gonna have a lot of China to
deal with. So here we go with we
got three left guy Kaylee's fact
check false.
Hello, everyone. Hello noon.
Yesterday, the United States
witnessed a medical miracle. The
first doses of a COVID vaccine
were administered to frontline
workers across the country. The
President promised a safe and
effective vaccine and record
time and President Trump
delivered. Earlier this year, we
heard from several news outlets
and so called fact checks that
President Trump would be quote,
a miracle to be right. That was
an NBC News article. We were
Told according to health line,
quote, a vaccine will still take
more than a year to develop. USA
Today warned us that quote,
despite medical researchers
progress, the vaccine quote was
more than a year away. And
National Geographic even told us
that achieving a vaccine within
quote a year to 18 months would
be absolutely unprecedented. And
quotes. These reports deserve
their own fact check. False.
fact check false. What's an
interesting I'm realizing now
that whenever Kaley does one of
these press briefings, my inbox
is flooded with the backup
material to back up what she
said.
That's funny. It's where Yeah,
it's where I think a lot of this
last bit and especially here
National Geographic even told us
that achieving National
Geographic got to do with
anything? Yeah, I know. And I'll
get like look at National
Geographic did my fan quote a
year to 18 months? Oh, yeah.
We're looking at Bill Nye, the
Science Guy said he said it
would be two years for a
vaccine.
It's like, okay, we get it.
Alright, so here's our on this
stuff. Now, there's now somebody
asked a question, a really
question that kicked her off.
This is a question of assault on
democracy. Oh, yes. I love
these.
Thanks for President Trump
supporting the Texas lawsuit. At
the Supreme Court and lawsuit
the president elect Biden called
an assault on democracy. How is
it not? Is it not anti
democratic to try to nullify 20
million votes? I think pursuing
legitimate litigation through
the judicial system is in no way
assaulting democracy. In fact,
it's, it's using democrat
institutions in the manner. They
are to be used to pursue pursue
legitimate claims with sworn
affidavits and additional
evidence but I do think what is
an assault on democracy are the
four investigations into
President Trump over Russia
collusion that turned up
nothing. I mean, Moeller alone,
you had 19 lawyers, 40 FBI
agents, 2800, subpoenas. 500
search warrants, millions of
taxpayer dollars all to find no
collusion. And the investigation
into President Trump began far
before he was even elected
President of the United States
and his Intel briefings in the
transition period where he's
been weaponized against him on
an insurance policy from Peter
struck, was put in place against
this president prior to him
being elected. That is what is
an assault on democracy. Hello,
God
was waiting for
all these Kaylie clips and no
sound effects something's up.
Right now we go to the finale
clip. And I have a little
comment after that, because I
have a little a little
I boost it a little bit so we
can hear something. But this is
Kaylee is finishing up and she
walks off the stage after this.
This is somebody is this the
hunter Biden commentary. Oh, I'm
sorry.
I got
an interesting pre election and
post election coverage to on the
hunter Biden scandal which was
not covered at all by many
outlets. And the lead up to the
election. In fact on October 15,
you had a New York Times
headline that said Trump said to
be warned that he was being
confirmed given Russian
disinformation over hunter
Biden. Now December 10. Just a
few months later, New York Times
headline investigation of hunter
Biden is likely to hang over
Biden as he takes office,
Washington Post on October 16.
That headline read the truth
behind the hunter Biden non
scandal. Now you have the
Washington Post headline that
says this hunter Biden tax probe
examining Chinese business
deals. Political October 19.
Hunter Biden's story is Russian
disinformation that's a
favorite. Dozens of former Intel
officials say false yet again.
December 2 now Politico reads
Justice Department's interest in
hunter Biden covered more than
taxes really interesting turn of
events are in good for those who
covered what was the story all
along and not Russia
disinformation.
you accuse others of
disinformation when you spread
it every day.
I think I heard what he said is
that your Is that what you have
here? Yeah, here's the bush you
can play play it again.
What do you want me to play the
booster the boosted one. Okay,
here we go.
you accuse others of
disinformation when you spread
it every day. Is that the CNN
douche? No. He says I don't I
listened to that voice a couple
of times. You know the guy he
normally does the gets Acosta
that sounds like a cost that to
me. It could be a cost of it, I
think is john. JOHN Robert
Roberts from ABC. Carl
from Fox listening
critical for you to accuse
others of disinformation when
you spread it every day. Yeah,
it's not a cost. No, it's not.
It's not I hear it now. It's not
a cost.
Well, john roberts is with Fox.
Yeah, that would make sense.
It but then but then to say, how
can you stand here and talk
about misinformation when you do
it every day?
Oh, my goodness, a chicken shit
thing to say whoever it was. And
I don't know why these guys are
even in these briefings. They
should throw them out. I mean, I
think Obama threw a couple a
lot. I know bush did for sure.
No, no, no. Obama just spied on
them and threw them in jail. We
talking about the right way
Trump learn these tricks.
nice guys finish last, I guess.
You know?
Well, that was it. So that may
be the
Daily Report. And maybe the last
we ever hear of Kaylee, ladies
and gentlemen.
JOHN C. Dvorak. Bakelite. Hi,
today's Teddy Kennedy. He's an
OTG kind of guy. Yeah, baby OTG.
We haven't had a report in a
while. And I do have some
information from the front lines
of the OTG wars. Although
really, are we talking about a
wars, there is a little bit of
war going on, as Apple is now
about to release all of these
features, that cut off a lot of
the spying, not a lot, but a
significant portion of the
spying that apps do.
And Facebook is now trying to
garner some support for their
position because it's pretty
much their business. And I've
learned from a couple of
developers have been talking to
this is honey pot kind of deal
that's going on with with the
app stores, and certainly the
apple, the iOS App Store, where
if you really want to get some
good data, some good statistics
on how people are using your
app, there's pretty much one
library. And that's the one that
everybody puts in there. And
what that does is it gives all
of your information, all of
those statistics to Apple, they
take it on the way going out to
Facebook, to the what's the big
aggregator, I forget who I think
who bought them recently, and
Oracle by them or something, you
know, they combined credit card
data with online data. So yeah,
I forgot myself. So that's so
Facebook is now saying, and of
course developers can get paid
for this information, either
through ads or similar
mechanisms, if they install this
toolkit, and they get to see
what their users are doing.
Facebook is saying this is
horrible, just horrible that
Apple's doing that this will
kill this will kill free apps.
Well, now, this is exactly where
I want to have. Yeah. Turns out
free is pretty expensive. I
think we learned that from you
Facebook. So well, Apple is is
trying. But they you know I'm
there so many sensors in these
phones. Now, so many things. I
mean, it's I don't want anyone
to ever see that I just can't
trust these guys. Enter graphene
OS which one of our producers
had sent me a pixel two months
ago, if you can remember, with
graphene OS, which is a D
googled pure Android, actually,
it almost feels like this on
Linux, of course it is some
Linux in there. And I decided
upon this apple news since I was
using the cloaked iPhone, the
old iPhone, I would give this
thing another shot. And I am
blown away by the level of
permissions that you can set for
every single app, everything
that is happening. I love that I
didn't lose any functionality
really, other than I can
completely control all this crap
that used to pop up and tell me
to do things and you're just not
being tracked by Silicon Valley.
And there's some great pie hole
like blockers, VPN blaze based
blockers in there. I've been
really examining this for the
past week, and I think it is
going to replace my OTG flip
phone. Although, yep, yep. It's
going to replace it. Now. I'm
also I need to be able to send
text messages faster now.
Because I'm saving podcasting.
So I do need to be able to
communicate and
I am sick. Believe me. I'm
saving more than you realize.
But what's happening with pod?
I'm trying it's our own
preservation. Mr. devore. I
appreciate the the the the
sentiment. I just don't
understand how this means you
have to send text faster.
Well, because I communicate with
a lot of people
And I'm trying to orchestrate
and move pieces around. And so
if I'm, whether it's an email or
anything else, I do need to be
able to do this. Not just when
I'm in the house, because I'm
also out sometimes and even even
the newsletter, I'm in the
newsletter to California where
they won't let you out.
Well, who needs a phone? We can
live in California, right, john?
So I've decided I'm going to
give this a real go. But I'm
going to get a an upgraded
pixel.
And this is kind of fun. The
pixel four, which is still an
old phone, I mean, it's all it's
old compared to what they have
now. With graphene. Oh, s
generation old, the five is the
one they just released. Yeah,
but it's old. That's what I'm
saying. It's old. So now it's
old. It's not it's no longer
old. So you can you can buy them
for like 360 bucks in the box
unlocked? Well, it's doable. But
the same producer? Because, you
know, installing this graph he
knows is maybe not for the
uninitiated or weak at heart.
But however, luckily, if you go
to, can I stop you? Yeah. Can
this producer he knows who he
is. He knows who I am. Can you
do this with a blue phone? which
they're only 75 bucks 80 bucks
for a good blue phone? They're
dynamite? Can you take and put
the graphene on there without
having to throw 300 bucks away
when you don't really need that
much if you're gonna bring it to
take and then reconfigure it
anyway. Can you do it on another
android phone? Like a blue
phone? No, probably not Miami?
No, probably not. Oh, you don't
use? You're just saying that
you? No, no, no. Okay, you want
to be an asshole? Probably.
No, you can't? I'm going to
answer the question. Instead of
you insulting me, because they
specifically build it for
certain types of phones, blue
phone, not one of them. And it's
all the pixels. And it's one
galaxy. And that's so there's
your answer. No. It's only for
specific devices. Don't tell me
I don't Well, I will stop you
again. Why don't they do it for
the cheap smartphones, like a
blue phone.
Because I'm talking to you, I'm
talking to the developers.
Because the cheap blue phones
really are not applicable for
the integration that you want.
If you want everything to work.
See, it's it's not about that
you can get the software on the
device. But if you want the
screen to work, right, if you
want the buttons to work, right,
this takes an incredible amount
of effort. And they just did it
on better devices. And not on
cheap pieces of crap because
people want good good phones.
But they don't want to have all
the tracking in there. That's
why now if you want to if you
want to install some, some some
other operating system on top of
Android on your blue phone, you
can there's things out there,
but I can't vouch for this. This
is the first one I'll vouch for
good news, though. If you go to
no agenda phone.com you can send
your phone directly to our
producer and he will do all the
flashing for you and set it on
there. Will he do it? Does he
charge? Not for you and I but he
will for everybody else and
maybe charge? I don't know.
Okay. Guide because I presume
I'm not sure he says send me the
phone. But I was looking for
this guy. I couldn't find him
through through searching. If I
know agenda phone.com like Oh,
wait a minute, I sent an email.
This the same guy. So this is
the this is the look when I get
my new one. I'll send this one
to you. So you can you can play
with it. How does that sound?
Oh, that'd be great. But wait a
minute.
Okay, I'm not going to look at
gift horse in the mouth. I would
like to play with it. I would
like to know, I assumed
questions immediately. Okay, I
am curious about this. I know
you're asking. I know you are.
Can you use the navigator? Yes.
It has what? Yeah, hold on.
There's an open source program.
And it's called the opening it
now. It's called I think it's
called you are here. And now you
can obviously you can completely
lock down your, your GPS, what
apps are using it. But this
thing works pretty well. It's
based on Open Street maps. It
has a very clunky dude voice in
there. So you know
counterculture. Let's make a
completely different from
anything else. No women, just
men.
And I tried it out just a little
bit yesterday works well. So
yes, you can and the maps are
not bad. I mean, it's not going
to do traffic routing for you.
Well, you can add that but that
is uh, let me make a few
comments.
To pad this report, first of
all, the original mapping that
went on at both Apple and
Google, they had some licenses
from somebody that really had
good maps when they first came
out. They were dynamite, they
could try to chase you around,
they never made you, you turn,
you turn your tune, you you
turn, you turn, where they are.
Now, it's not even a U turn,
they wrap you around a bunch of
cities, you know streets to get
you back the other way, when
they could say you turn to be
easier. And then it slowly
deteriorated to the point where
the maps are really lousy. I
think Garmin, I think Garmin was
giving them their maps. And you
remember Apple had the big
fiasco with with maps, and they
had to pretty much start Yeah,
they kill the old deal, the fire
the guy who was responsible for
it, and they had to pretty much
recreate the entire Apple Maps,
it was horrible. Remember people
driving into the water and
stuff? Yes, the water drive it
through? Yes, I remember that.
So the new a new mapping scheme
that might have some might be
better actually, than the
current situation. I mean, I, I
try not to use a navigator at
all, I try to keep my brain. I
agree, I take it I got funny got
j to take it off. Because now
people are driving to the store,
you know, they've been to a
million times have turned to
navigate around. I try not to I
tried never to use it. Except
when I'm in a pinch.
The what is remarkable is the
speed of it. Just how fast
things snap. And you can you
know, it's like it's almost like
Linux, where you can control a
lot of these things and make it
even faster than it already is.
But in general,
you're not gonna have a lot of
douchebag apps that you don't
need that are tracking you
anyway. And you get your K nine
mail, which is good and open
source and proven to not be
spying on you. Believe me, a lot
of those great email apps you
get from the App Store for free.
Hello. Free is expensive people.
So that's graphene OS I'm
excited about it. And and with
this with the upgraded version,
the wait for it, you can plug in
an external monitor
and floating windows, so you can
perhaps use it very much like a
desktop.
just plugging into a USB see the
USB C port and an outputs video.
Wow, yeah. And I've already I've
already tried it. The pixel
doesn't do the pixel two doesn't
do it. But it was very
interesting to hook up a
Bluetooth keyboard, Alt Tab
works. It's just goes through a
different app that's open in
email, you know, control our
reply Ctrl S and it's like, holy
crap. It's kind of good.
Everything. I was surprised,
very subversive product. Yes, it
is. It is.
So I will keep you up with this.
Be honest about it. I when you
install anything on any one of
these smartphones, it says can
we get permissions for this and
that new your contact list? We
want this we want that they want
all these things? Like there's
no reason to have these these
programs want me my contact
list? No, there's, there's no
ask for any of that. Now, there
is something called APK pure,
which means you can get the
Android packages that might be
on the order would typically be
in a in a in the Google Play
Store. You can get them without
all the Google stuff in it. But
if you I mean, I always have to
laugh. Yeah, get signal. It's
encrypted. It's great. Well, I
understand how some app that is
supposed to keep you safe and
encrypted and your identity
hidden, refuses to work unless
you allow it to take your
address book.
I mean, hello. It doesn't work
unless you let it upload your
address book. So there's a
possibility for someone to
compile relationships for sure.
So that's what I would hope that
these guys who do graphene and
they start thinking about this
sort of things. This is the way
brave operates the browser,
where they give they get bogus
information. You want my address
book, yeah, here and they give
you a blank book.
Right, but but it won't
function. It won't actually fun.
No, but it will if it asks for
your address book that could
only book OS won't ask for it.
No, I'm just saying the app.
Right if you have an OSC I mean
brave does this is a browser,
the browser level it gives bogus
information? Yes. Oh, yeah. I am
a I'm functioning as a Chrome
browser when it's not. I'm also
Oh, yeah, no, I you can track me
here is where the information
would go in and it puts it off
into oblivion. Things like that.
I don't see why that can't be
done. Just generally. Yeah.
Well, that sort of thing says
you have to give me your address
book. Okay. I'll give you my
address book and you give them
an address book which What is it
Not your address book. It's just
not phony. Yeah, I mean,
unfortunately, the whole app
just won't work at all. If
I mean, if you want, it thinks
it's got an address book, it
will know you can't contact
anyone. If you don't have, if
you haven't connected your
that's just a signal, I'm just
telling you signal doesn't work
unless you give it access to
shows on personnel I try to
contact your signal has to be in
my address book that I gave to
them.
It has to be in your address
book on your device. You cannot
give it access to that unless
you give it access to it. And
then it uploads it. So yeah, you
can't just enter a number and
and have signal work. It will
not work unless you let it
access your contacts. It's
ridiculous. Well, I'm That's
what I'm saying. Why can't you
give it a bogus? Because you
need the actual number? Should
have to be in there. Yeah, you
Jhansi devorah? I would have to
have 415, whatever. Yeah. So I'm
just asking these questions.
Because I have a lot of people I
call on different systems.
They're not in my address book.
I just happen to have their
number and I call them and then
they see you I put in the
address book. Now I don't feel
like it.
But with signal that it has to
be they check to make sure that
it's actually in the address
book. I can't just call you out
of the blue or something right?
The blue correct.
There's no good. No, it's not.
So these things are not to be
used.
It has real it's I'm just very
impressed. I like it, I didn't
think that I would be able to
work fast enough on it. I didn't
think that it would have all the
features. The only thing and
this is a downside for me. The
only thing it doesn't do is low
energy, low Bluetooth energy or
Bluetooth low energy to hearing
aids. So I have to wear I have
to have a Bluetooth dongle in
between which is just hanging
around my neck. And it
communicates with the hearing
aids and you just connect to the
phone with Bluetooth. Otherwise,
yes, and I've got like a dorky
necklace.
Hey, man, I'm off the grid. Look
at my cool necklace. Says put a
shark's tooth on it. You'll be
fine.
Be very dumb. Anyway, uh, no
agenda phone calm. You can learn
more about it. And
I'm gonna. Well, I was going to
here's another thing I was going
to buy one on Amazon. And guess
what the worst possible thing
that could happen around
Christmas time happened? my
credit card got yanked got
stolen.
Yeah. So I had the best possible
thing that could happen. It's
horrible.
I only have one credit card. And
Tina has now she has an she has
a backup that she I don't know
if her if her new name is on. So
how did this this explain how
this happened? I got a text
notification from from my bank.
And it said fraud alert. Are you
trying to buy something for
$162? From fashion? nova.com?
Yes, if you say yes, then they
will, then it will have to then
the purchase can be made left to
run it again. If you say no,
then your credit card will be
cancelled. It will close
immediately. And we'll have to
send you a new one five to seven
business days. No. So what are
you going to do? You can't say
yes. By the way, fashion.
nova.com is like a store for
lingerie. Like Like, but like
not a high end one. So clearly,
just the testing to see if it
works and the show suck it out.
You still have your card in on
your person? Oh, yeah, no, this
is just the number. I don't
know, they got the number
somewhere. I'm thinking solar
winds.
Oh, who knows? We got all kinds
of you know, when Google goes
out Gmail, Google Docs drive,
YouTube. When AWS goes down, I
start to get suspicious of stuff
happening.
And well, and what's interesting
what you got, and why you got
that? Well, here's another one
for you. Why is it that visa
said they will no longer process
payments for Pornhub until they
address the concerns of the
quote unquote, legitimate
content and Pornhub who cannot
survive without VISA credit card
transaction clearing
they immediately set to work
deleted 60% of their videos
which were deemed a legitimate.
Here's my question. Why only
Pornhub
there are plenty of other porn
sites that do transactions and
take credit cards. Why only
Pornhub Why? But So you're
telling me I'm just reading
between the lines.
That your credit card was stolen
from Pornhub
that did not come out well. What
I was trying to get to is that
hunter Biden had been uploading
his personal porn videos to
Pornhub and I have a feeling
that there needed to be a purge
to make sure that none of other
things that he may have been
involved with surface to the top
on Pornhub Oh, these are the
things that I start to look at
like Oh really? We have we have
solar winds happening Amazon
goes down we have Google
multiple servers is going down
and then Pornhub has to as only
company has to purge a lot of
their content. Will you tell me
this? I'm not going on?
Well, time is up. But I do like
your analysis. And I lost my
credit card. I'm
gonna show my school by Jonah
evil who could do Oh Yeah,
that'd be fine.
Oh, and we do have a few people
to thank for show true 13 before
we do, starting with desert Cal
of lavender blossoms who came up
with the under $72.27 he does
say Happy Thursday.
Love it. What's the name of his
lab lavender blossoms. Lavender
blossoms.org.org. That's where
you want to get your your
solves. bombs. Your lavender
lavender blossoms. That's what
you want to get there. Paul Bre
x in mobile, mobile, mobile,
mobile, mobile mobile.
Mobile Alabama 100 Andrei ortego
in Eunice, Louisiana. I believe
he needs a z d douchey. Well
hold on a second. There was
something else here that I
needed to check. That's $100 by
the way from Andre Hold on a
second is Andre needed.
Yes, they do.
You've been de Dieu shot Got it.
Got it.
Okay, wants some good karma at
the end call Colin McCormick and
er Haney, Dublin, Ireland. Yeah,
this was not a not a fantastic
note. This is meant to send
condolences to
Baron Bryan Matthews to his
mother. Since Baron Bryan
Matthews passed away of cancer
on the 17th of November. And I
would say that his condolences
to all producers of get mo
nation. I did not know about
this, but I saw the note come
through. And we're very sorry to
hear that. So we will do a an F
cancer because that's the only
way to address it.
You've got karma.
Yeah, that was too bad. Yeah.
We lost a Baron Thomas Wilkinson
meanwell. Ottawa, Ontario also
donates $100 to his Happy
Christmas to everybody. Tara
Reese, and we're bhana Illinois.
Urbana, ad dollars and 33 cents.
He's been or she's been getting
a lot of 30 threes. boosted on
her. Janet fury Kramer. Dame.
dangerous dangerous. in Harlem,
Holland. 69.
Axl
pale Phl Paul. Paul. Yeah. And
he's in Deutschland in Xin vedo
$60. Nicole Sinclair in La
Jolla, California. 5678. I can
pronounce that.
Jennifer Sayer 5510 Parts
Unknown Daniel Mariano and
pflugerville. Texas. 5510.
Armand. We don't have a big list
today by the way. Armand de
Hedrick and normal Ella,
Illinois 5333 which is might
want to do check that out. Sir
Jimmy in Summerfield North
Carolina 5150.
He reads the hollow book guy he
says we made Atlas Shrugged is a
hollow book and please douchebag
Paul, the book guy
I have I have a Atlas Shrugged
dollar book from sir Jimmy. d.
Now, that's really one of my
favorites. Get. Is that just a
wet one? You bet anyone you buy
is going to be a hollow?
I snotted on that one. Very
funny, john. Just because you've
never read it.
Oh, no, I've read you've grilled
me. Daniel Verrilli, if 5033 Jim
Farley and piqua Ohio 5033.
Sir Baron economic sir Barents
or Economic Hitman in Houston,
Texas 5001 and the following
people are $50 donors name and
location. Jessica young Yuba
City, California David chaloner,
in Madisonville, Louisiana
Gabriel Ngozi Guzman, Guzman.
$50 in Parts Unknown, it's got a
note there. Yes important. He
needs a karma which we'll do in
a moment for his first born or
not born yet was first born to
be he and his keeper are
pregnant. So yes, we'll give you
a karma for the baby Chris, sir
Chris Lewinsky and Sherwood
Park, Alberta where all the
money used to be. Tony Smith in
Fort Worth, Texas.
Brian Henderson in Indianapolis,
Indiana Murray love brewery air
in Kennett square, Pennsylvania,
john camp in antlers Oklahoma.
Christopher Mueller Mueller, in
Cedar Park, Texas. Uh, in Texas,
that will be pronounced Miller,
believe it or not. Oh, Miller.
Does it surprise how people
pronounce it? Yeah. I am. abiel
losh Kumari, insane. In India,
in India. Now that's impossible.
That's impossible. We had one I
think it was either Kumar or
somebody else. And I know it's
not possible because you can't
send money from India. Oh, to
paypal. So I don't know how he
did this.
Well, he may be an imposter note
and explain it. I think he's I
agree with you. We have people
from India, although it could be
the people from India bitching
that they can't send money or
just using it as a bogus excuse.
Now you're talking with the
Indians? Is that what you're
saying? That cheapskates Well,
we've known they admit to it
them in the French?
No, it's the Scots.
That's their the Berman gildan
ways who as I think was truck in
Canada, Feldon house.
Do it. So I would say there's no
help. I would say geldenhuys is
probably how we pronounce it,
but it's Dutch name. It is a
Dutch name and Michael berlet in
Odessa, Florida 50 And last but
not least, are Jason deluzy Oh,
in chats for Pennsylvania 50 we
want to thank all these folks
for making sure 1304 possible
and we wish everybody who gave
us lesser amounts the same thing
Thanks a lot.
Thanks a lot. Yeah, thanks a lot
well those a series those under
the $60 under $50 is mainly from
reasons of anonymity but and I
know you you hit on this in the
newsletter often get one of
those subscriptions the
sustaining donations are
extremely important and we're
probably going to rely on the
more than ever as we move into
our build back better phase
build the podcast back better.
We're gonna have to do something
and thank you to all of these
producers a well deserved a
karma I we haven't had a go
karma today. So that's for
everybody who needs it.
You've got
karma and remember, we'll do
another show on Sunday for more
info and to help go to bull
run.org. Slash and
today Mandy be celebrated on
December 5, Kevin redacted to
celebrate her birthday and
Lorraine ours is happy birthday
to our human resources James and
Emma answer code monkey Jason
says Happy Birthday to his
brother sacks Eisler who turned
38 on the 14th Happy Birthday to
everybody here the best podcast
in the universe.
Don't want
one title change as you heard it
was made good and well deserved
for all of his work. And of
course for his he will not just
his time and his talent but it's
treasured Dred Scott. Early
large becomes Duke of the
Southern California megaregion
and we thank him for his
unwavering support of the best
podcast in the universe. Then
today one ceremony we have a
dame so it's been a while since
we had one of those. Let me
I need your blade. JOHN for the
day off. Sorry. Here you go Game
Boy, I got it. Yes, good, much
better.
Man, you've got a great partner.
He launched you all the way to
the roundtable. Very, very
pleased to welcome you here. And
of course, to thank you and your
man for the support of the no
agenda show in the amount of
$1,000 or more, and therefore
I'm very happy to pronounce the
Kate vs. Dane sparkler of New
Braunfels for you. We've got
hookers and blow but I think
you'll like the rent boys in the
Chardonnay we have Oh
rabbit meat and goat milk we got
talking boy still reserve and
Black Milk we got organic
macaroni and plasticizers vodka
and vanilla ginger ale and
jerboas bonnets and bourbon
breast milk and pablum gangsters
and sockeye or of course the
mutton in the need everybody
loves the mutton and the meat go
to no agenda nation.com slash
rings, and we'll get that out to
you as soon as possible. So you
can flaunt that everywhere you
go. And thank you for supporting
the no agenda show the best
podcast in the universe. No one
the party continues all around
get mo nation. We have a couple
of meetup reports meetups, which
are cloaked as protests whenever
necessary, go to no agenda
meetup calm or if you need to
prove it to somebody no agenda,
protest calm. This is where you
can meet human beings human
resources from around the
country around Gizmo nation, you
can meet them anywhere in the
world almost. And we have a
whole calendar system a meeting
system where you can discuss
hang out, there's no triggering.
Everyone always has a good time,
usually supported by alcohol.
And here is a report from our
recent Houston meetup. This is
Brian at the Houston raging
surge super spreader luncheon we
have very fine people on both
sides of the table and I'll let
them introduce themselves. Joker
millennial Scotty Rober here so
younger millennial David handle
stay humble specs, apps over
rainbow for a new thought, elder
millennial, thank you for your
courage as Brian aka speedskater
wait for the Q Fs blockchain to
kick in
Orlando in the morning.
there we're super excited to be
at the super spreader events.
In the morning, I like to call
out douchebag Flynn.
in the morning.
I realized, you know he's had a
lot of female producers in the
not in this particular one take
on the human vessel carrier and
a lot a lot of people are
pregnant.
Have you noticed this?
Yeah. Well, do you know why I
noticed it? Yeah. Well, it's
very obvious. They're stuck at
home, but also is there? Yeah,
we've been in this for 10
months. Hello. It's the COVID
generation. They're popping out
now. The COVID generation. We go
to the no agenda, protest
Veritate meetup. We're here in
Alexander Valley at the no
agenda protests. I'm Amy in the
morning in the morning. This is
Justin Elin senior, john, john
C. Dvorak. This is Dana Adams.
Favorite sir DB Knight of Norco
or state of Jefferson. Thank you
very today for this very private
exclusive protest in the
morning, Alex. Oh, that's the
error. So at the end, I like
that. That was your meetup.
Yeah, so when I was supposed to
edit and submit I think I think
our producer Dana got tired of
I can produce this dammit What
am I am a producer. More meetups
or protests as you wish coming
up on Friday tomorrow the whole
This is the cocoa coffins
Florida OTG campout the whole
weekend bonfire camping tree
house building. Ham Radio
anybody that sounds fun.
Saturday convexity Carol Carol
and troll join get my nation in
the QC for Shaka lodge show and
festivities in cinque rock. Also
on Saturday Toronto a the no
agenda peaceful protest super
spreader event five o'clock on
Saturday, the tiny amygdala of
Anchorage, Alaska that Matt
anouska brewing Midtown
anchorage the Nashville Noel
agenda at six o'clock and that's
party followed downtown. It
sounds like fun, like upon the
Western New York meetup stay
negative seven o'clock on
Saturday at bucket bar Odessa if
open at all.
Cypress California flight Oh 10
of the no agenda 3:33pm Now this
was a change venue is no longer
in Garden Grove they moved it to
campus Billiards in Cypress
California. Now that means 21
and older only and Leo Bravo
will be there to welcome you if
you show up and make it looking
ahead towards Christmas Eve
December 24. The Christmas the
Xmas tangerine chugging protest
in Lithuania.
Now you're talking if you're an
expat stuck in Lithuania and do
not want to spend your Christmas
Eve alone. I propose a protest
together with the rest of the no
agenda global slave community by
eating tangerines and shell Tina
together, which is probably some
Lithuanian thing. That's
disgusting. You know what this
is shell Tina shell tea
Have you ever heard of this?
Never heard of it?
Hmm. So
here we go. Shell Tina. No. Yes
sh ALTNA
know what that is? A l oh you
look at
that right rounding out the rest
of the month on December 27 a
very fine people meet up in
Charlottesville Virginia at the
Trump winery should be
the like head cheese
Really?
Okay, it's an aspect dish that
looks like yes she's to me.
Okay, that's not attractive. Not
no question. I don't even want
to hear about head cheese.
Really? It's not doesn't sound
attractive.
Yes, and then we have the New
Year's small amygdala bash 719
Colorado on New Year's Eve,
December 31. These are the no
agenda protests. They are
meetups in disguise make sure
you go and check one out you
will love it. You'll have a good
time. And if feather isn't one
near you go set one up no agenda
meetup.com
All right. Let's see where we
are. Yeah, time to go. So I have
one last clip. Do you have
something to play us out? two
clips. I've got two clips. All
right. goody, goody goody.
Uh
I don't know which one to go
once about air pollution killing
a kid. And the other one is
about terrorism is back. Well,
let's think we can start with
the kid both up uplifting Yes.
very uplifting. Shall we go with
the dead dead dead kid first the
dead kid story as an uplifting
thing to leave with. And now I
want to preface this this is a
story that is a creation because
they make it sound as though
they kind of ignore the great
Russia the Russian the great
London Fog I think was in
1955 33 sir like that? Yes.
Which literally literally killed
a number of people hundreds. I
think I had to look it up. But a
lot of people most of the air
pollution laws around the world
are written
or created because of that
London Fog the death fog but no
No, no, we did current air
pollution which as far as I can
tell is borderline non existent
compared to what it was
apparently just killed a kid and
now they made a story out of it.
I think this is just a prelude
for some global climate change
thing, but let's play the clip.
nine year old Ella kissy Deborah
wanted to be a pilot and fly
around the world. Instead she
left her mark on it today a
London coroner ruled Ella's
death was caused in part by air
pollution. A historic first air
pollution is a pandemic her
mother Rosamond spent seven
years fighting for the
designation. Hopefully it means
governments everywhere will do
something for the for the
citizens who are breathing
filthy Desi air. The oldest of
three, Ella walked to school
along one of London's most
congested streets diagnosed with
severe asthma at age six. After
seizures and 27 trips to the
hospital. She died at nine. I
hope never again will any child
suffer? way my daughter did. The
World Health Organization
estimates air pollution causes 7
million premature deaths a year.
What do you think Ella would
think of all of this? I think
she would just smile at this.
She would like the idea that
she's helping other young people
for a child who left too soon.
Well, this reminds me
of that.
Wait, let's do the jazzy one.
Second insert
second insert. So the kid was
sick. The kid had all kinds of
issues. Oh man, we're just so
dry area but no, this is this is
the mind control. This is what
they do to you. This is what
they do.
More coming, not less more
coming. He Well the good news,
which I thought was good news
because Biden's gonna come in
they're getting it back to the
old ways. Let's go back to four
years ago, where we didn't know
if no one's noticed this. During
the last four years under Trump.
terrorism has not been a story
there's been no real six week
cycle that's gotten any try to
get back to the old days build
back better they get back to the
old days because terrorism was a
lot of fun to deal with and
here's the terrorism is back
baby clip on NBC. The FBI says
the plot
came from Al Shabaab, the al
Qaeda offshoot in Africa that
killed 72 people at a shopping
mall in Kenya seven years ago.
Investigators say the group was
incensed by the Trump
administration's decision to
move the US Embassy in Israel to
Jerusalem and plot it to attack
Americans in response, including
a plan to hijack a commercial
airplane and crash it into what
us skyscraper. Court documents
say a Kenyan man cholo. OBDII,
Abdullah enrolled in a flight
school in the Philippines three
years ago, and did research on
how to hijack a plane how to get
a US visa and look for
information about the tallest
buildings here. tipped off by US
intelligence agencies.
Philippine police arrested him
in July 2019. with intense
coverage by local media. He was
brought to the US to face
terrorism charges and appeared
today in the New York City
courtroom. The FBI says tonight
it's a reminder that overseas
terror groups remain committed
to attacking Americans and are
still obsessed with hijacking
airplanes. Oh, this is
fantastic. We are on track we
are going back in time which
means we can roll out the old
jingles
Shabaab yeah baby al Shabaab is
Broadway This is all the things
al Shabaab I am so sure that Al
Shabaab and African terrorist
group really gave a crap about
moving the embassy sure that's
what it was all about. That was
all they're preoccupied with it
over there. And Kenya I got
nothing better to do a move the
embassy Oh my god, this is the
most important thing in our
lives is bom bom of an American
building. Yeah, that makes
nothing but sense. What is what
is the general view of Milton
Friedman? What is your view of
Milton Friedman maybe a better
question. Milton Friedman picked
up that there's an economic
cycle. And after each collapse
of the economy, which happens, a
new theories need to be
developed, that are that explain
everything from the from the
last collapse, which is never
explained by the current
economist. But as explained by
some new guy that comes with
this new gap, as the guy's been
saying this for a while. And
then he becomes in high
prominence. He developed the
supply side economics theories,
and became very important and
he's the one probably
responsible what was called
Voodoo economics by George Bush.
But in fact, he was the leading
economist until he died pretty
much and but he's not good, but
his explanations for things
probably won't explain what
happens next. But somebody had
to explain stagnation. Right.
He's the one who did stagnation
or stagflation. Obviously,
stagflation. Yeah, you're right.
Good catch. But yeah, he he
explained that away. And he had
all these these all these theses
about how things really operate.
And he's I really like him. Oh,
good. Well, I have a clip from
1999 that I ran across that I
thought you might enjoy, I think
that the internet is going to be
one of the major forces for
reducing the role of government.
The one thing that's missing but
that will soon be developed is a
reliable ecash method whereby on
the internet, you can transfer
funds from A to B, without a
knowing B or B knowing
all hell is gonna break loose
and you're gonna need a bit.
Friedman predicts the Bitcoin.
He does, and I wish I had heard
that before and I would have
bought some bitcoins at 25
cents. You can still get in
john, let's go on to 400,000
in our lifetime, he probably
will go to 250 I don't think
he's
gonna collapse. No, it's not
gonna collapse. But all the
institutions are getting and
everybody wants a piece of the
action.
Nick the rock coming up next on
no agenda stream.com we
appreciate the work that we got
from our end of show remixers
Jesse coy Nelson and Professor
JJ with some original lyrics and
nice Christmassy vibe. And we
will return with more Christmas
cheer for you. Like kids dying
of pollution and
vaccine side effects all the
good stuff on Sunday. So until
then, coming to you from
opportunity zone 33 here in the
capital, the drone Star State
Austin, Texas FEMA Region number
six on the governmental maps in
the morning, everybody. I'm Adam
Curry. I'm from Northern Silicon
Valley where I can look at and
see the freeway filled with cars
driving around when they're
supposed to be at home. I don't
get it, but then it is what it
is. I'm just here. We return on
Sunday right here on no agenda,
remember us@devora.org slash na
until then adios mopho goes in
such
a way to keep it from us being
able to be in a position where
you can manipulate the machines
Like, the one way to do that is
I think we should pass a federal
law mandating that the same
machines with paper trails be
mandatory for every federal
elections in a nutshell, it
should be mandated that we have
a paper ballot with a
standardized machine
Dominion voting systems.
Dominion CEO john flows
testified that there was no vote
for being no rank choice voting
and that the voting machines
were not connected to the
internet. There were no switched
or deleted votes involving
Dominion machines with Nokia
says my nose grows now he is
either lying or not. There are
no algorithm that enabled
fractional voting, he is not
lying, then his statement is
either true or false. There are
no evidence and voting machines
were not corrupted to alter this
election, therefore, either his
nose does not grow now or his
nose has grown out. Attorney
Sidney Powell responded saying
that the votes are counted from
the images Dominion creates the
balance, not the ballots
themselves. She said these
images are a part of her fraud.
The other two voting system
companies used by Michigan heart
voting systems and SNS declined
to attend the hearing. We have
put together the most extensive
and inclusive voter fraud
organization in the history of
American politics.
Good Maxine, and if you do a
public key to inspire confidence
to the people that can mean he
said he is absolutely open to
taking it you will receive the
vaccine as soon as his medical
team determines its best but his
priority is frontline workers
those long term care facilities
and he wants to make sure that
vulnerable kits are access
first.
Walk your dogs
every piece
vaccine trials with indemnity
they will inject you
every 192
like the sheep say many times
many ways
mopho vortec.org slash n A.
Why is this so small?