Adam Curry Jhansi devora
award winning media
assassination Episode 1300 This
is no agenda, pinning down dates
and broadcasting live from
opportunity's own 33 here in the
frontier of Austin, Texas
capital of the drone Star State,
everybody. I'm Adam Curry from
Northern Silicon Valley where
we're drinking instant coffee.
I'm Jesse Devaraj.
Wait a minute. Wait, you are
your ground zero of the
tyrannical lockdown in
California. And that's all you
got? Is your drinking coffee.
So I look at the I looked up, I
always look these orders up and
actually read them. Nobody does
that the media especially well,
no, because they're exempt and
they don't care. No, actually,
they're not exempt from this.
Oh, what media is not exempt
from this? No, apparently
everyone is Whoa, including
protesters. Protesters in curl,
okay. Just want to make sure we
still have it and it is listed.
Okay, let us know what's in the
order. Well, how are you? How is
your movement being restricted?
Uh, if you start to look,
actually look at the order and
read the document, you can go
out and do whatever you want.
Wait a minute, just this, you're
just discouraged. Really? Yeah.
And the thing is, of course, all
the restaurants and everything
is close. So if you go out and
do whatever you want, what are
you gonna do? This is like my
idea of going to Paris, I would
love to get on a plane and go to
Paris. What am I going to do be
locked down for 14 days? Even if
I wasn't locked down? Like what
hotel? Am I gonna stay? What am
I going to do when I'm there? I
can't go to a cafe
doesn't move is closed. Right.
But the the shutdown of
businesses and restaurants
that's being enforced?
Yeah. Okay. It's being enforced,
but they're not enforcing people
being outside. And do you have
to wear a mask in your own bed?
Is that part of the I'm serious
a wish? It's possible. No,
that's coming. This is this
order, which to me, just on its
face feels like I could I'm
probably wrong. But it feels
like Gavin Newson got
caught being a dick. Everyone
pointed at him and said, You're
a dick. And he went, Oh, watch
this.
Is there any other reason?
Because what they're saying is
completely ludicrous. The stay
at home order is because you've
crossed over the magical 15%
free ICU bed space in hospitals.
Which as we know, is really only
a portion of all of the
artificial construct. Yes. So
this isn't even a flattening of
the curve or anything like that.
This is just saying, Well, we've
passed 15%. If we're below 15%
capacity, then we have to lock
down until January 4. This is
this is not even based on
science. This is based on
hospital man's hospital
management. But you know, it's
like, oh, so do we just need
more beds? Can we then one day
friend. So what they've done is
they've implemented the harshest
order, which is again, like what
I just said is you can go float
around if you want to, but
you're discouraged from it, but
you can. And so there's no media
exemption, because pretty much
anyone can do what they want.
But again, there's nothing to do
so what would you do that you
might as well stay at home and
eat or watch TV?
Did is only a few counties that
are really put it into full
force. Mm hmm. All the night and
not all the counties in the Bay
Area except San Mateo County,
right there was
Barstow open away San Mateo
County is they are walking the
the order.
That's Silicon Valley. There's
your irony. Wait, that's the
Silicon Valley guys.
Silicon Valley.
That's Palo Alto, Redwood City.
douchebag.
So their fancy restaurants.
They're all open. They're in San
Mateo for the Silicon Valley set
is that ideas are out there. I'm
pretty sure for outdoor dining.
You can eat San Mateo County.
Yes, they're real. This is on
that. Do you Is there a general
feeling in California that this
is some kind of gap? Oh, that's
the feeling. Oh, so it's they're
not angry. Gavin Newsome.
They're thankful for him locking
them up. That's what you're
saying. You got it in Los
Angeles. These orders including
that those of Mayor Garcetti are
presenting huge problems. This
video went viral. I've tightened
it up somewhat. This is
A restaurant owner in Los
Angeles who had created an
outdoor restaurant with a little
tent over it and some picnic
tables right next to her, her
restaurant, which has been shut
down now with these orders. And
well, if you haven't seen it,
she sees that 50 feet across the
road, someone else did get a
permit to open up an eating
facility. So this is my place
the pineapple Hill grill in
saloon. If you go to my page,
you can see all the work I did
for outdoor dining for tables
being seven feet apart. And I
come in today because I'm
organizing a protest and I came
in to get stuff for that.
And I walk into my parking lot.
And obviously Mayor Garcetti has
approved, this being set up for
a movie company. I'm losing
everything. Everything I own is
being taken away from me. And
they set up a movie company
right next to my outdoor patio,
which is right over here. And
people wonder why I'm protesting
and wine I have had enough.
They have not given us money and
they have shut us down. We
cannot survive. My staff cannot
survive. Look at this. Tell me
that this is dangerous. But
right next to me as a slap in my
face. That's safe. This is safe.
50 feet away. This is dangerous.
Mayor Garcetti and Gavin Newsom
is responsible for every single
person that doesn't have an
employment that says not have a
job, and all the businesses that
are going under and we need your
help. We need somebody to do
something about this. You go
this Yes, she screwed.
And you're gonna do right. No,
what are they gonna do? Nothing.
Who mean who is they? In this
case? Because Yeah, the
government Jim's doing he's
gonna go and fall on deaf ears.
Yeah, well, we'll see if that
happened in Austin. I'd be out
there. I'd be out there
protecting this like New York,
this is going to happen more and
more. People just want standards
or anything left in New York,
New York. Well, at Brooklyn. I
think there's one restaurant
that is you know, The Last
Stand. And 4000 people a night
are now showing up to stop the
sheriff from shutting them down.
tears will come of this. And
people, you know, as you said,
though, that's very interesting.
This order makes it feel and
sound from a distance like you
are locked down, shut up, slave
mask up in your house in your
bed, be quiet, don't make waves
follow the rules. But that yet
you're completely allowed to do
whatever you want.
As an I see no evidence to the
contrary. If you start looking
at the order, it's pretty much
more of a strong suggestion for
the public and a very strong
more than just suggestion for
the businesses. Hmm. So I can go
outside right now and go to the
store, walk around and wander
down to walk through the park.
Well, there is good news. As you
know, the freedom pass is on its
way and we'll get into that a
little more. But just so we all
know, there is a COVID freedom
past.com website, which you can
use to get out of this mental
jail that you've been placed in
this mental prison COVID freedom
past.com
that of course redirects to no
agenda. show.com
This is one of the better
forwards I've seen I really like
COVID freedom pass calm because
we're setting you free in your
head. That's all it's perfect.
So these arguments are spilling
over everywhere. And as you and
I know, whenever we have an
argument on the show people
always resort to this very
childish, literally childish
remark of I hate it when mommy
and daddy are fighting. Which to
me means a new voice for you.
Thank you. Thank you I can do it
again. I hate it when mommy and
daddy are fighting
should like your voice I think
I've had that one for a while I
think it's just slightly I just
got it it's got a little
it's got a tomato in it that I
think makes it
okay cuz I'm really sad. And and
I always say the reason why you
feel that way and uncomfortable
is because this is how adults
actually resolve issues and move
on. And you don't see that on
television. You see phoneys with
phony arguments, feigning phony
outrage. It's not real. That's
why it doesn't feel
uncomfortable. So it hits the
hits the listener, the producers
of the show, gets them in such a
sensitive spot that they
immediately equate that to mommy
and daddy fighting.
There was a really good which is
the problem that the I think
you've identify
Just ignore these comments.
Because that you know, I think
they're people think you're
being cute, but it's possible
that you've nailed a
sociological issue that is
serious. Yes. Yes. There's no
examples of what good discourse
is phony discourse, which is
what you see on television. Is
that not exactly the same play?
Yeah, but isn't that exactly
what you see on Twitter when
people argue it's just bullcrap.
But just yelling back and forth
there's no resolution it's not
adult behavior it's stupid. Now
the this this descended to an
incredible for me a high for
many a low on CNBC, you probably
saw this. I think it's
worthwhile to play the the
entire clip in context, because
I only play the entire Yeah,
because it was it was just
clipped here and there. And if
you haven't seen it, this is
Rick Santelli, who has always
been kind of a troublemaker on
CNBC. And he's always been a
screamer. Yeah. And he's
appreciated for it. I think in
the 2008
financial meltdown, he was
yelling Yellen every single day
and he was just completely give
a briefing on this. Yeah,
rescued during 2008, which I
thought was on, I thought was
unwarranted, but he did it,
which is that the people who got
suckered into these stupid
subprime mortgages and they lost
their houses, and he said,
they're idiots. And they deserve
what they got. Yeah, very
unsympathetic to the fact that
most of them were victims of
sales pitches.
Which is something I'm somewhat
sympathetic towards anyone who's
sold down the river by no means
are kind of buy into it because
they're, I don't know, not
necessarily a bad person. But he
really was very accusatory. I
thought it was unfair
personally, but in this
situation, he's with I believe,
David Sanger. Now, Andrew Ross
Sorkin Sorkin I'm sorry, Sanger
Sorkin in New York Times? Yeah.
And Sorkin is from the New York
Times and he's an old New York
Times hack and he would be part
of the system. Oh, yeah.
Somehow the golden boy on CNBC
this what is he done that has
made him so revered people Oh,
Andrew Ross Sorkin Oh, Andrew
Ross archive.
We could waltz over to the
Wikipedia and check him out. But
he is a New York Times Golden
Boy there. And he was in fact I
remember talking to him about
him and with some other New York
Times reporters. And you know,
he was one of these guys that
was going to be bureau chief,
which I think he came maybe from
Hong Kong and we went all over
the world if you know what that
means.
A Hong Kong and then he was Oh,
I remember it's because he he co
wrote too big to fail, including
the movie adaptation. And he's
the CO creator of millions.
That's why because he's of
course it's a Hollywood Connect.
And so he was going to be he was
on the fast track to become like
the editor of the New York Times
or The executive editor or
something like that. And then he
gave us very successful with
these books. And he he got kind
of full of himself.
So he like Bay wants to do that.
It's the new york times they'll
just kick you to the curb. And
so he's over now at CNBC is, is
there with CNBC? You know,
unless he can get out of CNBC. I
don't see any I think he's at a
dead end. The his problem is
obvious why he's Why didn't
become editor of the New York
Times. He doesn't have vocal
fry.
He's most listened to the
previous editor. You know,
obviously, I read I read the New
York Times, like all day long,
mainly on my iPad. That's what
if that's a Gil Abrams, if you
want to be edited the New York
Times. That's the attitude you
got to have. But no. Instead, he
threw on his Superman cape and
flew around Rick Santelli,
telling Rick Santelli, that he's
hurting people is dangerous and
he has to intervene in his rant,
because this is bad for society.
And we need a public service
announcement for health and
safety of our viewers levy I
believe in careful and when I
point out Governor's cheating,
it's not for the high hypocrisy
which exists. It's the fact that
I think many of these governors
that's the point that I think a
lot of people didn't hear it
really it started about the
hypocrisy of the governors and
the mayors of Mayor Adler and
Austin jetting off to the times
to family timeshare and Cabo
when he told everyone to shut up
and stay home then of course the
Newsome and
what is London breed in San Jose
Mayor all of these douchebags,
no, they should just we should
just go towards the French
Laundry. I'm not this is not an
instruction. This is not an
instruction well that do happen.
But if you want to get the
attention of your government
burn down their favorite eatery,
that would be
Start back to the thing at hand
cheating. It's not for the high
hypocrisy which exists. It's the
fact that I think many of these
governors are intelligent
people, and they love their
families, which they've taken
out into restaurants. Therefore
there is actually in should be
an ongoing debate as to you know
why a parking lot for a big box
store like by my house is jam
packed. Now one parking spot
open. Why are those people any
safer than a restaurant with
plexiglass? I just don't get it.
And I think there's I don't
think this has really been
discussed. Maybe you and I have
talked about it a couple of
times saying why is this big,
big box store safe? And the rest
isn't? We've talked about this.
No one really does. I bitch
about it. Yeah, you do. You do?
You do. Sorry. But before I get
let this you got to do a lot of
setups here to get make sure
this works. A Sorkin is going to
defend the big box stores as
being totally different, totally
different science. And I think
what you might you might make
the argument even though he
doesn't do it, you might make
the argument that well, when you
go into a Costco, which is open,
there is almost like being
outside, the roof is a mile
high. There's a lot of airflow
in there. And it's kind of like
being so it's different than a
small boutique. And my
complaint, of course, is that
people can go into target or
Costco and buy clothes, but they
can't go into a small boutique
and buy clothes right? Now, that
argument about the big bucks or
I want people to keep in the
back of their mind that concept
that target doesn't have these
ceilings. Correct target is just
as far as I'm concerned, the
department store. That's why
they agreed. Oh, the target.
Remember, this is a financial
show where they're meant to hype
certain stocks.
To make sure people buy them
open. Why are those people any
safer than a restaurant with
plexiglass? I just don't get it.
And I think there's a million of
these questions that could be
asked. And I think it's really
sad that when we look at the
service sector and all the
discussions we've had about job
losses, that that particular
dynamic isn't studied more is it
worked more, we don't put more
people in the room and try to
figure out ways so that the
service sector employees and
employers could all come back in
a safer way. You can't tell me
that shutting down, which is the
easiest answer is necessarily
the only answer. Rick, I just
just as as a as a public health
and public service announcement.
This is my favorite. As a public
health and public service
announcement. I'm Andrew Ross
Sorkin and I have written
billions. So let me tell you
what the science is for the
audience. The difference between
a retailer
the difference between
the different different, like
how the co host saying who else
man, you know who it is, is the
douche? Who weld Could it be
between a box retailer? Hold on?
The difference between a big box
retailer and a restaurant? Or
frankly even a church are so
different? It's unbelievable.
Oh, really a church?
Where I disagree. You're we're
gonna have your thoughts and
science science.
That's the problem. Ah, damn it.
Whenever you and I disagree over
something, john, we the the the
way you used to end arguments
online was your Hitler. He don't
do that anymore. You just say
it's science. If you say that
then End of discussion because
you can't dispute science.
aren't any safer than 150 people
in a restaurant that hold 600? I
don't believe it. Sorry. Don't
believe
there's a lot of restaurants
that have fought back and they
don't have any problems. And
they're okay. You don't have to
believe it. But let me just say
this, you're doing a disservice
to the viewer because the
viewers need to understand
the viewer. You are You are
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. It I would
like to keep our viewers as
healthy as humanly possible. The
idea of packing people into
restaurants. I think our viewers
are smarter.
smarter different than all the
viewers like some people do. Can
I get in here please and get
like mommy and daddy baby.
How's it all working for you? I
mean, look at the numbers right
and then this guy Rick, look at
this guy's a douche. This. This
is the fat head guy.
How's that working out for you,
Rick, why don't you just say he
should have just added these
people are dead because of Trump
brick. You know that it's
working out fine.
The numbers lie. Rick, Rick, the
numbers show
that when people are getting
sick and dying,
I just stopped
talking about this. There'll be
no agreement. So let's move on
from here.
He's done. They're gonna fire
him. Sorkin or Rick?
I don't think so.
I mean, if they don't heat then
he read book it. If Okay. All
right, that's that's a worthy,
that's a worthy one. If if they
don't fire him, that will be the
equivalent of having tenure on
television, that's for sure.
Because that's, I hear what
you're saying. Let me just see
date is December 6 2020. We have
11:31am, JC de AC brick,
Santoli? fires and Kelly
Harrison. Yes, it's entirely
over COVID
restrictions. Okay. It's in the
book. I'm not going to dispute
it. I'm not going to dispute it
is the science, on the other
hand is being disputed in a
number of interesting ways. And
this one has cropped up recently
in Ireland. As you can recall,
Ireland has pretty much changed
their population to their four
poster beds, close down the
pubs. And that's like cutting
off oxygen supply. Ireland one
of the most restrictive
regulations that is ruleset that
had been put in place. And
there's this woman, Gemma
Doherty. And she has spent a lot
of time going around to she kind
of looks like the Code Pink Lady
surname again. You know, I mean,
yeah, I know. He needs to wash
her hair. Yeah, well, yeah, it's
the flashy the flask flask did
kind of blondish hair, thin
hair.
And she's spent time going
around Ireland, exposing on
video that the hospitals are
empty.
Which, of course we've seen this
at anywhere. Yeah, you can. But
she's been doing except there's
always one or two places where
you can't. And that's where they
send the cameras. In fact, that
reminds me and I have to do
this. And I feel remiss for not
doing it because I've been
thinking about it for days on an
era is these the nbc cbs and ABC
show? People are getting tested
and they show a line of cars.
Yeah. You can't show this on the
show. Because but it's been a
line of cars a mile long. Yeah.
into like a football field lined
up for hours to get tested.
Yeah, I think it's the same line
they show for the food bank
might be
Burke, I go to Berkeley this
week. And take a picture of the
testing carline testing thing
there, right. There's nobody
there. But this isn't even
testing this is this is what's
happening in the wards. It's
just it's just not there.
They've cut back on personnel.
No, I'm just I'm just saying
they you can find places where
there's a long line and that's
always in the camera. Yes. So
Gemma Doherty
is out and about. And she posted
this, this one video most recent
one in front of Ireland's public
health building and one of these
big, elite Illuminati like
structures. And she had some
interesting evidence, which is
very reminiscent of a time a
previous time with the same
actors on the stage. I'm here
because I have some very
important information to impart
in relation to a development
that has happened in the United
Kingdom. You know, that for the
last eight months, I have been
entering hospitals in this stage
and exposing the fact that they
are empty my latest one and the
matter has gone viral worldwide.
And of course, we know it is the
case that these hospitals have
never been emptier. Probably in
the history since since before
beautiful Fini Gail took over.
We know that at this time of
year, our hospitals are normally
packed to the gills as they are
in late February, March, April,
at the end of the winter season.
But they were empty them and
they are empty now. So people
are right to question whether
this virus actually exists. But
we now in Europe for the first
time have the scientific proof
that it does not exist. And this
is thanks to a Department of
Health letter that had been
received following a request by
a citizen in the UK, which he
actually had to appeal. But he
requested the department of
health and social care in the
United Kingdom to give him
scientific proof of the
existence of a virus called SARS
code two and they confirmed and
I will read it now to you that
the department of health and
social care
does not hold any information on
the isolation Tsar's code to.
In other words, it does not
exist.
This is this is a real mind
bender. And this is actually
what David was talking about, at
the beginning of this months and
months and months ago that the
PCR test is just rigged. It's
not meant to be a test but the
PCR process is rigged to show
fragments
of
a coronavirus and is then
saying, Well, you've got to SARS
cov. Two, but no one has
actually isolated the virus. And
this is exactly what happened in
the late 80s and 90s. with HIV,
they never came up with the
isolated virus they could never
show it. Now, about three years
ago, there's been some paper
released that complicated, you
know, the in a very complicated
manner shows Oh, yeah, it was
the there or something. But in
general, you can read book after
book after book. And then you
just won't find it. And it's the
same people.
And they had the PCR test for
HIV back in the day.
And my personal opinion is that
people died from the from the
rejected chemotherapy, azt, that
they were giving these patients
they went in very similar to
the, to the, to the ventilator
story. Like you test positive,
you go into the hospital, and
you never come out it dead. You
know, and I think there's
something to this. I'm not a
virologist, not an imminent
knowledge disorder. And those
ologists can't even say it, I
can't even pronounce it, let
alone Let them have a diploma in
it. But I'm I'm suspicious of
that, then well, there's a lot
of things to be suspicious about
the existence of the virus, I
believe it does exist. I don't
think that come from an animal I
think was made in the lab and
they can't find an animal with
it until they've been able to
isolate it, then why is that
something? I don't know that
that's true? Well, that's I
don't know that that's true. I
don't know that. That's true.
I'm just saying,
I just hear this. Now. But I do
know this is true. When the
first reports came out in April
or March, April. And they were
showing all these lines at the
hospitals. They were numerous
youtubers would go out to those
same hospitals the next day. And
we saw that he made those videos
reported on this. And there was
no line of ambulances at those
hospitals. There was no
ambulances, there's nothing
there. And then they went into
the hospitals. Some of them went
actually went in with their
cameras, and they found nobody
in the place to play. It's just
pretty much empty. Right? There
was this example has happened a
number of times. We have a
friend who works at the in
Cornwall at the National Health
Service. And she reports back
that there's no the hospitals
are empty. And you keep hearing
this, but there are hospitals
which are reported to be full,
and they can be document to be
full. But those are all they
seem to be the outliers, along
with those long car lines. So
there's something fishy about
this whole those hospitals, the
ones that are better lit, I
guess.
lighting, lighting for the
lighting for the shot. Yeah, you
gotta light it up. Because this
sort of thing has been to see
this before to get my I actually
had my hair cut. Wow, the other
day.
And the guy who cut my hair, I
saw I'm just trying to get going
here, but I couldn't manage it
would know. You hadn't been that
you'd been a year without a
haircut. No, I was going for a
year. I couldn't get it. How
long did you go? March? Not bad.
Was it down to your shoulders?
It was getting there but it was
a scramble. I look like an old
witch.
But you know, I was I mean
yeah. So I talked to this guy
and he was going to get a an
operation on his back. Yeah,
just before the whole thing
broke out and he didn't let
anybody in. And then he got his
operation during the middle of
the crisis. And he says he went
in the hospital because for
electric surgery which is being
done to places dead empty. Yes,
it was great. You go in there
and get nothing but you know
everybody's You know, you're
there you get in the good
service.
So I mean, this these stories,
these stories are not bullcrap
stories. Well in more health
related news and numbers from
sir arcane code. He heard us
talking about the ambulance
services and why they were in
financial trouble.
Which we both found indeed kind
of weird. Like seems like no
sense. Well, he has a rundown
for us. He has some friends who
work for an ambulance service
turns out, less than half of
their business comes from
emergencies. The majority of
Ambulance Services is for
mundane calls taking someone
from a nursing home to their
doctor and back that's a big one
patient from hospital to a rehab
facility or transferring between
hospitals. So when hospitals
shut down everything except
COVID related procedures, and
this comes down back to our
point it's shut down all the
more mundane services and so no
more need for ambulance in
general. At least around the
Birmingham Alabama area of the
services many are hurting
financially. That makes sense.
And and we're going to and when
this ends when I guess after the
hundred day mass mandate from
Joe
you're going to see it then
you're going to see hospitals
overrun when everybody comes
back to get treated for all the
crap that yeah, if they're still
alive, I sweat that's when it's
gonna be bad. It's all this
elective surgery that's been
backing up. Yep.
Yep, you bet.
Now's the time people go in now
in the EU a fantastic this could
have been a curry divorce tech,
consulting group exit strategy,
I am beating myself over my head
that we missed this opportunity.
I'm very, very disappointed in
myself in you as a consulting
partner, founding consulting
partner, and probably very
disappointed in our associates,
known as producers of the show
that no one came up this this
must be really bad. You're
scolding everybody. 97 year old
Collette dupa a nursing home
resident in jumaan France has
been taking precautions against
COVID-19. She's been limited to
speaking with her family via
video call or through a window.
But now Dubai is able to feel
their touch through plastic
thanks to an inflatable tunnel
known as the hug bubble, baby.
It even has one of our names the
hug bubble. This thing is
fantastic. We could have
manufactured them overnight. Do
pies daughters recently visited
her putting one arm through an
airtight sealed plastic stroller
and stroke her hair. Stephanie
Lazo is often at the nursing
home.
It has brought comfort residents
would see their relatives
through a window or through a
camera and they were really
missing having real contact and
they are getting a lot of love.
Before dupas daughter's left
they took turns kissing their
mother on the cheek the plastic
after get
disinfects the plastic sheet to
prepare for another loving
encounter in the hug bubble. Do
you see the problem?
The problem?
Hug bubble is disgusting. I
mean, and it's all it is is it's
a bouncy house, you know clear
plats without the colorful
pieces a bouncy house castle
with two arms and then though
your granny comes up you can
stroke her hair with the plastic
it's it's beyond sad
ah
very very very upset. We didn't
come up with that. Dammit. Now
before I go into after that big
lead and I'm less here's like
you're not that upset you didn't
like i think i think it's I
think it's a huge moneymaker I
would have been I would have
been embarrassed to be part of a
company like that called what
the hug bubble company. This has
a future baby says a future I
unfortunately, the domain name
is gone. So we couldn't get
that. Before I get into
vaccines. I think you may have a
poor couple of reports to run
through. I did want to make
mention that very observant
producers have noticed in
several of the Bill Gates videos
that he does from his office
when he's doing the interviews
and he's talking about how the
severe pain will hurt you from
the from the vaccine. people
noticed he had a stack of books
next to him on his Bureau. And
do you know what book is almost
right on top one below the top
one. It's called a book called
How to lie with statistics.
But an embarrassment man, it's
available on Amazon and it will
give you the blurb there is
terror in numbers writes Daryl
huff in how to lie with
statistics. And nowhere does
this terror translate to blind
acceptance of authority more
than in the slippery world of
averages, correlations, graphs
and trends have sought to break
through the days that follows
the collision of statistics with
the human mind. With this slim
volume first published a 1954
book remains relevant as a wake
up call for people unaccustomed
to examining the endless flow of
numbers pouring from Wall
Street, Madison Avenue and
everywhere else someone has an
axe to grind, a point to prove
or a product to sell the secret
language of statistics so
appealing in effect minded
culture.
is employed to sensationalize
inflate, confuse and
oversimplify.
I've ordered it. Yeah,
definitely. This is our book. So
that's what Gates is doing. He's
lying with statistics as is
everybody else, everybody? I
don't think so.
You don't think so? I think many
of them are very sincere. Okay.
But they're confused about what
they're presenting because
someone else gave somebody in
the background, his language
statistics and, and Horton,
swaddling the idiots.
Yeah, yes. Well, do you want to
get him back? Cesar? I see you
have a couple of reports. I have
some let me look at what he got
here. I have a bunch of COVID
there's some good stuff here.
Actually. Let's do it. Start
with the grim news from NBC. You
get it like like a feeling for
what's going on. Okay. Good
evening, we've been running out
of ways to stay grim new
milestone, we're talking about
COVID. Now, so far beyond that.
Yeah. This week. It's surpassed
heart disease as our country's
top killer. Today, more drastic
measures to try to slow the
spread. Southern California is
now set to go into full lockdown
issuing a stay at home order to
begin tomorrow at midnight, and
more states and regions may not
be far behind as the unbearable
burden on our nation's health
care workers grows. For the me
turn this crap off people.
Watch this guy.
You know what happened? You know
what happened? You're right.
They all saw Cuomo get his Emmy.
They're like, Oh, hold my beer
like I can good.
Acting? Yes, of course.
unbearable. It's horrible. Yeah,
it's on bearable right here. If
you want to hear of your top
actress. Amy, if I can use that,
if I can use that term. Here we
go. COVID report, Amy. Whoo hoo
ha Come on in the United States
has set yet another world
record.
virus cases, hospitalizations
and deaths with over 216,000
infections confirmed Thursday
and more than 2800 deaths. Hold
on. When she says confirmed,
what exactly does that mean?
Well, let's listen to one of our
Canadian producers who said
Do you know that in Canada This
is some semi scandalous is that
when you you're in an emergency
room, you check into the
hospital for like a broken leg
and bleeding? Yes. They give you
a covid test. If you give your
test positive, they put it on
the record. If you die from your
broken leg and bleeding you die
to COVID. And it's a confirmed
case because you had a test
right but she's talking about
confirmed cases who are not in
hospital just confirmed cases. I
don't know what she says deaths
confirmed guests. Oh Dez. Yes.
And because you had such
excellent use of reverb I'm
going to start it over again.
United States has set yet
another world record for daily
coronavirus cases,
hospitalizations and deaths with
over 216,000 infections
confirmed Thursday and more than
2800 deaths. Nearly 101,000
people are hospitalized with
COVID-19 across the US in
California Governor Gavin Newsom
has imposed sweeping remain at
home borders covering the vast
majority of California's
population just in the last 14
days close to 1000 Californians
have lost their lives due to
COVID-19. The bottom line is if
we don't act now, our hospital
system will be overwhelmed if we
don't act now. We'll continue to
see a death rate climb. Governor
Newsome sorter came a day after
Los Angeles Mayor Eric Garcetti
warned Los Angeles is nearing a
devastating tipping point,
ordering residents to rain at
home and skip social gatherings
in order to prevent needless
suffering and death. in Rhode
Island officials have opened two
field hospitals with a combined
900 beds to relieve hospitals as
COVID cases hit new record
highs. Rhode Island governor
Gina Raimondo says the problem
now is finding enough medical
workers to handle the surge on
Thursday she appealed to retired
and unemployed health care
workers to join the effort. Wow
first of all dynamite we are
we're both going to hell for
this you realize that that
people think we are we are the
worst human beings in the in the
universe just to put echo and
mock mock death. But notice how
she said they're gonna run out
of employees and they're gonna
go get and she says first
retired and then unemployed.
Yeah. Why don't you reverse it?
Bring all the ones you laid off.
That's what's going on here.
Yep.
Yeah, this is a fault. This is
like unbelievable. They pulled
this off. So fake
Fake its fake display part two,
but I'm happy that California is
dumb enough to shut down to
others will follow me and we'll
see the first day I'm on our
grid to say I'm gonna ask the
public for 100 days to mass mask
up just 100 days to mask not
forever 100 days, and I think
we'll see a significant
reduction if we occur that event
that occurs with vaccinations
and masking to drive down the
numbers considerably.
Researchers at the University of
Washington project the US
Coronavirus, death toll could
reach nearly 540,000. By April
1, the same researchers recently
projected that if 95% of
Americans wore masks
consistently, over 68,000 lives
will be saved by March 1.
I want to mention
we did saved or created, how
many lives we're going to save.
Is that what she just said? Oh,
yeah, hold on. Let me just hear
that last bit. Again, that's
important information. Over
60,000 lives will be saved by
March 1.
Why? Wow. So they've got it down
to that much science. So masks
work so well, that if we wear
them for 100 days, 68,000 people
will be saved or created by
March 1.
In fact, here's the thing that
is ignored. The San Francisco
Bay Area.
Especially Alameda County, which
incorporates Berkeley, and
Oakland,
all very Democrat. Were masked
up. Yeah, of course. I mean, Max
maxed out, maxed up. There are
people driving masks in their
cars. There's people jogging
with masses by cyclists going
down, right driving around on
the bike lane, and they got a
mask on. So what's the deal?
Here? We're wearing masks like
no other part of the country.
This is this is mask Central.
Yet, we're in the purple zone
where we have to shut down and
shelter in place and stay at
home. How does that work? I
don't see the evidence for this.
This sounds like both bullcrap.
Because we are masked up. If we
were like, if Berkeley and
Oakland were all like, well, you
guys can do whatever you want
now, because you've been a good
little boys and girls, and you
messed up and you stay social
distance. And you have all these
spots on the street where you
stand here and you stand there.
We've done that, nothing didn't
help. So this is bullcrap. Just
a little side there for you.
Yeah, there's a video from some
UK data scientist. And they're
running the numbers of cases and
deaths in the UK. And no matter
which way they ran the numbers,
they see a market increase in
cases and subsequently some
deaths at one specific date, and
no matter which way they look at
the numbers, I'll put it in the
show notes. So you can see it's
not clickable because it's
boring and you can't see it.
The exact day that masks were
mandated in the UK is when the
cases and deaths started to
increase. Well we've had those
those graphs in the newsletter
about five shows ago from the UK
you everywhere all over the
world this this is evident when
you see where the master
mandated all the numbers started
going up because they started
testing now.
So that's this bogus but lets us
know I got two more clips and
we're out of here. Well, I got
some vaccines stuff, but yeah,
don't I want to hear the vaccine
stuff? I have nothing. Okay.
First of all, let's play this
one. This is the I have the
world report which is wrapped
around the world with Amy given
us all the world. Oh, when did
you get into dy Italy but I
wouldn't play this one because
this one is
a suspicion. This is the COVID
farm workers step away. I want
you to pay careful attention to
this and give me the rationale.
I don't know why they even
mentioned it. But it makes it's
something fishy about this
report. Back in the United
States. California's farm
workers have contracted COVID-19
and nearly three times the rate
of other state residents. That's
according to a new study by the
University of California
Berkeley researchers. The first
report to explore how
farmworkers are
disproportionately affected by
the pandemic. The report also
found farm workers who only
spoken indigenous language had
higher positivity rates and
farmworkers who spoke Spanish or
English.
Did you hear this?
So what is that depends on what
language you speak. Um, it was
the report also found farm
workers who only spoken
indigenous language had higher
positivity rates and farmworkers
who spoke Spanish or English. So
what I take away from that at
face value is we're not
communicating in the right
language.
Because indigenous people, I
don't know what that means, but
around the world, it could be
all kinds of things.
American Indians Aborigines
that guess because we don't
communicate to them properly. Or
maybe she's insinuating. They're
stupid.
I think she's insinuating
they're stupid. They should
learn English, or Spanish, or
Spanish even. Hmm. That is
weird. Well, I mean, she's not I
don't think she thinks she's
doing that. But that's in the
report. So you might as well I
mean, what else gonna mean?
Because the problem with Amy and
that entire news operation, if
you want to call it that news
reading, as they never try to
explain anything, they just,
they they're just almost like
flat reporters, they report and
they leave you hanging, like why
they leave you, you know,
reporting is who went one who,
what, when, where and why. They
always leave the why out there's
never a why answered? And there
was a good example right there.
Why, yeah.
I want to know why.
David, Democracy Now never
addresses why. And when they do,
it's usually just with some
propaganda. Didn't democracy
now. Don't they have a grant
from the Rockefeller Foundation?
Oh, they got grants from
everybody. We should be so like,
well, I'm just stating that for
people who you are new coming to
the show, because you heard
about it during the Rona. Or
maybe you saw me on the Joe
Rogan or whatever it is. Go take
a look at event 201 people have
asked Hey, have you seen this?
It's crazy. They set this up?
Yeah, yeah. Hello 10 months ago.
And if you go to if you go to
Bing it.io bi n gi t.io. That is
the official no agenda show
search engine which are many's
but this one I use. And you put
an event to a one you will get
John's clips, which were
excellent, excellently
categorized, and many more
articles, etc about this. And so
that would make sense that
democracy now is a part of the
live version of event event.
201. So say whatever is that
that's the problem with money.
Probably it has control. It has
control is the problem with
corporate money with an agenda.
There you go. Money itself is
fine. All right. The last one
here's our world report around
the world is swinging from
country to country and is always
locking down. I don't know
what's going to happen. Italy
recorded 993 new COVID-19 deaths
Thursday a daily record. The
Italian government's declared a
national curfew and said
Thursday it will bar people from
traveling between regions over
the Christmas and New Year
holidays. Iran's official
Coronavirus cases count top 1
million on Thursday in October,
a member of Iran's Medical
Association said the true death
toll in Iran could be four times
higher than the official number,
which now stands at nearly
50,000. In the Gaza Strip
officials have ordered schools
and mosques to close as part of
a partial lockdown as more than
800, New covid 19 cases were
confirmed Thursday. Among those
infected are senior members of
Hamas, including its leader.
Yeah, yes. Anwar, what Hamas has
been infected. She's got to stop
saying people are infected. It's
just not true.
Because Because the PCR shows
something doesn't mean you're
infected and seething with
virus. I'm telling you, I think
they put an end to this real
quick if they made them check
everyone with the same exact
test with the same revenue, you
know, the same cycles for for
AIDS as tuberculosis and maybe a
half a dozen people wouldn't
want to test so fast as what
you're saying.
Well, yeah, cuz you're gonna
come up positive.
Even
the Baltimore Ravens, you know,
they had their their guys test
positive. And as part of the
shaming, as we know, it's like,
well, you clearly didn't do it,
right. You didn't mask up, you
didn't follow the rules. You're
probably a republican Trump
lover. That's why you're sick.
So they had to counter that
narrative was true. They had to
counter that narrative. And they
came up with a good one, which
is a well there were at least
four unique strains of COVID-19
found inside our facility. Three
of the four were stopped and not
spread. Unfortunately, the
fourth was a highly contagious
strain and spread throughout
before we can get to it. I mean,
this is this is the thing this
is fantasy, fantasy and for
those of you in question, if you
if you test positive if you feel
sick if you contract the this
virus
It's not your fault. It's not
your fault. It's It's like
saying, you know that got well
that's like the guy. We played
that clip from that YouTuber who
was crying. Yeah, yes.
I did everything right. I did
everything right, I still got
it.
I think a lot of people that
have that kind of attitude and
you have that kind of reaction
make themselves sick. I think
that I think yes, good. Porsche
suffers. They're psychosomatic.
Oh, definitely. And that's what
the undercover nurse told us in
March as well. It's a people
coming in have severe anxiety.
That's why they have heart
palpitations, shortness of
breath. They're freaking out in
New York at the time.
Here's deal going on that the
media has done nothing, you
know, you can take this like
stock market reports. You can
take a look at anything up or
down and spin it in a positive
manner or a negative manner.
They have done nothing and you
can spend this entire situation
in a very positive manner if you
wanted to. But they don't want
to No, of course not.
This is an excellent example of
shaming certainly at the end of
the clip, and it also shows you
that you do not want to mess
around in Maryland, as a guy is
going to jail for a year. Sean
Marshall Myers will spend a year
in jail in Charles County,
Maryland. He was arrested around
seven months ago after officers
found more than 50 people
hanging out around a bonfire at
his home when COVID restrictions
were at their strictest and this
gentleman was ridiculous.
Charles County State's Attorney
Tony Covington tells me police
arrested Myers at his home for
refusing to comply with Governor
Larry Hogan emergency order
against large gatherings of more
than 10 people at the beginning
of the pandemic in March. The
sheriff's office says it was the
second time Myers hosted a large
gathering at his house. And he
was accused of being
argumentative with officers in
both time today, Myers was
sentenced to one year in jail, a
$5,000 fine, and three years on
supervised probation. These
decisions were made for the
public good for people safety.
We've got 200,000 people dead
because of the attitudes that
Mr. Myers demonstrated that
particular day. That's the
problem, whoever that guy is su
brother.
And that's that Hogan character.
We brought him into the show
some time ago. And she was he
was interviewed by Margaret
Hoover. And the two of them were
just hating on Trump. And he's a
republican. He's like one of
these worse than a rhino types.
Guys a creep. Yeah. But this is
this is the narrative is 200.
Now it's 300,000 people are dead
because of people like you
because you now, you thought
that adding a little bit of
reverb to Amy talking about how
the United States is number one
would be great. But it's number
one, it's nothing nothing
compared to the UK health
minister, who really really
knows they're number one, as the
UK is the first to administer
the vaccine. And lastly, did the
fact that Britain is in the
process of unhas Brexit it did
that mean we got the vaccination
a world first ahead of the US
and the EU? Yes or no? Do you
believe Secretary of State?
Well, I just reckon we've got
the very best people in this
country and we've obviously got
the best medical regulators much
better than the French had much
better than the Belgians have
much better than the Americans
now that doesn't surprise me at
all because we're much better
country than every single one.
So it did help that we Yeah, I
someone lying when they do that.
Let's listen again. That doesn't
surprise me so because we're
much better country than every
single one. So it did help that
we Brexit it finally, II to get
back there. No, no, no, it's
just a stutter, right? It's not
it, there's no underlying
meaning.
The guy's going to full on CPU
overload
is like his hard drive and
writing fast enough that was
finished in our medical
regulator making it happen means
that people in this country are
going to be the first ones in
the Western world to get that
fat fire or in the world to get
that Pfizer vaccine. Real
competitive advantage, but you
know who it's down to. It's down
to those brilliant brilliant
clinicians in the regulator
who's made it happen so fast. So
this is a problem because this
is not just the vaccines. This
is not any vaccine. It's the
Pfizer vaccine. This plug will
not stand as we know the eggs
are in the modern a basket
ladies and gentlemen. This is
the
One that Fauci has a patent is a
part of the patent. That's how
it works. By the way, it's all
it's all aboveboard, when the
National Institutes of Health
and certainly Fauci US
Department of death, when they
work on stuff with the
pharmaceuticals, they are listed
and added to the patents and get
payments to get royalty Pat
payments for that. So Fauci
he poo pooed it. And he said,
this is maybe maybe not the
smartest thing to do. The BBC
has a very good report of what
he said that offended and the
rather lengthy as sucking he did
to get back in good graces with
Pfizer, because has nothing to
do with you, UK has nothing to
do with your health, or the
vaccine. It only has to do with
the money. And the promotion of
Pfizer, which we identified on
the show hat was the one to win,
according to our insiders. Now
Madonna is not rolled out yet.
That has not been the choice of
the UK. And it's a problem for
Dr. Fauci, UK announced
yesterday, it will become the
first country in the world to
approve that vaccine, meaning
mass injections can begin next
week in Britain, in defending
the approach of America's
regulator, which is more
cautious to Anthony Fauci
initially took a swipe at
Britain accusing its regulators
of taking a shortcut. In an
interview on CBS News, if we had
jumped over the hurdle here
quickly and inappropriately to
gain an extra week or a week and
a half, I think that the
credibility of our regulatory
process would have been damaged,
and we would have more people.
You know, I love the Brits.
They're great. They're good
scientists. But they just took
the data from the Pfizer
company, and instead of
scrutinizing it really, really
carefully, they said, Okay,
let's move it. That's it. And
they went with it. Now, how
about that, huh? He saw he's
giving it to them.
And I think the most egregious
accusation is Oh, they just took
on face value. It was in the
they took the test. Pfizer said,
Okay, we're good to go. Pfizer
says it's good, let's go, we're
good. They, they believe
whatever they were told those
idiots. So transparent what is
going on here? Well, after
blistering criticism from across
the Atlantic in the UK, he told
me earlier that he apologizes
for those comments, and they
have the utmost respect for his
UK scientific colleagues. Now
listen to this suck up job.
First of all, there really has
been a misunderstanding. And for
that,
for that, I do have great faith
in both the scientific community
and the regulatory community at
the UK. And anyone who knows me
and my relationship with that
over literally decades. Know,
that's the case. Pfizer, I
really do love you. I'm sorry, I
didn't mean that. I was just
promoting my own house. I know
I've got other deals with you.
I'm sorry, the point that was
really trying to make and and I
did not make it appropriately
well, and that's the reason why
I welcome the opportunity to get
on your show, wow, is this, I've
never heard him suck like this,
and say that I do have
confidence it came out wrong.
And that was not the way I meant
it to be. In the United States,
there is such a considerable
amount of tension of pushing
back on the credibility of the
safety and the efficacy that
notice what he's doing. The
problem is not that Fauci is a
commercial a whole. The problem
is, Americans are conspiracy
thinkers. That's the problem,
you see, because we don't trust
the vaccine. So yeah, I mean,
it's really it's really the
Americans, please just don't, I
didn't mean that it's their
fault. If we in the United
States had done it as quickly as
the UK did. And that's no
judgment on the way the UK did
it. And even though my
misstatements did come across
looking that way, that if we
had, for example, approved it
yesterday or tomorrow, they
likely would have been pushed
back on an already scrutinizing
society that has really, I
think, in some respects in the
United States, too much
skepticism about the process. So
when we had conversations, and I
had just had a recent
conversation with a UK station,
the first thing they said was,
aha, we beat you to it, we won
the race. And I wanted to get
the point. This is not a race,
where there's one winner, and
one good one and one bad one.
It's a bunch of companies and a
bunch of countries, trying as
best as possible to get vaccine
to their citizens as quickly as
they could possibly suck up some
more to do that in the United
States. But our process is one
that takes more time than was
taken with the UK. And that's
just as the reality I did not
mean to apply any sloppiness
even though it came out that
way. So if it did, I just
Want to set the record straight?
I have a great deal of
confidence in what the UK does
both scientifically. And from a
regulatory standpoint. If I
somehow came across differently,
I apologize.
Already. Yes. Now, you know what
this is all about. Right. Well,
there's, there is something but
I don't know if it's well, you
know, it was. It was a simple
phone call from the, from the
Pfizer rep that has the CBS
account, of course, first a
media buyer.
Yes, we can. Hello, CBS. We
heard what you're you put on the
air that kind of demeaned our
company when you're Mr. Fauci,
the expert there said that they
just read our tech sheet and
we're liars. And I want to point
out to you something. Have you
looked at the balance sheet of
how much advertising money we
spend with your network compared
to Madonna for our boner pill,
which is modern spend with your
network? Zero? They've never
done anything. So do you? Are
you going to sit there and let
and let this kind of stuff pass?
We're not going to put up with
it. Unless you want us to pull
all the ads. Every ad we do with
every subsidiary and every
company we have anything to do
is we're going to pull from CBS
and move it over to NBC. Is that
what you're asking us to do?
there on the phone that that
answer real salary? Of course,
there is an actual problem,
according to the literature from
Oxford, that the Pfizer vaccine
may may result in sterilization.
Which I get that what there's
that And don't forget, there's
the other one, it may only last
90 days. Well, yes, that's
another good one. But the
sterilization has put the
conspiracy theories into high
gear, obviously, I have not
heard this. Oh, yeah, it's good.
And it's backed up, I think
poorly. But I did want to play
this short clip, by Sir john
bell of Oxford. He's also a
member of GAVI, which is the the
vaccine Alliance headed by
gates, the genius for GAVI and
sage, which is the advisory
organization to the UK
Government. And he said this in
a in an interview, which I think
was his old, I think it's at
least a month old, but it's
going around as see. So I'm
hoping that's going to happen
pretty smartly this autumn. But
then don't forget there, these
vaccines are unlikely to
completely sterilize the
population, they're
unlikely to sterilize the
complete population. Now. I
believe he meant as in that
would clean you have any
infection these infected you
know, but as as a as a high end,
sir, no, no less from PR
agencies exists? Yeah. What did
he use a different term
inoculated? Wouldn't that be the
term, but he says sterilized.
And it only plays into the
classic Bill Gates, Ted Talk,
this equation has four factors,
little bit of multiplication. So
you've got a thing on the left
field two that you want to get
to zero. And that's going to be
based on the number of people,
the services, each person
choosing, on average, the energy
on average for each service, and
the co2 being put out, a per
unit of energy. So let's look at
each one of these and see how we
can get this down to zero.
Probably one of these numbers is
going to have to get pretty near
to zero. That's fact from high
school algebra, but let's let's
take a look. First, we've got
population, the world today has
6.8 billion people, that's
headed up to about 9 billion.
Now if we do a really great job
on new vaccines, healthcare,
reproductive health services, we
could lower that by perhaps 10
or 15%. He's always talking
about having less people after
saving their lives. I've never
understood this now. There's a
possibility that we can connect
the dots. Vaccines will reduce
the population it I don't see
how that works, but he always
puts it in the list of
reproductive care
and vaccines that will lower
that will lower the population
and his reckoning with that as
well. In the poor countries,
people have 18 children because
they know half of them are going
to die. I don't know. But you
can see rationale for the whole
you can see why in combination
was information from Pfizer
itself that they're not quite
sure if this will sterilize it.
This will sterilize people
general public. Now, we have
nothing to worry about. Because
it doesn't matter what vaccine
is showing up. Everyone's gonna
take it. Especially you can
Denae Viens here's your health
minister again, but will you as
the Chief Medical Officer of
health in any way make something
Sort of mandatory vaccination
recommendation. So similar to
our all our immunization
programs in the province of
Ontario,
and we have some special acts
related to that, like
demonization of school pupils
act, etc. We can't force someone
to take a vaccine. That's clear.
And because we want to make sure
that people say, is the only
book I would want it. And we
want to make sure we have all
the information they need, as
well as all the safety
information, etc. What we can do
is to say sometimes for access,
or ease and get into certain
settings, if you don't have
vaccination, then you're not
allowed into that setting
without other protection and
promotional materials. So what
made it mandatory is proof of
immunization vaccination was a
proper product, in order to have
latitude and freedom to move
around in certain, like access
into long term care facilities
or the hospital different things
without wearing other types of
form of personal protective
equipment, etc. Same as a school
attendance may be much like our
other vaccines, we haven't gone
there yet, but we would make it
mandatory for access in and
sometimes be excluded if there's
a risk or hazard going on. So
it's more of
facility of movement and around
that not that someone is going
to be forced to take it against
their will.
So this is a reason to go to
COVID freedom past.com and tell
all your friends, it truly will
free your mind of everything
that you're being told. And it
appears to me that we need to
keep a very close eye on any
stimulus or rescue package that
may or may not come out before
the end of the year. There's a
lot of talk about it. And let's
pay very close attention to what
the sectors that goes to. I
guarantee you if a lot of money
is going into airlines, they
probably will come up with some
kind of requirement for proof of
test or proof of vaccination.
Because it's government
government money, they will they
will Why have the government be
the bad guy, when you can just
pay the commercial and sector to
do it for you. Just like spying
it's a good point. Just like
spying it's the same thing. Why
would we spy we'll just buy it
from you guys commercially,
stupid citizens give it to
Facebook and Google and Twitter
willingly, willingly.
Not going to be so easy in the
United States, particularly
amongst the black and brown
communities, who are always
talked about as such in the
mainstream.
Because the black and brown
communities of America are not
stupid, and they've learned from
their own history. Tuskegee
anyone, just trusting
communities of color is not just
a small town problem. It's
nationwide, a study conducted in
September, exploring the issue
in black and Latino communities
found just 14% of black people,
and only 34% of Latinos trust a
vaccine will be safe. It's like,
it's almost to me like a fear,
like I have a phobia of needles.
I'm almost at the point where I
have a phobia doctors, Carmen
Bailey was diagnosed with
COVID-19. In April, Bailey says
she avoided medical help,
because she feels she has been
poorly treated by doctors in the
past. Now the grandmother of
three suffers from adverse
effects with her heart, lungs,
and kidneys. Sometimes I could
barely walk alongside of her
know what to do, what she will
not do is take a backseat. We
don't know any kind of side
effects from them.
So I just really felt like at
this point where it's people
that's gonna take that vaccine
as guinea pigs
are gonna Yes.
I just felt like you. We don't
know enough. In the I was
looking at the Pfizer stuff
going through the sterilization
part. They were I think only of
the there was like only 15
African Americans in the entire
trial of 30,000. I don't
understand that may not maybe it
maybe I don't have the right
data. But that seemed a little
under under represented to me.
But we have nothing. So numbers
that seem higher than that there
was a percentage and it was
something like
it was like that was 15% I may
have misread it. But even then
that's a little low.
Particularly because we know
that they suffer
disproportionately.
But don't worry, we have help.
It's all gonna be okay, even
though you're gonna take the
vaccine. And you know why?
Because of this guy.
Anthony falchi tells me this
vaccine is safe.
And can
vaccinate
immunize you from getting COVID?
Absolutely. I'm going to take
it. I may end up on TV or having
a film just so that people know
that. You know,
do I trust this science
Few people that are actually
experienced in science. In other
words, never don't have a degree
in science never worked in
science to have anything to do
with science are the ones who
say that. Oh, yeah, I'm sure.
I'm sure. Now, I want to read
this. I want to read this little
report we got from anonymous.
Hi, Adam.
Here's the UAE cases continue to
hear they continue to climb. But
the government's opinion is that
this is normal. And they're
opening everything. restaurants,
bars, gyms, weddings, house
parties and on schools have been
open since September. Oh, and if
you've ever been here, it's hot.
I've been there. It's very hot.
damn hot, he says. So none of
this outdoor dining rubbish.
We're all inside an air
conditioned space is no problem
to downsizes you can't talk
about it. So nobody talks about
it because of the authoritarian
state. And they don't it's not
publicized.
So everything's normal and lots
of parts of the world and
because of I don't know what
what the deal is with these
what? They're just annoying to
me. Well, no and British
Government. Yeah. I mean, look
at us. Texas is open. We have no
restrictions. Adler trying to
make some noise, but he can't
he's been totally discredited.
And we're having a pretty damn
good life. We have one of Tina's
friends is over from Chicago. We
went out last night we went to
mangoes fish market which was
open and as full as they can be
for the day. Of course they do
have some restrictions, but
completely packed for what
they've got. Meanwhile, the only
thing opened in California is I
think the the weed dispensaries
are open if I'm not mistaken. So
there's that as the weed
dispensary is that for you?
Definitely open.
So French Laundry is open. Yeah.
Now, should there be a problem
with compliance and people
willing to take the vaccine? All
we have to do is talk to Larry
Larry Lightfoot, I've learned
from our Chicago friend. That's
what they call her in Chicago
now. Lori Lightfoot Mayor Lori
Lightfoot is known as Larry.
And this I thought it would be a
color bait Beetlejuice because
she said that but she's no no
everyone calls it Larry. Larry
Lightfoot, which is bad enough,
don't have to go to the
Beetlejuice. But she was asked
about this. And well, she knows
exactly how to take care of this
problem. Would you support
vaccine mandates?
Well, look, I always think it's
better to educate people into
compliance if we can. But we
can't live in a world where only
certain people are taking a
vaccine, and some are opting
out. That won't help anybody and
that will perpetuate the spread
of this incredibly deadly
violent virus. So we're looking
at a range of options, but our
first choice, obviously, is
educating people into
compliance. I love this term
educate. Wait, yes. How is it
incredibly deadly when the stats
clearly show that it's under 1%?
You need to be educated and
compliance young man. You
haven't been paying attention we
need to educate you into
compliance
is not the same thing as telling
people to obey.
You must obey not you will obey
you will obey you will obey you
will obey. Educate into
compliance.
That's it That's reeducation
camp. If you don't that's just
rude if you don't pay careful
attention. Yes, the reeducation
camp. Let me see what else I
have. The New York Times says
the true pandemic toll in the US
is is in reality 345,000 we
haven't counted right. So shut
up, slay Oh, yeah, we're low.
Yeah, we're low on the count.
When I was looking over that the
Canadian producers sent over
this information about the COVID
cases. I'm going to read this
because I left a important piece
of information out.
There's a piece of information
missing with the picture of the
hospitalizations caused by the
covid virus done by people that
go to the hospital. They get
tested, when they are
hospitalized for whatever
reason, and both situations have
been added to the total that
apparently I know here in
Canada, everyone who is admitted
to the hospital and test
positive with a PCR is added to
the official hospitalization
total of covid patients, even if
they're not in their symptoms,
and the reason they're in the
hospital wasn't the virus. Yeah,
this is a medical scam. Medical
scam, medical industry scam.
Well,
one more thing, one more thing
on the vaccines. There's
a fact sheet going around Well,
actually, what was this this was
about side effects from the
vaccine and yeah, there's the
typical things that you know,
pain in the arm pain in the ass,
etc, etc. But a lot of the
literature is now changing some
percept or trying to change
Perception when we were looking
at the vaccine industry, and
just to recall how we got
interested in it, I came across
the financial conference in
2010. I want to say 2000, maybe
even earlier 2009 It was during
swine flu. Okay, it had to be
earlier early than that. And the
it was a financial conference at
all the pharmaceutical
companies, everyone agreed. This
was a hundreds of billions of
dollar industry because we could
make vaccines for everything in
the future. This is really what
Madonna is, by the way, this was
that era, that same error when
you discovered this PowerPoint,
that within a year, they were
coming up, remember the vaccines
for smoking,
overweight, all of that none of
them were vaccines in the in the
least, but they were trying to
get in under the umbrella of the
liability issues, right. Which
is obviously still there. Now
with
the vaccines,
the one thing we bumped up
against is the use of adjuvant.
And as humans, we kind of
concluded if I recall, in an
unscientific manner, we're a
little dodgy because they work
as a form of hamburger helper,
to really kickstart the exact
same phrase you use back 10
years. That's why I remember it.
So now we have a subhead in
these articles, vaccine.
adjuvants bring the danger we
need.
And they're explaining how,
particularly with these mRNA
vaccines that your immune system
still need some kind of
Kickstart to start
producing
antibody antibodies against
whatever is invaded you like
spikes, yes. And that mRNA may
not be enough. So they add some
of this Agilent, which just just
makes you your body think that
you're being attacked. And we've
seen some bad results from over
use of edge events. But now it's
being here, edge events are
safe, but designed to inflame.
So the I think this is all part
of the education process, which
we've seen the survey, we're
seeing the reports, the studies,
how do we teach people? So I
think that's kind of good, that
going head on by addressing a
lot of the concerns that people
have by lying about them, which
is great.
So you just shouldn't worry
about anything, just we will re
educate you into compliance.
And the final thing just as a as
a conspiracy report, there's a
lot of links now, connecting
Anthony Fauci to Mother Teresa
and child smuggling show, just
so you know, that's out there.
Apparently, Mother Teresa was
not such a Mother Teresa after
all.
No, Christopher Hitchens made a
career out of blasting her every
chance he had he just thought
she was a horrible, missed all
that. I miss lectured and
lectured about this was pretty
funny, because I certainly was
the only one. I certainly got
the programming of how to think
about Mother Teresa.
But I didn't realize that she
was so evil.
Not saying she is I'm just
saying that's what we got going
on. He's a saint. So to take us
I'd like to take a break in a
minute. And then we got to come
back. So we have lots of
election News. I'm going to
spoiler upfront, everything is
China's fault. Just so you know,
the Wu Han flew the
vote corruption and, and
stealing and flipping.
Everything's China. It all
points back to China. I'm
letting you know now because
that's what you'll be hearing
over the course of the next two
months. And let's kick it off
with Gordon Chang, I think
respected here on the show.
who hates China, at least the
Chinese Communist Party, and he
knows exactly is a major major
CCP hate. He's a hater. And he
knows exactly what China is
doing. Well, China's efforts to
collect DNA of the world's
population have been determined.
I mean, they're not only
collecting Chinese people's DNA,
but they're collecting DNA of
everybody else. So for instance,
they've been buying up American
companies that have DNA
profiles, also, they subsidize
the DNA analysis. So if you go
to an ancestry company, chances
are that it is actually a
Chinese business that is looking
at your DNA. And that of course,
can be shoveled on to the
Chinese central government or
Communist Party. Also, there's
been hacking. We know that China
hack anthem, which is America's
second largest insurance
company, that was
Discovered in January 2015. So
there's so many different ways
that China is collecting the DNA
to make probably the world's
biggest database of DNA of
people on the planet. I think
that China has at least two
motivations. Well, first of all,
we know that bio business is
very important to them. They
included it in their Natan,
China 2025 initiative, which is
a decade long program to
dominate certain industries,
including biotechnology. But
also there's something sinister
about this. And that is, we have
heard reporting from Bill Gertz,
for instance, in The Washington
Times that China is probably
trying to develop diseases that
target not just everybody, but
target only certain ethnic or
racial groups.
And there you go, everybody, I'm
glad that you went for your
23andme DNA test good with your
ancestry.com DNA test. They're
gonna design diseases for you.
Did we not warn for something
like this? Did we not?
Make sure writers have been
talking about a targeted genetic
targeting? Which this may have
already been years this may have
already been? Yeah, it's very
possible. Well, if we look at
the fact that apparently nobody
in China, if you're gonna
believe the numbers, has gotten
another version, you haven't
gotten COVID, to what, to
whatever you want to call it.
They haven't caught this virus
in the last nine months are
working at full capacity over
there. And there's no cases, but
everyone in the Western world is
infected.
Of course, then the whole thing
could be a fake on both sides.
But it's beside the point. If
we're if we are to take the
numbers at their face value and
assume it's all true. Bochum.
China has no cases at all.
Well, here's what I'd like to
know.
Where are the dead vaping people
that came in when so fast? Were
all the people who died from
vaping they're in the same room
where they got hunter Biden's
laptop. Here's the theory I've
been working on
in so I vape constantly I vape
and it's propylene glycol and
nicotine obviously, isn't it in
these vaccines is also
polyethylene glycol, which is
not far from the stuff that
that is used for the theater
smoke and the and and the vape
vaporization.
These AC two receptors that we
talked about way in the
beginning and there was
difference in people who were
smokers did or didn't get
the COVID I have a feeling that
a combination of certainly the
nicotine and propylene glycol
has been proven we have lab
tests on and you can look it up
being a.io has been proven to
kill Corona vaccine on the
minute it comes in contact with
Corona virus. Corona, thank you.
I'm doing a reverse. You're
doing the same thing everyone
else is doing. I did a reverse I
said vaccine instead of diverse.
Yeah, so that's better. But
you're right. Stop me on that
stuff. The AC two receptors,
apparently and I said it is very
similar. The nicotine somehow
attracts the corona virus. This
is just a sum. I'm not a
scientist. So I'll just say at
the end I'll say science and you
believe me, and that the
Coronavirus has tricked away
from your own AC two receptors
and tries to bind to the
nicotine. So all I'm just
pulling it out together and
saying maybe they wanted to get
kids in particular off of the
vape sticks because we needed to
get them infected. And we even
try it a little bit later on by
saying ha if you if you vape
you're definitely going to get
more infected which isn't it
clearly I have not there's every
reason for me to have been
deathly ill every reason you
take vitamin D three through
three you might you if you're
going to continue on this line
of thinking please play the
theremin in the background.
Okay, I will and with that I'd
like to thank you for your
encouragement to see in the
morning to you the man who put
in the scene educating into
compliance john
well in the morning to you Mr.
Adam Curry also in the morning
all ships and sea boots on the
ground feet in the air subs in
the water and all the days and
nights out there. Are you
talking through a tube?
I am talking through a tube
to the trolls in the troll room.
Hands up trolls Hands up, hands
up. Let's count you put little
troll counter on. Ooh 2032. Nice
to see it trolls good work on
Sunday. That is the troll room
available to all at no agenda
stream.com where not only can
you sit there and troll along
with all the others.
Thunder that digital bridge You
can also listen to this show
live we've got Darren O'Neill
once again did a great rock roll
pre stream show for us and we
got Nick the rat does live stuff
for Rhino the bearded but also
podcast just that are perfect
from all across the gizmo nation
no commercials mostly talk and
certainly no agenda that is the
troll room no agenda stream.com
and you can ask for an invite
there to no agenda social comm
which is our
algo free social network. It is
federated. So it does work
across all these other servers
which are all their own micro
communities. And since there's
no algos, the signal to noise is
quite enjoyable and you will
like hanging out there. I did
want to read
briefly since he sent a note and
we couldn't find it on the last.
I think he became an instant
night David Fox. I just wanted
to read this note I paraphrase
it somewhere along the along the
line. Forgive me pod fathers I
have deuced I've been listening
since episode number one donated
off and on over the years no
agenda show is truly a great
product. Not only is the show
great, but the producer network
is outstanding. Recently I was
assaulted to the point I was in
the hospital. The first thing I
remember when coming to
consciousness in the hospital
was the nurse coming in the room
and saying Sir, your friend from
Australia Christmas and wants to
talk to you. That's right. My CB
radio wife Chris tracked me down
in North Carolina from New South
Wales. Then right after that the
second call I got was from DC
girl who'd also track me down at
the hospital. The no agenda
producer network swung into full
effect making sure I was okay. I
had someone checking up on me 24
seven, all of them people that
have no agenda social talk about
value for value and could not
agree more. And that is indeed
exactly what's going on over
there. It's really beautiful.
And thank you to farm slave. No,
that can't be farm slave. Let me
get the right. That was the
previous one. Let me go back and
get the right we had show 1300
and that's interesting. Why show
1300 not showing up here on my
Oh, there we go. title that was
electrical college. And the
artwork. Well, we went with
mountain J's very nice 1300 with
blood like
letters, vampire letters. We had
an audio waveform, our classic
mic. They was just kind of a
beautiful piece with the white
background. So it looks good on
the white webpages. The best
podcast in history was the the
monochrome this one.
And did we have anything we
needed to discuss about this
about? Well, there was there was
a lot of art lacking. Now I wish
you'd mentioned some of the
artists so they can fit on a
show like 1300 or even
Thanksgiving Christmas maybe
special dates. Yeah, the special
day shows
it's might not be a bad idea to
do something dramatic to the
day. It's not that often there's
maybe 10 a year true, as opposed
to some pawn or something that's
funny about some little moment
in the show. The 1300s Show. The
most important part of the show
was that it was the 1300s show
and it was a lacking number of
people who picked up on that. I
was kind of surprised Yeah, well
not everyone knows this but
stated as such there was a
couple of there was way too
busy. Most of the art just too
much stuff in there too many
letters not clear something that
pops off the page. I mean all
valiant efforts, no doubt. But I
agree it's the for those types
of shows getting the big 1300 or
turkey or Santa Claus or
something like that is kind of
what you want. And for those of
you on a podcasting 2.0
compatible app you can see all
these this art that we're
talking about right now if you
look at your screen go to new
podcast apps comm to find one
that is compatible with your no
agenda show and we have as part
of our time talent and treasure
value for value system where you
get back whatever you get out of
it. Not only do we have the
great artists Thank you no
agenda our generator calm. But
we have our executive producers
and associate executive
producers to thank right now in
starting with
a
matt love well.
Matt is in McCool kita makikita
I don't know how to pronounce
this and it's an Iowa of all
places mukluk maquoketa Macaca
mK makikita I think
I would go with McQueen
maquoketa Matt qwaqwa $1,000 and
$51,000 ISO five Oh, nice. And
thank you for that I wanted to
make sure your stockings were
full this saint next day I was
hitting the mouth by my generous
brother.
Mike from MAC Walker rock rock
who donated $556 for me in
October, I would like to return
the favor and get him to the
roundtable where he belongs.
Before the Corning festivities,
the coordinator money coming
coming coming in are you
thankful for some mac and cheese
and a long cut Sharpton, both of
which are plentiful now but will
soon be hard to come by. Mike
can pick up his own night name.
But if he had to pick one, if I
had to pick one farmer would be
Mike Knight of all tradition.
Lastly, is in need of a deducing
we have that
you've been reduced.
So, okay, so he'll be on the
list and you'll be a use didn't
give him executive producer
credit. So you'll you'll get
that.
That's not the right mac and
cheese.
I'm sorry, what is this then?
President Trump said that
because of the killing of Al
Baghdadi make
the world a better place. And I
wouldn't give credit to he and
those that were responsible for
it. But we have a lot of work
that must still be done in the
area of terrorism in the same
area of the world where al
Baghdadi Baghdadi was
in our own nation. They're your
slaves with the mac and cheese
macaroni and cheese melted
together mac and cheese mac and
cheese mac and cheese.
There you go. Matt thank you
very much for your courage. On
word with
Jenny Jenny Jenny j Naples
Massey in Arvada, Colorado $588
and 90 cents. And she sent a PDF
file of all things.
Letter of explanation to bat
coin.
I tried emailing an image that I
took. I took it was a coin I
found and changing my original
donation mentioning the bat coin
on your show back in June but it
must not have gone through as
Adam properly debunked the coin.
So to clarify, this quarter has
actually been in circulation all
year. Yes, I was incorrect. And
I believe I stated such well I
don't believe you did because I
didn't I don't remember any of
this. Yeah, I think I remember
being quite strong about this as
bullcrap that it was a
commemorative coin. But it's
not. It was an actual quarter.
That was minted with the bat.
With a bat. Yeah. With the
baseball bat. No a bat as in a
Wu Han flu bat. What was the
point?
Well, there's a vampire coin.
I'm not getting that it's Yeah,
it was it was okay. There was a
quarter that people were finding
a 25 uS 25 cent quarter that had
a bat on the on one side. You
know this Really? Yes. Is it a
collectible?
Oh,
by the way I am and I like coins
I keep going about this. I
can't.
Okay, here it is. A quarter with
a bet on it will be this is from
Cincinnati will be minted in the
new year. It's part of the
United States Mint America the
Beautiful quarters program which
honors national parks and other
national sites across the Texas
that
impossibly Yeah, I think so.
Yeah. Yeah, I think and now I
started to remember I think they
had something to do with San
Antonio, Texas. Well, Austin is
the we've got the bat bridge. I
thought the San Antonio had more
bats than Austin. It's actually
it's so creepy. If you look at
this because I'm looking at a
blow up of it. It's two bats one
is hanging upside down has a
baby bat in it's Tony Hawk. It's
super creepy.
So she sent them in the Pio box
if I want one I def I never got
it back. Sorry. I remember
something like this. I think it
is It was so long ago. I just
bet she says to settle the mail
that prove a quarter each of you
I hope he was hoping to package
your eyes you for the show.
Well, I didn't. I have seen the
coins coming through. If I see
it. I'll put it aside for you.
As I own a restaurant in Denver,
it took a little while for one
of the coins to come through my
restaurants cash deposits. It
was great, random fun for my
marriage. As we looked to the
two coins we mailed to you both
couples that no agenda together
do indeed stay together.
Apparently, thanks for the bad
coin. We look forward to every
show and often find ourselves
quoting the clips randomly to
friends that time. Like it's
true with no explanation except
it's a good one. No explanation.
Just do it. I tell you but I'd
have to hit you in the mouse.
Most of the time. They're
intrigued and we have grown our
no agenda community within our
friend and family circles.
That's a plus. A lot of people
can't manage that. No agenda has
kept me sane through all this.
insanity the value is far more
than I can afford to send today.
But this amount brings me to
Dame hood. County attached nice
if available. I would love to be
known as Dame Valentine of the
bluebird powder region. I think
she's on the list, isn't she?
Yes, she is. Thank you for your
courage gentlemen and john, stay
safe. A little goat karma for my
restaurant would be greatly
appreciated with gratitude.
Karma
I'm gonna just get her did I?
What did she want at the
roundtable? I'm sorry, I missed
that. Oh, yeah, I have the PDF.
I just have to open it up again.
I have to I can get it back.
You can county attached you can
go No, nothing. Nothing. Okay,
go ahead and read the next one.
We're all good.
Okay, oh, Dave fukase. Oh, Duke
of America's Heartland and the
Arabian Peninsula is back. Nice.
Hello. But is he back? I don't
think he's back. I don't think
he's back from Asia is back on
the list. Poor guy 390 30
Gladstone, Missouri.
He should go to neon while
you're there. You know, there's
a apparently What's his name?
Dave Kirschner, whatever his
name is. And some other guys I
guess maybe pompeyo they're
gonna go meet to Prince Krishna
in Saudi Arabia before the term
is up so de fukase Otto has been
locked up in the United Arab
Emirates for 18 years and this
is your this is your great idea
for him. Oh, you should go see
those guys. He should he should
go to the horrible the guy's
been locked up. He can't leave.
He's there he might have to go
check stuff out. True.
I have a clip I want to play
it This is how important it is
to go see me I'm
just play this addition before
us because Oh, nice to hear
this. This is the neon rundown.
Oh, there it is. Neon will be
massive, over 10,000 square
miles or over 26,000 square
kilometers that will make it
more than 33
times larger than New York City
and a little less than the size
of Massachusetts located in the
northwest corner of Saudi
Arabia. Neon loosely connects
the three continents of Africa
Asia and Europe and hopes to be
a leading global hub
neon size of massive a city the
size of Massachusetts and we
invest in neon yellow Yeah,
isn't a strategy kidding.
I need to exit exit this earth
we need to go to neon neon Neon
is the place why I put that in
there because there's the code
word in there and 33 and so it
was nice to get that message he
knows what's up that's a
squirrel nest going on. He
writes on it the company
recently with details to follow
as things start to settle out
suffice it to say I respectfully
respectfully suggest the TPP
jobs karma with a deliberate aim
in my general direction you got
it. It's also time to once again
celebrate my end day Melody's
nuptials 17 years and we never
had a fight. That's because you
haven't been together for but
maybe Yeah.
How could you fight? Just Dame
Isabella's 12th birthday? I
guess you got together for that
milestones that at last I'll
celebrate with them from afar as
usual Ah, of course. Such a
suspicious happenings are made
all the better with a tooth of
the official no agenda
celebration horn Hello, and some
terrible terrier karma. Okay,
well we can always toot the horn
for you. Congratulations much
love from the kingdom yes and
much love from us and from no
agenda nation for your 17 years
together
I didn't mean that
that's not what he was looking
for. I gave him a dog karma that
was not the idea. This is what
he needs.
Karma That's better.
Now you got a double man and
that was definitely directed in
you. Now you've got the next
one. And this brings up an
interesting point is shortfall
this today. Okay. We have no
associate executive producers.
It is an interesting thing.
And this is our last for the
segment Baron dirty dick banks
who is in Washington DC. And he
says congrats on 1301 figured
that might be a letdown after
1300. Yeah, well, there's no
associates wide open. Hello,
Dana. A few things. One, my
tired and true method of sending
john a wine order or wine label
and getting insight on wine has
failed.
This is bad because I think
everyone I know
feels that they can text you
john at any time of the day.
If there's a picture of a wine
bottle or a list, you will reply
so I'm surprised I'm there a
surprise this failed. So he goes
on to dirty dirty big banks
recently bought a 2015. Bordeaux
case or two. Which is wrong. You
want the 2016 No, 2015 is great.
Okay, my honey Sorry, I was
unbelievable. I was out looking
for 2016 I didn't know 2020
here's the reason I'll say it
again. I said it before in the
show. You can pick it you can
throw a dart at 2016 Bordeaux
and it's going to be a winner.
Okay. 2015 Bordeaux's, that is a
great year, but only there's a
couple of areas where it's
spotty. Hmm, well, that's the
difference. He says he recently
bought a 2015 Bordeaux case or
two. And then he says you need
to check your email. That to
celebrate my oldest son's birth
year more on him in a second.
We'd love 2017 and 19 Bordeaux
recommendations to celebrate my
other two boys birth years. I'll
continue while you think about
that, too. Thank you I get the
sanity you provide myself with a
no agenda chief hater officer,
my smokin hot wife who will
never listen to the show because
of her corrupted feminist view.
This is a marriage made in
heaven are available to keep
things relatively normal for our
three boys in difficult times
the fact base statistics and
sensible approaches to living
life you've provided on the
show, which I then in turn spoon
feed to her unbeknownst to the
NA source. Allow us to avoid the
amygdala enlargement hysteria
for this antidote to the stereo.
I thank you. My oldest son,
Barrett, Alexander bangs, who
was probably screaming as I play
this in the car because we're
not playing his favorite Disney
songs. Turns five on Monday 12
seven. It's small, small world
you feel better now? Barrett,
you are my nugget. I love you.
And I'm so proud of you. Poor
Barrett's grandparents, who are
my folks and his uncle and aunt,
my brother and his wife have all
will have punted on Barrett's
birthday due to the hysteria
libtards. The irony, my parents
both already had COVID and as I
saw on a recent Wall Street
Journal, a whopping 54 of 200
million cases worldwide have
gotten it twice. Hopefully
they're spending my entire shit
hopefully. Hopefully, they're
spending my entire inheritance
on the lottery as we speak.
Since they're so Special shout
outs to Archer Campbell bangs
age three and Colton Reed banks
18 months both probably
screaming as well currently
since we aren't playing their
Disney songs either. Love you
both and thanks for being such
good little brothers too big
brother Barrett. Could use big
sales karma to close out the
year and health karma first
doctor's appointment in two
years on Monday. I wish I was in
bed but alas after traveling to
Disney for Thanksgiving. This is
the problem with your family.
You've got to cut back on the
Disney mind control for these
children. Please I beg of you.
Look up the Wizard of Oz.
After traveling to Disney for
Thanksgiving, the boys school is
required. Sorry.
The Wizard of Oz not a Disney
product. Yeah, but that's where
it all started.
Okay, all right. You're right.
Look at Christina Aguilera. Nuff
said look at Britney Spears.
Nuff said. So we hear we'll dam
as the boy school is requiring
buys the fastest of Montgomery
County, Maryland, which I used
to live in montgomery county.
That's where I where I was for a
few years after we came back
from Africa to get zivkovic
testing papers prior to them
coming back. So we all got
tested negative and I got a
sinus infection from the test.
Well that you got to get a
dirty, yes, dirty swab baby.
They infected you.
That we're gonna say john, well,
yeah, I was gonna say that or
they pee on the swab in some
areas.
And which would that be in the
DC area or montgomery county
area the PC area apparently.
We have several regularly tested
frontline workers as friends and
family and this is a common side
effect. So while I should be in
bed, my head is blasting with
sinus pressure side note. Pretty
sure I got COVID last Christmas.
It's been here longer than any
of us realize. Thank you for all
you do. It's truly it's
priceless, barren, dirty dig
bags of dcps. I'm an Eagle Scout
fairly remarkable how many
listeners are and like most
Eagle Scout listeners.
My listeners he
like most Eagle Scout listeners,
my kids won't set foot in the
Boy Scouts sad the corruption of
such a wonderful organization.
I'm also Jesuit educated, I'd be
willing to bet there's also a
larger cut that's also a larger
cohort of your listeners. Yes, I
think that's true, including Dr.
Anthony Fauci.
So thank you very much. We do
have some some health karma and
I'm going to throw in a little
bit of goat there for you in the
bank family. You've got
karma
Now why did you see 199 99
Do we want to push that one
person up as no such person
specifically said we'll read his
note. Actually since we don't
we're short. We're short
Missouri is no this is Dana.
This is our the Hollywood or
Hollywood producer celebrity.
Yeah. Dana Brunetti known from
social
is good enough and and and and
50 Shades of Grey 50 Shades of
Grey 150 shades of grey shade
you've ever seen. He's more
embarrassed by that except his
banker. Yeah, he's not
embarrassed by that at all this
state of Jesus in the state of
Jefferson he claims Oh, sorry
for the 199 99 but I have to
avoid the Associate Producer
credits. They hurt my standing
in the industry.
He says if I have any left
Hollywood Yes, my IMDB page
however happened to report the
karma works ironically, I just
sold the show to IMDb TV. Oh,
there you go. The karma works.
Also the rainstick works Yeah,
so we got a storm here and a
tree fell on the awning of my
Airstream and it destroyed it.
To be fair to be fair, the
awnings on the air streams are
pieces of crap to confirm
their crappy john turn your
speaker's down and stop clicking
your pin. Anyway, I'm gonna go
tasting with him on Monday. Oh,
you're gonna go and what are you
going to be tasting? We're going
to vary Kay. That's the name of
it very a very it's a very it's
a very tag. What is very a is
that a winery up in this Edward
Sonoma County winery in the
northern part is an Alexander
Valley. This is one of the
probably four super high end
called wineries that is
unlike the other ones, this one
is a little more problem. I'm
guessing because I haven't been
to the to the other ones.
Very, very slick.
Are you do you have to be very
tame if you go to Verity. Yes,
yes. I have to say yes. Doubt
Tell me in your just Verity
voice about the 2015 Bordeaux
recommendation that no What did
he want Deke? Bang. So I said we
get back he wants 2017 and 2019.
Um, I have to send them a note
on this. Okay. 2017 is the
sketchy year in Bordeaux. And I
think it's generally not good.
But there's good wines that come
out of it. Like they're new, but
they're all high end. So you
have to buy an expensive wine
for 2017 if you want to hold up.
Otherwise, there's not like you
can go through the dark like you
can with 2016 2018 and 19 have
not really hit the market yet.
But both of them look like
killer years. Which is better of
the two. I think they're both
going to be great, but I don't
know which was the throw the
dart year but 2019 I'm guessing
it just you can probably just
pick anything out it's going to
be good but you want to pick for
kids because you want to wind
the last at least 21 years. You
do with it? Is that a thing?
Well, Bordeaux is in a good year
last 50 years but 21 years is
what you want because the
kitchen has some wine is wine
year when he's
birthday is so cute as hell
there's wine and you know it's
this kind of kind of charming.
Oh yeah, super super. Well it is
to wine drinker.
Anyway, we were at the
restaurant last night I
specifically look for a 2016
Bordeaux there wasn't a Bordeaux
on the list. Oh
outrage it's an outrage or maybe
it was Bordeaux and had some
friends
of yours over generalized wine
tip because I've always seen
them once a second hold on a
second
generalized wine tip you go to
you go to a restaurant you don't
know anything. And you know you
got to sell me a and if he
really somebody is are no good
unless you know how to talk to
them. And that means you better
know something. So this
otherwise are just bullshit. But
if you know we're gonna be
talking about you're gonna give
us some phrases to use so we can
impress them. Now I'm just gonna
give you a wine to pick okay?
Because if this wine is on any
wine list, and it's on most wine
list, because they need these
alternative cheap wines that are
good. And this is a cheap wine
that's good.
Outside of a Beaujolais was
usually if there's emotionally
and they'll that you can talk to
the sommelier, and they'll tell
you which one might be the best.
But look for a G gone does g big
g gone? GOND a s is a Rhone
Valley wine is a recent
appellation, I think from maybe
20 years ago or so. It's always
dynamite. I don't care what year
it is. If it's on the wine list,
I guarantee I picked it up for a
reason because it's good tasting
cheap. So if relatively cheap,
can I ask a question Would it be
then if I'm in the restaurant,
can I say something like do you
have a gigondas or something
like that? When you sound like
at least sound like a loser?
Okay.
Don't do that.
I will refrain. You got it.
And thank you to our executive
producers exclusively today.
That has not happened a long
time that we haven't had an
associate executive producer. I
don't even know if that's ever
happened. It's usually the other
way around. Oh, yeah. we
bump a guy. Yeah. No, no one got
bumped. He's all he's all bummed
down. Yeah, no, it gets bumped
down. So we just don't have one.
That's the way it is. Well, we
are highly beginning of the end
highly appreciate
that. That's your build back
better, baby. That's how it
rolls Joe's coming in shows
going down. We highly appreciate
the support that we receive from
these executive producers. And
we do have more producers who
have certainly supported the
show. We'll talk about them,
we'll thank them in our second
segment. We do need your help,
especially from your associate
executives out there. And you
know, apparently Hollywood has
given up on us because they've
been shamed, shamed for
promoting the show. Shame for
benign promoting Same for
producing it. IMDb shame Oh, by
the way, you know, he says he
got a gig at IMDb TV and I'm
looking I said what is that you
know what it is? Yes, I think I
looked it up it's Did you know
that i AMD was purchased by
Amazon yes that's Amazon TV.
That's right. I didn't know this
because I looked at oh this is
like I am b d TV whatever it is
just like some sort of an Amazon
second channel what would you be
more ashamed of saying that yes
produce agree with
agree that you produce the no
agenda show you produced a show
for Amazon. But no, it's not.
Amazon is IMD BMT. But that's
but that's the head fake because
it's an IMDb TV. Yeah, it's a
Jeff Bezos property.
Yeah, that's what I okay. So the
he has to live with it.
You have to live with your
choices young man should decide.
And again, thank you. This is
exactly how we treat our top
donors. And somehow they like
it. I'm not quite sure how that
works. But we've been doing it
for a while. And we'd love to do
it again. With your help on the
show coming up in just a couple
of days will be Thursday. And we
are getting closer to all kinds
of fun deadlines. So there's
certainly be stuff to
deconstruct. Please, please help
us support the show by going to
devora.org slash and that's
really all I asked for is your
time your talent or your
treasure and thank you for
producing the show. Our formula
is this. We go out. We hit
people in the mouth.
little animal.
A little entre mom before we get
into other stuff. A win a win
for sane pneus a win for people
like myself, who are sick and
tired of lying scumbag fellow
travelers. Ha ha ha ha ha suck
it well, can I there's a new
rule for airline passengers no
more emotional support animals.
Next year the only service
animals allowed on planes will
be dogs specifically trained to
help people with disabilities
that rules out cats and exotic
pets including Yes, turkeys and
peacocks. Dogs
finally, finally, finally
finally and you will be
required. If the dog is for
psychiatric purposes you will be
required. Regardless Actually, I
don't think you can be required
to show why you have a service
dog but you will have to show
the true service dog papers not
some phony baloney saddle you
threw on your poodle that says
emotional support and the mo
haha suck it you pussies so sick
and tired of these liar that was
out of control. I was lying
they're liars. Oh and they get
too bored first with their lying
dogs.
So that's over. Thank you that
really trying to squeeze every
dime they can out of passengers
now they need people to pay for
their pets and they got no
money.
So I have a couple of little
side projects here a little side
reports Okay, from NBC This is
apparent what's coming up as
package get in package you're
getting this package package
you're getting yeah package
you're getting okay because all
these stores everything's all
the shops are closed so
everyone's ordering online and
so now there's the delivery
services can handle it so it's a
package get in.
So I picked up this very short
clips on NBC did a whole 10
minutes on it.
But I get this this I found this
to be peculiar This is package
Gedan with odd reporter NBC,
okay.
The holiday delivery crushes on
with a staggering number of
packages by Christmas companies
are now taking extreme measures
and the new deadlines for gift
delivery Julian cat has details
with Christmas around the corner
the shipping rush is on. And
experts say this year there will
be 250 million more packages
than delivery systems can
handle. We will be having 3
billion packages to be delivered
between Thanksgiving and
Christmas and that is not
counting the millions of
packages that will come starting
middle of next week for COVID-19
vaccines.
That's weird that doesn't sound
writing this indian guy in an
echo chamber because it sounds
like there's some science to it
you do the sounds like he's in
the sound This is more of the
reporting there's this the best
NBC can do is find this guy this
Indian who sounds like he's
calling you about you know
mariadb special offer or the IRS
disaster you know, the IRS is
after you or your social
security number has been
compromised. So they bring this
guy in
as a
loot. And so I thought this was
idiotic and so then they go to
the end of the report with this
is packaged get an odd voice
drop. Now they they put him in
as a punch line in another in
the later part of the report
once you play this because if
you leave your shopping to the
last minute but look destiny
thing for your orders this year
is going to be very expensive.
shipping fees will only
increase. Okay, let me just the
first thing I observed is he's
talking about because COVID
vaccine that's not being mailed
that's that's supposed to be
distributed by Yeah, that's true
operation works.
But the way what is NBC up to
that they have to use this guy
in a in a he's in a closet or in
a bucket. I mean, it's just
lame. I've got an example later
in the show some very poor
Editing by NBC is really
dropping the ball here. But I
don't think this report was
about shipper getting or
anything else. I think it was
about this native ad part. Right
in the middle of the of the of
the package getting report is
this little native ad right in
the middle listen to this
instacart now offering same day
delivery for major brands, like
the Disney Store, Bed Bath and
Beyond Sephora and more.
me hear that again. instacart.
Now offering same day delivery
for major brands, like the
Disney Store, Bed Bath and
Beyond Sephora and more.
What's the point of that? Oh,
that's totally a native ad. For
instance, they charge disney
store X amount of money just to
be mentioned in the report.
I'd like to know what the fee
was.
No, I really don't care. Doesn't
matter who's watching that the
only person watching is you and
it's not working on you. So
the President was I'm gonna
transition real fast away from
that. The President was in
Georgia yesterday. And yeah, and
he had a big rally
with a lot of mega nation very
excited to have him there. And
he was relaxed and chilled. And
he was cracking jokes.
It was he was a very relaxed
guy. The first lady came out and
had dynamite. Did I say
dynamite? Maroon red leather
coat? Oh my god. That was a
great she looks fantastic. She
almost winged it without the
prompter. got through most of it
pretty well. And here's just a
quick couple of sound bites and
cucumbers who grow does
cucumbers around here. Because I
like cucumbers, can you I'm the
only one. I like you. You can
tell he's back to his old self.
He's He's relaxed. He's chatting
about cucumbers. It really
doesn't matter too much.
Everything seems to be pretty
good. He does see something that
we've noticed as well. And this
issue is all go awry in Georgia
with the with the vote counts.
And if it turns out that there
was some Hanky Panky business
going on, according to mo facts
that Stacey Abrams would be left
holding the bag and the
president called her out. And
whatever reason your secretary
of state and your governor are
afraid of Stacey Abrams, they're
afraid.
So he's amping up everything on
What's happening in Georgia.
Now,
if you're interested in want to
dive deep into all of the
mounting evidence regarding
election fraud and can save
voter fraud, but I think
election fraud is more accurate,
and there and which lawsuits and
there's new lawsuits going in
continuously. Ted Cruz is now
involved. I find this very
amusing. Ted Cruz is going to
the Supreme Court on behalf of
the people. I know for the
people of Pennsylvania, but I'm
on behalf of the people. As he
feels that there's a catch 22
somehow that goes into the
latches act as to when you can
when you do or do not have
standing to bring a lawsuit, and
that you in an election, you
basically can't win. Because if
the election isn't dead, all the
counting is done. You don't have
standing because there's no
crime being committed. And if
you come after the fact and they
say, well, you should have
mentioned it earlier, so now
there's no now You're too late.
Ah, yeah, this is it's something
that is constitutionally weird.
And he's going to fight that and
that could change something in
Pennsylvania, Ted Cruz, for as
creepy as he can be. He's a good
lawyer and he has been at the
Supreme Court and he has he has
won stuff at the Supreme Court
and he was also which always
surprised me when he went up
against Trump because he lost
was Ted Cruz as it was always
the head and apparently a rough
and tumble debater. He was the
head of the debating society and
like a superstar debater. He was
a master debater he master
debater. I think we titled The
show after him once. So I have
three clips that will bring you
up to speed on what's happening.
I think the easiest is to start
with the man who
clearly knows exactly what's
going on. He works at CNN, so
why wouldn't he know what's
happening with the morning
briefing from Jeff Zucker. This
is Jake Tapper. To talk
specifically about El Cid, the
cracking keeper and Lynwood who
are filing lawsuit after lawsuit
city power new lawsuit in
Arizona alleging 412,000 illegal
ballots This Just In fact, most
of even Fox I heard yesterday
are going from
no widespread voter fraud to Wow
What did you open a beer?
A Miller Lite. Well, then I'll
have to pour it.
Well, okay, I mean, that's done
didn't work. I got water all
over my pants. Okay, well, I'm
gonna do my own version of it
here.
Perfect. No water.
So there's lots I mean,
interrupt that's go on. I wanted
to bomb hit anyway. There's lots
of
elbowed worn up. There's, you
know, General Flynn is now also
come out. And he's talking and
so there's a lot going on. But
let's Oh, yeah. That's what I
was saying before is interrupted
that fox news has gone from
there's no widespread voter
fraud, which mean and everyone
says this, oh, well, that means
there's some some fraud,
election fraud, but it's not
widespread. And now they've gone
to Well, it's kind of curious
where things are coming up with.
Unless you're Jake Tapper. This
is the best this is. This is the
handbook for m five m, how to
marginalize someone who may
actually be right about
something, just do the
following. So pro Trump
attorneys, Linwood and Sidney
Powell, who constantly push the
most deranged conspiracy
theories. Because there's,
there's a spectrum of them that
mean and if you listen to no
agenda show those those cats
aren't anywhere ever compared to
these guys. They held one of
these stop this steel rallies
this week in Georgia. Again,
this is all based on nonsense,
and the action.
Wait a minute, wait a minute,
point of order point of personal
privilege. You cannot say for
weeks, baseless claims, and then
say it's based on nonsense. It's
either baseless or not Jake
Tapper. Again, this is all based
on nonsense. And they actually
were discouraging Georgia
republicans from voting at all
in the runoffs on January 5.
Take a listen.
I think I would encourage all
Georgians to make it known that
you will not vote at all until
your vote is secure. They have
not earned your vote.
Don't you give it to them.
Why would you go back in folks
in another rigged election for
God's sakes.
Now, again, as a factual matter,
the vote was
secure and is secure by all
evidence, and it was not rigged.
So what they're saying is not
true.
There you go, that you know that
that report is so outrageous. I
have to give you a clip of the
day for that. Well, I appreciate
that unexpected by the way.
I have a Buddhist, I have the
NBC version of what you just
play. We need to hear this. This
is very important, but it's not
as good as that. Well, Jake
Tapper is the big leaks. So it's
beyond but Jake Tapper is really
an opinion guy, not not a news
guy. Here's the news guy. This
weird election report from NBC
tonight President Trump headed
south, dialing up his pressure
campaign against Georgia's
republican governor to persuade
the state legislature to
overturn Biden's victory. You
got to make sure your governor
gets a lot tougher than he's
been because it's taken this
election is control of the US
Senate. And that really means
control of this country are
waiting for him in Georgia. Many
Trump supporters echoed the
President's unfounded claims of
election fraud. I wanted to come
see my president, my next
president for the next four
years. While Mr. Trump's trip is
for Georgia's high stakes senate
run off next month. The
President is fixated on the
November election he lost.
Georgia's ballots have been
recounted twice. But the
President demands a separate
signature check for all voters
today blasting Georgia's top GOP
leaders. Why are these two
Republicans saying no. aides to
Governor Brian Kemp say the
president phone today. Kim
tweeted, as I told the president
this morning, I've publicly
called for a signature audit
three times. The President fired
back but you never got the
signature verification. Your
people are refusing to do what
you ask. The governor says he
cannot lawfully give President
Trump what he wants.
That was that a whipsaw?
It was the best whipsaw I've
ever heard.
People refusing to do what
the governor says he cannot
lawfully give President Trump
what he wants.
Did you edit that? That's the
way the report No I did not.
People
are yelling for more years. What
she's she did the whipsaw works
like this. She what Trump wants
is the signature recount. Right.
And that's what he wants. Yeah.
And so so they they edit in when
she says the words give Trump
what he wants, then they have
these people yelling for more
years, which is also what he
wants, but it's not part of the
report. So it's like a very
advanced whipsaw. Yes. I don't
think it's on purpose. I think
they're just idiots.
I don't I don't know you say
very advanced, you give them a
lot of credit. You I'm not going
to make an argument here. Okay.
But you might be right. But
it's, it's beautiful.
Let's get an update. Oops, let's
get an update from the horse's
mouth. So to speak from El Cid,
the cracking keeper? Well, the
11th circuit just rejected our
appeal from the district courts,
partial grant of relief to us.
And so we'll be back in the
District Court for a hearing.
Hopefully Monday or Tuesday.
We'll see where it goes from
there. But one of the things we
want and have been trying to get
with great opposition is the
voting machines to be secured
all across the state of Georgia,
because massive evidence of the
shaping of votes and the
flipping of votes from a Trump
to Biden exists in those
machines, except to the extent
they've been erasing things and
destroying evidence as fast as
they can do it. I have in my
office right now, a huge bag of
shredded ballots. I can't wait
to see what that discloses. And
they're more on the way where do
you get the shredded ballots
from who turns those over to
you? citizens are out there,
watching and observing
everything. The people of
America are not going to allow
our president to be defeated by
fraudulent election mechanisms.
And these people have used every
manner in means of voter fraud.
You can imagine it's was heavily
coordinated, it was heavily
funded. And they now have 25
lawyers or so lined up against
us, our little ragtag team of
misfit toys that are trying to
fight for truth and justice for
the American people. well
positioned ragtag team. Yeah.
Now, I think she has a lot more
coming. And we have some time
and I'm going to run through the
constitutional timeline and in a
moment with help from the
representative from Alabama, but
here's my conflict, my personal
conflict. The show's title is no
agenda.
I have no agenda. I don't give a
crap about Democrat, Republican
libertarian. I've never belonged
to any party ever. nor would I,
I don't like the idea. I'm not
interested in the political
power. I'm a United States
citizen. And the reason why I'm
still very interested in this is
because I do believe in stuff
like this, Samuel Adams said,
the liberties of our country,
the freedoms of our civil
constitution are worth defending
at all hazards. It is our duty
to defend them against all
attacks, we have received them
as a fair inheritance from our
worthy ancestors, they purchased
them for us with toil and danger
and expensive treasure and
blood, it will bring a mark of
everlasting infamy on the
present generation enlightened
as it is, if we should suffer
them to be rested from us by
violence without a struggle, or
to be cheated out of them by the
artifices of designing men.
So that's why I'm very
interested, if this is rigged,
then we need to make sure it's
unrigged for the midterm and
unrigged for the next general
election, four years, that's the
most important thing. And it's
not baseless, there's clear
evidence of election fraud and
some voter fraud are two
different things. And this will,
and this will go the president
who has sworn to uphold defend
the Constitution of the United
States, as has every other House
of Representative member, every
senator, they have the duty to
see this all the way through,
and the American people have
been poorly educated and do not
understand the civics of our
constitutional republic. So in
the next few months, actually, I
should read this first before I
go to the final thing I'll have
for today. This is the opening
paragraph of executive order on
imposing certain sanctions in
the event of foreign
interference in the United
States election. And this was
issued on September 12 2018. I,
Donald J. Trump, president
united states of america find
that the ability of persons
located in whole or in
substantial part outside the
United States to interfere in or
undermine public confidence in
the United States elections,
including through the
unauthorized accessing of
election and campaign
infrastructure, or the covert
distribution of propaganda and
disinformation constitutes an
unusual and extraordinary threat
to the national security and
foreign policy of the United
States. Although there has been
no evidence of a foreign power
altering the outcome or vote
tabulation and the United States
election, foreign powers have
historically sought to exploit
America's free and open
political system. In recent
years, the proliferation of
digital devices and internet
based communications has created
significant vulnerabilities and
magnified the scope and
intensity of the threat of
foreign interference as
illustrated in the 2017
intelligence community asset, I
hereby declare a national
emergency to deal with this
threat. And without going into
this deeper, it's it's alarming
executive order. It's your duty
almost to read it just to be
informed. But 45 days after the
conclusion of the United States
election, the Director of
National Intelligence, in
consultation with the heads of
any other appropriate executive
departments shall conduct an
assessment of any information
indicating the foreign
government, or any person acting
as an agent on behalf of foreign
government has acted with the
intent or purpose of interfering
that election. And it goes on
and on and on. It's almost as if
he knew it was coming. That's
all I'm gonna say. So how do we
get this to the final outcome
that the President wants? We
will have to go through the
process the Electoral College,
all of this is almost
unnecessary. If you listen to
the timeline of representative
mo Brooks from Alabama, who
explains exactly how this will
go down on January the sixth at
1pm. Eastern Time, the 50 states
will report to Congress, the
president Senate will preside
over this meeting, will report
to Congress, what they contend
for the electoral college
results in their state. If a
house member and a senator
objects to the submission of
electoral college votes by any
state that immediately triggers
a house floor vote in a Senate
for a vote on whether to accept
or reject those electoral
college votes submitted by that
particular state. The amount of
debate on the house and senate
floor is limited to two hours
under federal law. And if we
reject those electoral college
votes, then they're taken out of
the mix. If the election process
problems are so great, that
after subtracting the electoral
college votes of states that are
running a poor election system,
the system so suspect that you
can't give credibility to the
results that are being reported.
Then,
the United States Constitution
mandates that Congress determine
who the next president and vice
president of the United States
will be under Article One,
Article two and amendment 12.
United States Constitution, the
house of representatives will be
the body that determines who is
president knighted states. The
vice president will be
determined by the United States
Senate and they can even be
members of different parties, if
that's the will of the House and
the Senate. Now in the house,
there's a little bit of a twist.
It's not a majority of 435
congressmen that determines who
the President knighted states
will be, whether it is a
majority of the state
delegations that determines who
the President knighted states
will be. That being the case,
based on the election we just
had a couple of weeks ago, the
republicans controlled 26 state
delegations, the democrats
controlled 20 state delegations,
with the remainder being tied
with the possible exception of
Iowa. There's an uncalled Iowa
house race, if that is called in
favor of the GOP candidate who's
up last I saw about 47 votes,
then there will be 27 state
delegations that have a majority
of their members being
Republican, hence, the house
would be in a position to elect
a republican to the White House,
based on what we saw a couple of
weeks ago on Election Day,
earlier in November, November
the third, there you go. I think
Trump has it. Yeah, I don't know
how many times you're gonna play
variations of that exact same
scenario. I've never, I don't
think we've ever played this
exact scenario. This is the
first time I've ever heard it
explained so clearly. But I will
give you the clearly part.
But it's been played one way or
the other.
Two or three times, actually,
I'd had to dig up to those Well,
okay, but then then help me just
in quick review, so we don't
have to ever play it again. So
we understand because I saw the
troll room also go legally.
There's already one house member
who was going to reject that's
Mo, that's mo Brooks. If one
senator does the same, then
there's a possibility that
several of these contested
states will go away and be
struck and taken off would be I
mean, it is a possibility.
That's what he said. Yeah. And
then it seems like it may go
eventually to the States. I
mean, that's the ultimate I keep
hearing his although this Iowa
thing seems like there's a
little a little snake in the
grass there that could thwart
everything, but that will create
a lot of friction, a lot of
strife. And part of the strategy
I think, not knowing anything,
is to a blanket is much of the
alternative media universe.
That's rumble that
parlor, but it's also podcasts
with as much of the actual
documentation as possible. I'm
certainly receiving
just document after document.
Certainly when it as it pertains
to China, who apparently printed
up 5 million ballots complained
they couldn't get the the the
metallic watermark right, and
shipped it with medical supplies
to the US to be distributed pre
printed with Biden as the as the
selection.
It sounds to me like this would
be possible.
Certainly winnings possible,
certainly likely the likelihood
we have to deal with and the
likelihood is pretty close to
zero. Why do you say that? Why
do you see it so close to zero?
Can we at least give a 5050
almost go are the same thing.
Again, you have all the
intelligence agencies, the CIA,
the FBI, the entire mainstream
media, most of the news, the
major news organizations, The
New York Times, Washington Post,
everybody all lined up against
this president to get him kicked
out in any way they can correct.
I just don't see how you can
what your one or two represents,
like mo Brooks is going to
really put a stop to this. It's
like a juggernaut in the favor
of Biden. And that's what's
happening. And I don't see any
way of stopping it. And you
yourself used to play the clip
where it was Ron Paul, who said,
Well, you know, the CIA kind of
took over running the country
when they killed Kennedy, which
is an old clip this in the
archives, which I which I still
believe Yes.
And if that's the case, then
they're running the country and
they don't want Trump in anymore
and they're going to end they'd
luckily we didn't get shot. The
only thing I will correct you on
is that the
most sophisticated intelligence
agency in the world is the
Defense Intelligence Agency.
It's bigger. And I think they
have access to more toys than
the CIA and the CIA recently had
special operations taken away
from them. So, yes, the the
Special Operations was not taken
away from the CEO that special
operations is taken away from
the the military, the army and
the military jsoc. Guys, the CIA
still could do what they want.
Well, so Okay, now the budget of
the DEA and they, if that's if
that's iffy.
And who has the best toys
supposed to be? Right? All
right. All right. But let's,
let's just separate this into
two things. I have no argument
with you about the power of the
of all the intelligence agencies
and the media, which I don't
even know why you separate those
two, but Okay, well, we'll call
them two separate things that
mainstream media and the
intelligence community, but
they're not there, they're
saying, I have no, I no doubt, I
do not underestimate their
power. But I think we can agree
that the Constitution is now
against that power. And we'll
see what happens. Is that that
is that the the final word on
this? That Yes? Seems like
there's a possibility, but it'll
never happen because of the
intelligence agencies and the
media, which is the same group?
Well, I don't think it's the
same group, because they're not
necessarily everyone that works
for the media is not getting
paid by the by the CIA. You
understand what? You understand
the point? Yes. But it's still
not to say these are separate
groups in the public eye. And in
separate groups with their own
kind of, you know, they push
push here, and they push push
there, and they've done a really
good job with COVID. If you
haven't noticed, as we have our
show, I just, it's the
likelihood to me is zero. But
we'll see. I mean, it's great. I
think it would be fabulous. If
we could get an exercise in
this, because we've never seen
it before that we have is we
haven't hundred years. We
haven't but it has happened.
Yeah. Within the last nobody
living No, has witnessed this.
No, no. Okay, that's fine. So
I'm just saying that this is
This, to me was a very clear
path. Now I have a date, which
is January 5, so it'd be the
January 6. And now we know what
to look forward to. And now I
can not worry so much and have
this pay attention. I know what
needs to be done.
And we'll see if that happens.
We'll see if that happens. Very
I do not like the idea of
Sydney.
Miss Sydney, telling people not
to vote in the runoff in
Georgia. I really don't like the
idea. And luckily there's no
she's not she's not working for
the for the President. I don't
even know if she's a member of
the republican party. That I'm
just saying she's represents
herself is working for the
President. Even though she's not
a she represents a certain side
of the of the argument your
side. And I think it's
irresponsible for her to say
that because I think that that
election will be carefully
monitored, and probably be much
more legitimate than the
original. And I think these
people shouldn't be discouraged
from voting because this is more
important than anything else
going on is making sure that one
of those two people win a senate
seat, especially against the two
creeps are running against
names. And in particular, that
guy, the light guy that's
running against the republican
is an outrageous, beta O'Rourke
level creep. And he needs to not
win one correction. I, Sidney
Powell does not represent my
side, you really need to stop
that I represent on his show.
That's exactly exactly what my
saying it constantly just does
exactly what you said. You said,
Sidney Powell said it once. I
will not say it again. But she
is in my opinion.
representing your side I guess
I'm wrong. I don't know what I'm
what I you cut me off. I want to
say I on this show, I am
representing her side to make
sure at least we hear it. It's
fine if you don't like her. And
obviously it's not a very smart
thing for the for the Republican
Party for her and Lynwood to say
don't vote. Personally, I don't
give a shit. I don't care if
people vote in Georgia or not. I
would like to see this part,
just the constitutional part.
Run through. I would like to
know a little bit more. I'd like
to see the report. That is due
from
Defense Intelligence 45 days
after the election. That's what
I'd like to see. I'm interested
in that. My dog in the hunt is
elections moving forward, and
not even for me, because I don't
care. We'll be fine. We'll do
the show. We could we've taken a
vow of poverty. Maybe I'm
interested in our children to
see how they'll do. That's all.
I'm not. I'm not a rabid nut.
People who are rabid nuts on
real television, like ABC. Like
the view. The bottom line is
that the party
The President's pardon power is
really expensive. I wouldn't say
it's exhaustive. Like you can't
pardon someone from impeachment.
But there's no question. I think
that you can issue a blanket
pardon, even for crimes that,
you know, were committed, maybe
perhaps, could be that haven't
even been charged that could be
charged. So his powers pretty
exhausted. But the one thing he
can't be pardoned for would be
state crimes. He can only pardon
really for federal crimes. So I
would imagine that mark is still
open to investigation, Florida
still, Tisha James is waiting on
some of these. She really is, as
the Attorney General of New York
agian that, you know, is part in
power.
The other thing I want to
mention is that what is
interesting to me is once you
pardon someone like Michael
Flynn, that gives people
immunity. So Michael Flynn could
decide to turn against Trump and
so it's really not the best
sure. But I don't know that that
Trump has thought that through.
Now, oh, wait, wait, there's
something that happened right on
this In this segment, which, you
know, we talked about in the
last show that they have some
somehow Trump's gonna pardon his
whole family and himself. But
I've never heard this next bit
happen on the view already. But
you also have a legal note. Do
you have to wait, we have this
legal note that you're supposed
to do you need to read that?
Yeah. Okay. Yes. So we all read
it together has repeatedly Go
ahead, sonny. Trump has
repeatedly denied any
wrongdoing, saying
investigations into his conduct
in office, and his business
dealings are motivated by
politics. He has also denied
allegations of sexual misconduct
and affairs, saying payments
were a personal matter. Not a
campaign expense. I never heard
them forced to do a legal
disclaimer.
I've never heard that.
Well, I don't think anyone has
but what was the point of it?
What was I don't know there? Are
there I I know what it is.
I Trump known as a little
litigious type
A if he doesn't get back in
office, which, in my opinion, he
won't, he will sue the hell out
of it.
We'll see the way just thinking
about it now. I think it
pertains to the executive order
about misinformation. That could
be that's what there's all kinds
of elements there. That's what
I'm thinking but that was funny,
especially when they stopped in
their tracks. I have
this I think there may be a
kicker 19 seconds left.
I think it's very exciting that
you know, he can he can try to
precompile themselves federally,
but there are all these people
waiting Letitia James is waiting
with her little foot she has
patent that foot waiting for him
to make a step out because he
keeps saying he's going run in
2024 you're not gonna run if
you're in jail, my friend.
They want him in jail so bad. I
will say everybody wants it for
some reason. This is really
disturbing. I might add all my
liberal friends not only one him
in jail, but they think and they
have a little laundry list I
keep promising I'll print one of
these out of why he should be in
jail. None of them
jailable I mean, nothing like
Hillary's little violation there
was her own server which was
against the national security
laws. All right. Do you have
what is this from the lip Joe's
or just you liberal lib? tard
more than the lip Joe's? Okay.
And what what's the list? What
what? Why should he go? He's a
liar.
Okay, do not pass go go directly
to jail for lying. Right? Yeah,
he must have 30,000 counts of
lying.
It's unbelievable. That's it.
That's why
there's a laundry list but lying
Is that the right there in the
middle of it? Not the top
rather. I said but I'll read dig
up the list and read it for the
next show. The next show will
how pull out the list of a very
important person who is a
liberal
and thinks of himself as a
moderate and he's known very
somewhat devout, not somewhat,
very famous person. And he's got
this little list and he thinks
Trump should be in jail. And
it's just like the worst of the
lip Joes they should all think
he should be in jail. I mean,
one of the lip Joes is going on
about how Giuliana should be in
jail. For lying for years he
should be in jail. He's that
he's a crook is a crook. Hmm. I
it's just it's unbelievable and
I can't even get it. I do want
to play this clip though.
This is a on the damage being
done by what we just play the
damage of this questionable
election. In fact that dead I
think gore still stretch it out
longer than this, but it's not
the same.
Good
As Trump is not your right,
this is Shields and Brooks.
And of course these two guys,
they agree with each other more
than anything else. There's
hardly a debate between the two
of them. They're in lockstep
agree lockstep agreement. And
they're both Democrats, and they
both hate Trump and, and they're
in their analysis stinks to high
heaven exactly why they're on
PBS. And the analysis in this
case, Brooks makes an assertion
and then contradicts his the
assertion with actual
information. And then he admits
that he's befuddled by anything,
and it doesn't really be
funneled by everything. But
let's play this how much damage
is being done by what is going
on right now, Mark?
I can't calculate it God in
concrete terms of this a, it's
dangerous. I mean, America has
been the envy of the world.
That's been the example to bring
millions of people who are
assures a free and open
democracy where every voice is
heard, and to have the elected
leader of that nation charged
that it is not that that is
corrupt, that it's criminal, is
damaging beyond my calculation.
I just, I think I hope it's
reparable. But, you know, we
will, it'll be a while before we
find out just how much damage
has been done.
David, how, how deep is is the
damage that's being done. While
77% of Republicans or Trump
backers say the election was
stolen by fraud, according to a
Monmouth poll. A lot of those
same people don't believe in
manmade climate change. A lot of
those some people don't believe
that masks and save your life.
become detached from reality.
And under Trump paranoia has
become a style of research and
style. I wrote a column about
this a week ago. And I tried to
theorize that this derives out
of a sense of menace and threat
that people feel existentially
unsafe. And so they grasp for
conspiracy theories, because it
makes them feel powerful that
they see the truth. It makes it
feel agency, they can expose the
evil cabal. And I think there's
some truth to that, that people
a lot of people just feel very
scared economically, socially,
racially. And out of that fear
comes paranoia. But I got a lot
of emails from people like I got
one from a guy in Palo Alto. He
said the neurosurgeon down my
block believes all this stuff.
So where's his anxiety? And I'd
say, I don't know the answer to
that question. Oh, science, just
yell science. So the thing is,
he brings up this, you know,
this is the deplorables
argument. Anyone who supported
Trump was a deplorable, and
they're in a bucket, a bucket of
display marbles in this case,
Brooks says that, you know,
people feel it's the people who
feel unsafe. It's the people who
see a menace is the people who I
got there. That's your neighbor
insecure, they're scared,
they're fearful. It's just the
opposite. The people that I see
that are scared and fearful, or
the Brooks's, and the shields
and the people shaking in their
boots about COVID Yeah, that's
not the people that that support
Trump.
The people won't walk around
without a mask is not somebody
who's fearful and scared.
So he's got He can't even make
this analysis. even remotely
correct. And he's like, the main
guy, New York Times columnist.
Boom, he's on here and he admits
himself he says, I don't get it.
Why this neuroscientist?
guy I'm confused.
The neuroscientist believes this
what's going on with the world?
Yeah. You know what? He should
get a little vocal fry? Could be
editor. Yeah.
So call back. Yeah, pretty good.
We can do pretty good. Oh,
Brexit, just as we predicted,
but we predicted it a year ago
without the Rona. Yeah, it looks
like that's off now. You know,
this is supposed to be sewn up
and finalized. December 23. I'm
missing this. I missed this.
Well, so Brexit really hadn't
happened. Yes, it happened. But
the deal it was it was in name
only a bynoe. A Brexit in name
only. I just made this up. I got
to write that down by No. So
they had the mine Oh.
And but they had no deal. The
deal with the EU still had to be
finalized. And this was supposed
to be done as it needs to be
done by December 23. And it's
not getting done. So and this is
all about the trade. Brexit Tate
trade talks critical point.
Yeah, that's also that border of
Northern Ireland. That's the big
bone of contention. deal with
that Scotland waters all of this
stuff. That's not Jesse waters,
brother, Scotland waters.
Scotland waters is oil, oil and
fish.
Oil and fish fish is a big deal
for oily fish.
So we take a quick little break
and then we can get into talking
about bynoe
Briggs that was it. Brexit in
name only? No, I just came up
with I like it. I like to try.
No, we're using it by no show
name. I do have a quick bit of
entertainment showbiz news,
which I think is important,
because we've declared how I've
declared Hollywood dead. I'll
say we I think you agree.
And something very big happened
in Hollywood, which is an
extension of China.
So whether this is Hollywood,
finally, drawing the noose close
around this neck or China doing
it for them is to be determined.
But the only person who can tell
you what's going on in Hollywood
is of course, the YouTuber known
as overlord DVD. My forces
informed me that today Disney is
holding high level emergency
meetings. I was informed of this
yesterday afternoon. Then later
in the evening, I was informed
that Paramount MGM pretty much
all the studios in Hollywood are
holding emergency meetings
today. To discuss the bombshell
dropped by The Hollywood
Reporter yesterday regarding
Warner Brothers decision to
release their entire 2021 Slater
films directly on HBO max. The
article that is sent Hollywood
into a panicked tailspin was
titled Warner Brothers smashes
box office Windows will send
entire 2021 slate to HBO, Max
and theaters. The article reads.
In an unprecedented
announcement, the studio will
send 17 films, including the
matrix for the Suicide Squad and
due to its streaming service for
31 days the same day they hit
theaters. Warner Brothers is
plotting a sweeping response to
the ongoing pandemic which has
shuttered movie theaters around
the country. After announcing
Wonder Woman 1984 we'll go to
HBO max as well as theaters
December 25. The studio is laid
out a similar path for its 2021
slate amid uncertainty about
when moving going we'll get back
to normal
and informed the voices Baron
von Doom caulk.
I like that guy. He wears a you
know, he wears a mask he wears.
like a like a Transformers nose
comic. Yeah, but this is a big
deal. This is what everyone
didn't want to happen is that
one of the studios says screw it
we're putting it all online. We
don't give a crap about the
theaters take a beating and get
it over with I don't think I
don't think they can recover.
I don't know I think the studios
are gonna have to merge or
something. They're not going to
be able to survive. Ah, Disney
will buy more. Yeah, just to buy
more Disney is already a mess.
If you've ever looked at the
Disney org chart, I have a copy
someplace. It is I couldn't even
I couldn't put the newsletter.
You can't do anything with it.
It is a monster. It is a huge
it's like the map of the world
with all these different
companies and all these arrows
going every which way Disney? I
don't see how it does they can
continue to to be this monster
company that it is.
These guys, it'd be tough to
know. I know the movie business
has got to be getting the water.
Well, Tina and I met a couple
who just moved to Austin from
Brooklyn.
And the husband works at a
Disney subsidiary.
I don't want to give them away.
But he's a he's the chief
financial officer. I think he's
a he's a C suite guy for a
subsidiary that Disney purchased
a watch, you know, years ago.
And they are super conservative.
And they left Brooklyn because
they couldn't survive.
people hated them. And witches
and they'd lived there for I
don't know, 18 years. I think
they're both from one of them.
Maybe he's from the Midwest. But
I'm gonna ask about what what
the plan is because I think
we're seeing him next week or so
for another dinner.
And it's Brooklyn because they
were outspoken and you said
hello. And Hey, hello. They were
a Brit magga hat. I mean, what
did they get rousted? Well, they
rousted themselves out because I
think it was they they learned
through election of the 700
people that lives kind of in
their district or whatever it is
699 families
were all
democrats and six families.
Republican and I think that just
all of this came down on them
what Cuomo is doing and what de
Blasio and they don't even know
if they can ever sell their
house.
No, they said, we just make it
public and lived in there. Don't
buy it, you're get contaminated
with a up and left. Yeah. And
the interesting thing is that
the upper echelon of this
particular company is very
conservative, very right wing.
So we'll see how they fare under
this Disney stuff. Anyway, it's
interesting. I will bring a
report a good place. I have a
former
Hollywood executives why current
Hollywood exact along with the
former New York banker now to
deal with and we'll talk about
some more fun stuff in just a
moment. I'm gonna show my
agenda. Imagine all the people
who could do that. Oh yeah,
that'd be fun.
We do have a few people to thank
for show 1301
we already discussed Dana
Brunetti who did continue to win
9999 from
Jefferson California Jefferson
not college. It's not in
California is the new state
Jefferson. Chad McCloskey and
bovard, Texas 133 33
Bradley shell nut in Walnut of
walnut Mountain View. 131. He's
actually
just down the street from me.
James powers in Carnegie,
Oklahoma, or Carnegie, Carnegie
130 Carnegie, Michael Rohrer and
Powell Ohio
130 Christopher Tomkinson in New
Holland, Pennsylvania. 130. So
sir, no void 130 from Camp be
those people who are all
celebrating our 100 guests or
1300 episode. There's 12344
I think Bradley Sheldon that
kind of made it 131 for the gist
of it. Yeah. As a nod. Well,
1301 you know, yeah, they're
doing Peter karnowski and we'd
California 12345. I think he's
you want to send us the mug?
Somebody from weeds? Tennyson.
mugs. mugs. I didn't get any
mugs. Get your weed mug. Oh,
yes, I did. Oh, that's an old
one. Yes, of course. I got the
weed mug. Thank you. Yes.
Beautiful mug. It is a great
mug. Yeah, it's not like a
slouch mug.
Khloe, Chloe sure heart I think
what do you think in Marietta,
California. 909 big perky boobs.
She's got a happy 38th around
the center my devastatingly
handsome dilf
Phil Mr. Phil, Mr. Phil Clayton
may ring and Twin Falls Idaho is
6969 Dan's scalisi in Vernon,
Connecticut 65. Carson Grover in
Nolan's
Dan had a douchebag call out his
smokin hot wife Courtney is the
douchebag
never misses a show but never
makes a contribution and happy
anniversary, darling. Now
donate. We love this partisan
glitch pod and so do our kids.
Okay, now. Good luck tonight
with this sex.
Carson Grover.
These are $65 donors also
celebrating the 1300 episode
Carson Grover 65 from Nolan's
Ville, Tennessee, Donald de Hart
or D. Hart in Clarksville,
Tennessee. These are all 65
Laura Wilson in Kirkland,
Washington, James Palmer, in
Grand saline or sailing grand
sailing I'm sure the Texas go
podcasting Nicholas brown stead
in Chicago, Illinois, Philip
Lovett, liquid Nicolas Nicolas
needs a quick deducing as per
request.
You've been reduced.
To veggie, I'm guessing and
mullica Hill, New Jersey jersey
65 Eric Hoffman Edmonton,
Alberta 65 and that's our little
list of 65 folks. Aaron
Chamberlain in Dayton, Ohio.
He's got a birthday for somebody
who's 6060 his dad actually yep
turns nasty. Matthew derny and
Frederick's Burg Virginia, we
got a douchebag call out. He's
5432 a douchebag. Call out both
listening for years without
donating he says Brandon be
Gary M.
He appreciates the show and and
wanted to let us know. Michael
gates in Colorado Springs
colorado. 52 at Christopher
Grimm in New York City. 5150
that's Brittany's jobs. Karma
gives you that at the end
following people or $50 donors
name and location shortlist
today we didn't. It was you
know, let down after 1300 but
it's fine. Villareal Villareal
and Mercedes Texas and Justin
commence in Columbia, Missouri,
Mary Huey.
Esther Matthew Jana Zoosk in
Chicago dance Galeazzi in
Vernon, Connecticut.
Susan Lee, Parts Unknown boots
on the ground from Korea to
follow me I saw that's a great
note. Great note long little
long. will read it all right.
Yes. Review. Yes. Michael
Copeland in Rockville, Ontario
That is the old CEO from Scrum
corral.
Wait a minute. Is that really
the guy? Yeah, no. Yeah. Wait so
him with the smokin hot trophy
wife is smokin hot wife who is a
genius now you bring him in man
where to go john Where to go?
Yeah, he's not he's not hanging
in there with with a producer
but no. No
Michael Michaels donated before
Jeffrey Zimmerman and South
Euclid Ohio and Brett sir Brett
Farrell who I know where he's
from. I don't know he I think
he's an Oklahoma City if I'm not
mistaken. All these folks want
to thank them for producing show
1301 we wouldn't get it done
without you. And Justin Clements
as an additions as this is
credit this to my wife Lisa for
a birthday she's on the list for
just for today. And could you d
do her? Yes.
Been
call out her brother as a
douchebag.
Always a pleasure thank you to
these producers who gave up
their time their talent, but
here specifically their treasure
to support and produce the best
podcast in the universe Episode
1300 and one 1301 episodes and
we also want to sincerely thank
everyone who came on in under
$50 typically for anonymous
anonymity reasons, but also
something I'd like everyone to
take a look at, which is our
sustaining donations, which is
something that comes back every
week or every month you can kind
of determine that yourself.
We've got 3333 1111 1212 just a
whole bunch and to learn more
about that you can do it by
going to vote rack.org slash n a
n for the people who need it and
it seems to be several some TPP
jobs karma jobs, jobs, jobs
jobs.
You've got
karma
man December 6 already here is
the birthday list for no agenda
nation. We heard David Sir David
fuba Soto saying Happy Birthday
to Damien sibella. She is
turning 12 and Uncle Adam and
Uncle john also congratulate on
that Chloe chart says Happy
Birthday to a devastatingly
handsome husband Phil he turns
38 he's adult Justin Clements
Happy Birthday his wife Lisa
celebrating today Aaron
Chamberlain says Happy Birthday
to his dead dog he turned 60
tomorrow, sir Matt wiffen
celebrating tomorrow bearing
dirty bangs Happy Birthday to
his son Barron Alexander bangs.
who turns five tomorrow Peter
karnowski says Happy Birthday to
Nell Williams 35 on Tuesday, and
finally sir Matt wiffen says
Happy Birthday to his daughter
Victoria. And she'll be
celebrating on December 10.
Happy birthday to all of you
from the best podcast in the
universe.
Now we have no title changes,
but we have one. We have two
days and two nights it's bad.
Let me look at this list because
I've got a note here I was
there's something amiss. Well,
look, let me see.
Do I have Dame tiara? Yes. Yeah,
we got James here. Ah, good.
Jenny. We got Mike. To Mike's.
Mic check. We got it off. Mic
check. Mic check. Yeah, that's
all well, could you then give me
your sword?
Oh, sorry. Hold on.
All right. Can you get mine as
well?
theater of the mind people.
on the podium please. Jenny
maples Massey anonymous, Mike
McRoberts. And Mike from
MacCormack Ada Okita, we could
never figure it out. It doesn't
matter your name is about to
change as all of you thanks to
your support of the no agenda
show in the amount of $1,000 or
more are now not just eligible
but seated here at the round
table the no agenda knights and
dames and therefore I'm very
proud to pronounce the name
Valentine of the bluebird powder
region. Name Sierra. Reasonable
suspicious Night of the thin
blue line and sir Mike Knight of
all tradition for you.
For the ladies, we got boys and
Chardonnay we got kebabs and
Persian wine we got
bourbon ginger ale and gerbils
and
the favorite of all mutton in
Mead, go to nogen nation.com
slash brings. Give Eric the show
your deets. That's a millennial
talk for details. And that's
like your,
your 20 where you live in where
we can get to you. We can send
off your ring, your ceiling wax,
and the coveted certificate of
authenticity, that you are now a
night slash Dame fill in your
appropriate pronoun of the no
agenda show and again, thank you
all for supporting us. And
please remember to support the
show for thursday@devora.org
slash in a
Yes
The meetups have been quite busy
recently we received three
meetup reports we're always
happy to see how the slaves of
getting donation are doing out
and about as they support all
rules and go for their personal
protest.
It is known as the site formerly
is no agenda meetups calm we now
it is known as no agenda
protests.com you are going to an
official protest although
there's no triggering no
fighting no yelling just a good
time to be had by all such as
occurred in Springfield that
they're super spreader event.
This is Caleb Brinkman, aka
brickmania
coming at you live from
Lindbergh's Tavern where we are
having the Springfield super
spreader meetup.
And we're gonna pass the phone
around so Anthony chosen here
bear in the Philippines,
defending people from
interdimensional space demons.
Brittany trust Nick, here with
the human resource vessel.
Justin road here and my mom and
brother to a meet up Say hi. Hi,
Sergio Sabir kkc ro DDD him
enjoying my first weekend to
meet up. Amanda del Favre, I
have to be a dame soon if I as
one loves me.
My husband loves me. I love the
human resource vessel. If you
notice a lot of a lot of the
dames of donation refer to
themselves as a human resource
carrier vessel incubator. Kind
of somebody started that gang
some time back and picked up on
it some trend, kind of like
Bothell coming with your report.
This is sir Jared of Southbury.
His wife Stephanie and two of
our human resources, hosting the
Bothell breathe easy speakeasy.
It's like a party to serve. It's
the night of Pacific Northwest.
It's my first meetup. And the
password is orgy named Ben here.
My first meetup. It's pretty
awesome. I'm a douchebag in the
morning, this is Steven and our
whole family.
I'm 15.
I'm Hannah and I'm their mom.
In the morning
in the morning, john and Adam,
this is od international
Snohomish Washington. Epstein
didn't kill himself. Here he
voted. This is Bryce and here I
am at a genuine speakeasy just
like the prohibition days. This
is Jacqueline This is my first
ever meetup but I'm always happy
to come super spread COVID with
a bunch of people.
I hadn't heard that gag. Jeffrey
Epstein didn't kill himself but
I hear he voted that's pretty
good. Yeah. Doing
and I'm thinking we're gonna get
a Pronunciation Guide here in
the in the report from this is
the cottage country meetup in
kawarthas. Is that how we
pronounce it? Hey, Sir Richard
dullish the epicor fez There you
go. tricky words. never
pronounce properly. Sorry, great
time here in Peterborough,
Ontario, Canada.
Is Alec of the ghetto of
Toronto. Stay safe john. From
Peterborough. Carolyn Blaney
from hug story Hey, john
Fletcher.
This is called acid or sir acid
in the Camden Ian woods and the
rare encounter podcast from
cordis not cortizo. Ortiz,
Ontario. Get that right. Please,
john, everyone.
So concludes our meetup reports.
It's beautiful to see everyone
hanging out having a good time
and coming up. We haven't got a
number of this coming Saturday.
That's December 12. We got the
Houston raging super spreader
luncheon at rodeo goat we've got
the eastern North Carolina Hot
Pockets Christmas bash at two
o'clock, and that is oh David
fox is organizing that that's a
good one. Go to no agenda,
protest calm or no agenda
meetup.com to learn more.
Also Columbus, Ohio, the small
amygdala meetup at six o'clock
and Bruno's pizza restaurant,
Saturday the 12th again in New
Orleans area meetup three
o'clock at the river shack
Tavern in Jefferson, Louisiana.
And finally the Pittsburgh
Christmas party again on
December 12. this coming
Saturday, Emma bloomer is
organizing for you and go to no
agenda meetup calm to find out
exactly where if there's not one
near you It's very simple. Why
don't you make one for yourself
started no agenda meetups calm
they are like a party.
You will
be triggered
Yo, yo,
Nick get lucky today and get the
show in in under three hours.
I haven't asked Adam. Oh my
Okay.
Do I just really the rohingyas
are being
rousted from Bangladesh is the
group that was kicked out of
Southeast Asia. And Jamar that's
the guys. Yeah, me and Mario's
guys. And so they're being
rousted because? No, I guess. I
don't know. These people have
nothing but bad little their
muscles get them out. It's not
what happened being moved to an
island.
A lot of Bangladeshis are
Muslim. And so and
yeah, and here's that this is
just a little piece of this
report from Democracy Now,
ironically, that's a clue by the
way. Yeah. To the to what I want
you to answer is what's what
stands out as very odd in this
report, and Bangladesh human
rights advocates are condemning
the relocation of thousands of
Rohingya refugees to an isolated
island. hours away from the
mainland. Police Thursday's
squirted refugees who were put
on buses for the long trek from
Cox's Bazar to a port town where
they'll be put on boats on route
to Boston char Island, which is
prone to flooding frequent
cyclones and only emerged from
the ocean two decades ago, the
islands never been inhabited. To
aid workers told Reuters
refugees were pressured into
move by government officials who
threaten them or offer them cash
and exchange Human Rights Watch
called the refugees relocation
quote, nothing short of a
dangerous mass detention of
Rohingya people in violation of
international human rights
obligations.
Okay, I think I know this one. I
don't often get these right. But
this one stuck out like a sore
thumb. What is wrong with this
report?
Ready? Yeah, the island that
appeared two decades ago, what
happened to global warming
wouldn't the islands
char Island, which is flooding
frequent cyclones and only
emerged from the ocean two
decades ago.
This is from a big global,
warmest Rao on
an island, unbelievable,
emerging in the last 20 years
when they should all be sinking.
This is so off message. I mean,
this is so off message.
Let's just I do have a few
global warming, great reset
clips to go through just before
we get out. I know we're the
affiliates are getting angry.
But
Dr. Ted Ross is doing the
connecting for all of us. He of
course, is the shill from the
World Health Organization. And
we must not go back to the same
exploitative patterns of
production and consumption, the
same disregard for the planet
that sustains all life, the same
cycle of panic and neglect. And
the same divisive politics that
fueled this pandemic. The
pandemic has brought us to a
fork in the road, a fork in the
road, behind the lies the
purpose of business as usual.
Okay, the path that led us to
this crisis, the, you know, the
mason jar that you're digging
peanut butter out of or
something really reads on the
mic. So just a little bit away
from not even gonna touch that
thing again for a year. I don't
want to unmute you. I mean, in
case you have something to say.
So here we go before us lies a
new path, a path on which
nations do not see themselves as
rivals in a zero sum game. Oh,
but as fellows, travelers, with
the same aspirations, hopes and
dreams, ah, we are fellow
travelers, we say must be
nation's hopes and dreams, a
vision that affirms our common
history and our common future
that recognize we're richer for
our diversity, and that we are
more than the sum of our parts.
Our diversity is our beauty, and
even our strengths. 75 years
after its best, it's the United
Nations remains more relevant
than ever, and more essential
than ever.
What he's saying is, listen to
these guys, I have the UN
Secretary given delivering bad
news you and I want I don't want
you to do that in a way to
finish with that.
After we
Go through the New Zealand Prime
Minister because she takes the
cake. She is the number one rule
follower of the United Nations
World Health Organization, build
back better great reset
producers in New Zealand. I
would strongly encourage you to
get out while you can. This
woman is out of control. Mr.
Speaker, I think the first and
most important point to make is
that this is a declaration.
based on science science. The
United Nations Intergovernmental
Panel on Climate Change the
preeminent scientific body in
the world on this matter has
determined that in order to
avoid a situation, a disaster is
1.5 degrees Celsius rising
temperatures and beyond a rise
that would see increased risk to
human health and livelihood
civil and Reese mess drought
myths, disease, loss of lands
and homes, increased fires,
increased tropical storms, Miss
human displacement and globally
exhausted resources, then we
must act with urgency mr.
speaker to ensure global
emissions fall to net zero by
2015 means consigning our region
to a devastating reality that if
we are responsible members of
the Pacific, we cannot and will
not accept, Mr. Speaker, this
declaration is an
acknowledgement of the next
generation and acknowledgement
of the burden that they will
carry if we do not get this
right. And if we do not take
action now, as a government, we
are also announcing the carbon
neutral government program that
requires government
organizations to be carbon
neutral by 2025.
To get our own house in order,
how can we stand and take a
leadership position amongst the
private sector and least we take
the same action that we expect
of them will require government
agencies to measure and reduce
their emissions and if that
unable to achieve carbon
neutrality, they must have said,
Oh, there it is. If you can't do
it, you gotta pay. That's what
the offset means. This.
I had so much hope for people in
New Zealand.
It's just a bunch of sheep
farmers are getting hoodwinked.
hoodwinked.
20. Crap. 25. All right.
I do have I want to play for the
next show. I'm gonna tease it.
Okay. Jason Kenney. Oh, he's
great. The prime is the premier
of Alberta. Yeah. lays it into
the great reset. You don't you
don't want it you don't want to
play these now on today's Okay,
let's play. Okay, who tells it
like it? Is that what I saw?
This is almost like a podcast
he's doing. Like some somebody
is calling Shawn. He's answering
questions. Yeah, that's the
premiere. I think this is the
way to go. Just a call in show
any lead in for one?
No, but it's about the great
reset and is to conspiracy.
Everyone kind of thinks to some
sort of conspiracy and he's just
debunking that and saying that
we're not doing any of this
crap. Alright. Ricky
Butterworth, or might be Cindy
Butterworth says, Where do you
stand on the great reset the
liberals are planning on
introducing.
Well, I let me just say that
first of all, what is this great
reset?
Pure Polly of the Federal
conservative finance critic
recently raised concerns about
this and then he was attacked by
some in the media and by the
liberals for supposedly
circulating conspiracy theories.
Well, the great reset is
actually the name of a book by a
very prominent advocate of it.
It's his name is Klaus Schwab,
he sent to see I guess, he said
one to every, probably every
government leader around the
world, and close Schwab's thesis
in his book is that we should
governments and societies the
world should, quote, seize the
opportunity of the public health
and economic crisis to reimagine
the world and radically change
policies. Now, in what ways I
would describe it as a grab bag
of left wing ideas for less
freedom and more government for
more government intervention for
policies that would I think,
create massive poverty is
particularly energy policy
policies that he is advocating
so close fall, by the way, is
the president and founder of the
World Economic Forum, also known
As the Davos summit, I call it
the biggest gathering of global
hypocrites bags in history. It's
the
it's a little ski village in
Switzerland. And every I think
February,
a couple of thousand super rich
people, a lot of billionaires,
millionaires, global CEOs, and
politicians fly into Davos men
with hundreds of private
airplanes. They go into
Switzerland, and they spend a
week basically lecturing
the world including especially
working women and men, about how
they should reduce their carbon
footprint. The hypocrisy in that
crowd is is so thick you can't
even cut it with a knife. How
much power does this guy have as
the premier? He's basically a
governor like the governor get
the governor's Gavin Newsome
level? Well, pretty powerful.
Yeah, yeah, he's no slouch. Does
he also eat at the French
Laundry at the lift class
laundry, as they call it in
counter? navia? I don't know
what to do in Alberta, there
probably be a couple of cool
places in Edmonton.
Might be they're not sure. I
don't think they're shut down.
He's one of those guys. You
know, he's not
good. He's better than New
Zealand.
no comparison, this play part
two.
The hypocrisy in that crowd is
is so thick. You can't even cut
it with a knife. And so no, I'm
not going to be taking any
policy direction from Klaus
Schwab or his his ilk. And what
I find offensive Look, the so
called great reset. It's not a
conspiracy theory. It is a
actual set of concrete proposals
being advocated by some very
influential people, and
including apparently by Prime
Minister Trudeau, who's clearly
alluded to it referred to it
quoted from it, the Schwab
theory in a speech he gave to
the United Nations a couple of
months ago. So it's not a
conspiracy theory to talk about
that. Those are the folks
advocating it. And I think it's
perfectly legitimate for a
democratically elected leaders
for me to say, heck, no, we're
not going to exploit or take the
take advantage of a crisis to
advance a political agenda.
We're actually all in this
together. Like we keep saying,
then how about we focus on the
crisis on protecting lives and
livelihoods helping people get
through this?
And And how about after that,
instead of exploiting the crisis
to impose on democratic
societies a whole bunch of
social failed socialist policy
ideas? How about instead, we get
refocused on generating economic
growth, on recreating some of
the trillions of dollars of
wealth that will have been
destroyed. That restarting some
of the hundreds of thousands of
businesses that will have gone
under
of obsessively focusing on
getting the millions
10s of millions around the world
back to work. Those who have
suffered most in the COVID era
have been the poorest
around the world. And so the
notion that we would then drive
them further into energy poverty
through a close fobbs policy
agenda is I just, frankly, find
it offensive.
Very curious how this guy a got
elected and be still alive.
Well, he's in the rich province.
Okay. And it's oil rich. Ah,
birdie is for all practical
purposes. The Texas Yes, of
Canada. navia. Yes. Okay. Well,
of course, then he represents
his constituency very well. But
he might as well start learning
how to sing.
He better learn how to sing it.
Be on your free.
That's right. Everybody build
back better for someone else.
It's what they really want you
to do.
I think that's it. Yeah. No, I'm
done. I'm done. You're done.
We're all done. There is some
cool stuff to talk about on
Thursday, though. There's some
new OTG things I'd like to
discuss okie G, go and opkg also
needs to look at some of the
incoming Biden that cabinet
administration. Yes. As the
mainstream has, is shuffling us
right through there. We just
have to it's happening is what
it is. no going back should have
a betting pool on who's going to
be picked for what? Okay, we can
basically take a look at
everyone who's in Obama's
administration and figure out
where they're gonna put them.
Up next to no agenda stream.com
we've got the grumpy old Ben's
and I have a lot of submissions
but only two and a show mixes
for this show. Move the other
ones to Thursday. We have Tom
starkweather
And Noah's archetype or Rick's,
I believe is how I pronounced
it. Coming to you from
opportunity opportunity zone 33
here in the capital of Jerome
Starr state Austin, Texas team,
reason number six and all the
governmental maps. Remember us
at the vorak.org slash na until
Thursday in the morning,
everybody. Oh, Hi, I'm Adam
Curry
in from
from Northern Silicon Valley
where we're supposedly shut down
but people seem to be driving
all over the place. I'm just, we
return on Thursday right here on
no agenda, remember us in the
vortex.org slash na until then
adios mofos and such.
I am counting absentee ballots
that Biden needs to win the
vote.
And there's no poll watchers in
this room.
For more hours to scan this pie
go but I am tempted to keep by
Dan
until he gets a disease and
resign.
Wow.
suitcase filled
with printed balanced scan No.
Well, it might be a
constitutional crisis
or just some changing of some.
But either way,
some
loss.
Why?
So what I've committed Fota for
it's hiding the quiet majority
Trump has
said say
I love you, Joe.
We're gathered here tonight.
You're a very important word.
Because I like you.
I like your President Trump won,
as we said,
and then Ohio. But we will still
win.
This election was rigged. Very
simply, you will decide whether
your children will show up in a
socialist country or whether
they will grow up in a free
country
trying to convince us that we
found a lot of balance that can
be nice.
And I felt so good. But I met
this guy and I met three of
them.
Buy a piece of machinery.
Remember that
I'm running when
I don't run the election. I
don't run to see if people are
walking in suitcases and putting
them under a table with a black
robe around
mopho.org slash and
you're like God you sound crazy.
No, no