What are you expecting? I will
run government? Adam Curry
Jhansi devora December 13 2020
this is your award winning give
a nation media assassination
Episode 13 103. This
is no agenda,
blocking the Silk Road and
broadcasting live from
opportunity's own 33 here in the
frontier of Austin, Texas
capital of the drone stars thing
in the morning, everybody. I'm
Adam Curry,
from Northern Silicon Valley
where it's never too late to
remind everybody. You can always
start journaling.
journaling for fun and profit.
Oh, man. We got a red alert
today. Red Alert. Red Alert. Red
Alert.
What's the Red Alert? Chinese
are everywhere The Chinese are
coming. The Chinese are here
everywhere. We
know that
they're taking over. Oh, yeah. I
am enjoying the show everything
China this morning now exposed
worldwide.
Who's the guy who did that
little jiggle force? Download
did this and Wow. I can't get to
tune. So subs, China. I love
China. There's a we have a
jingle here.
I've left China, I don't know.
We'll have to we need it. We
need a china jingle. Because now
we have breaking news coming out
of Australia, home to one of our
Five Eyes friends. So
tonight, I sat with some
breaking news that will be
fanpage of the Australian
tomorrow. And big news in the UK
as well, amid rising tensions in
the Australia China
relationship. There is now been
a major leak of official records
from the Chinese Communist
Party, it is believed to be the
first leak of its kind in the
world register with the details
of nearly 2 million Communist
Party members includes the name,
party position, birthdate,
National ID number, ethnicity,
and in some cases, even their
phone number. What's amazing
about this database is not just
that it exposes people who are
members of the Communist Party,
and who are now living and
working all over the world from
Australia to us. Okay. But it's
amazing because because it lifts
the lid on how the party
operates.
So this came in this morning,
and I immediately sent out
messages like Hey, what's going
on? And what I got back was, oh,
if you're going to send me a
message about a list, at least
send the list. Oh, wait, here I
have it for you. This list is
it's like 10 megabytes. I put it
in the show notes. And up in it.
It's hosted on Git lab. And
apparently there's a way to
translate from the characters.
Yeah, no, there is.
I wasn't able to find it that
early or this this morning. But
there are apparently Biden
administration members in there.
And this is the part that is too
funny. Biden administration
members are listed in this
database, as well as and I think
this is probably more egregious
many and up to 75,000 across the
world, who are not in China,
many of them in the US and in
companies. And they have their
own little little little fiefdom
set up inside these companies.
So here's the waiting for this.
You know what this is, you know
what this is a result of Right.
I mean, you're where this stems
from? This is this is the part
of the Trump strategy,
I think, no, this is this is the
CIA's get back policy. Remember
that about two years ago with,
like, 20 or 30?
Yeah, yes. murdered? murdered?
Yes.
12. Okay. 12 are murdered. Yeah.
This is what this is what this
is? Well,
I would want to agree the the
issue I have is that this hack
is not new. This occurred quite
some time ago. I'm talking like,
what was it after the 12?
killed? CIA?
Yes, yes. It was after the was
that 2012? I think it was right.
It
was during It was during Obama
were like 14, but it was during,
during Obama. Yeah. So yes,
definitely after that. But for
this all of a sudden to come
now. I think it's just part of a
whole bunch of things that are
coming. And of course, he we
didn't get to talk about it on
on Thursday show. But the best
part, the best part of the China
link news has got to be hunter
Biden's laptop, which suddenly
is now news again, and they're
headed mainly by Fox. And I
think that fox news. They're
probably choosing a side here
like they don't want any
implication that they might be
involved with some kind of China
and this is their way of maybe
attacking their rivals in the in
the cable news business. But
here's senator Holly. Well, we
need to get to the bottom of
what exactly is on here with
hunter Biden. And
by the way, I
hope an apology will be
forthcoming from the Biden
campaign. And from Facebook and
Twitter and all these people who
censored The New York Post turns
out, guess what the New York
Post was right. Hunter Biden is
under investigation for money
laundering for tax fraud and
involves his Chinese business
dealings I want to know is Joe
Biden involves What?
Hunter was traveling to China on
a government plane in order to
try to seek out business? Now
he's under investigation for
federal crimes for this? What
did Joe Biden know? And when did
he know what he needs to answer
questions? All of these things
fold in so nicely, that I wonder
this could also be a nice push
from an IF and that would make
sense for Fox News. The
Democrats who run Fox News, it
would make a lot of sense
because they want Joe out. They
want to have komla have her
being the sock puppet of Obama
third.
That would be ideal.
I think that's what they're
pushing for.
Well, maybe guy I do have
related to the punter thing. I
do have some super cuts that I
think are important. Okay,
I have a few of those. Well,
what do you got?
I got shoot, I got to have this
on the same seven just on a on
100. Biden's laptop when when
some of the before the laptop
was released. I but there was
all these innuendo. There's a
lot of news about hunter being
involved in all this criminal
activity. And so you ended up
with this super cut. This is
super cut a
Oh, okay.
I just want to deal, in fact,
because there is so much
speculation out there and there
is zero evidence
that hunter Biden or Joe Biden
did anything wrong here.
There is no evidence that Joe
Biden was you know, involved in
anyone, of course,
what to note that there is no
evidence that Joe Biden or
hunter Biden has done anything
wrong. I
just want to reiterate and let's
be clear for the viewers. There
is no
evidence Biden did anything
wrong. I'll
note again, because it's
important, there
is no I repeat, no, there is no
evidence that either Biden did
anything illegal.
There's been no evidence, there
was no evidence. There's
no evidence, there is no
evidence. There is not an iota
of evidence, no
evidence finding anything wrong.
Joe Biden did anything wrong.
Nobody's ever accused him that
there's no
wrong. Joe Biden did nothing
wrong. Hunter Biden did nothing
wrong.
So this is great, because now
you get everybody you also
skewer all the media and notice
Fox isn't in there.
I'm not sure. But, Dan, we have
supercut B which is after they
found a laptop with all the
evidence that they didn't have
any of this evidence before. Now
they got the evidence and here's
what they did.
Biden secret emails are really
fishy stories. The post claimed
that the emails were found
on a laptop computer that was
brought to a repair shop in
Delaware in
the spring of 2019.
The FBI is now investigating
whether those alleged hunter
Biden emails are actually
connected to a larger foreign
intelligence operation
they may be related to a foreign
foreign intelligence operation
foreign
intelligence, foreign
intelligence for an intelligence
operation. For all we know these
emails are made up
the information found on the
laptop may be part of a Russian
disinformation campaign
of a Russian disinformation
efforts
described by many intelligence
experts as having hallmarks all
the harmar hallmarks rather all
the hallmarks of a Russian or
Russian Russian disinformation,
Russian disinformation
misinformation campaigns is a
classic example of the right
wing media.
Scott Adams made a really big
stink about this, he feels that
it's incredibly scary and an
outrage that over 50 of our
current and former intelligence
officials and specialists would
lie. As you know, they they
signed that letter Oh, no, this
looks like classic Russian
disinformation. Scott somehow
was a surprised by that and be
somewhat taken aback.
Why doesn't realize that half of
these guys are Democrats. And
then the clips the third one,
which is says three instead of
see. I think this is after all
that Russian intelligence,
intelligence, intelligence.
Here's the head of the DNI, the
actual intelligence. Hearing
this he has to come out and make
a statement. Don't drag the
intelligence community into this
Hunter. Biden's laptop is not
part of some Russian
disinformation campaign. the
intelligence community doesn't
believe that because there's no
intelligence that supports that.
Yeah.
Now it's, it's very interesting
also to see who is in the
limelight and talking about it,
because this this really now
comes down to it's really more
about China that the laptop is
not even being discussed in
regards to Ukraine. Oh, no, no,
no, it's China and you wait to
see who's gonna show up on this
list. Once that gets a little
bit of traction, which I'm sure
it will, after all, it's going
to the Daily News. Who we're not
seeing is the megalomaniacs like
Adam Schiff. He's nowhere to be
seen. Which is noteworthy, but
Oh, yeah.
But that guy's into it up to his
knees. Well,
I think someone else who all of
a sudden pops up onto the scene.
And I believe that this guy was
involved with the dissemination
of the Russian or the, the
dossier, the PP dossier, because
he was working hand in glove
with Jeb Bush. And so now to see
Marco Rubio all of a sudden pop
out and excoriate swalwell. You
know, listen to it in the
context of what were you really
doing a whole because I don't
trust Rubio at all. And why all
of a sudden, Is he out there
talking? Because this is a much
assess by yourself. Would you
cook to the health?
I think, first of all, the
tremendous irony, right? Yes,
yes. There you go. He's just
saying, the irony of you be
talking about the story of Marco
Rubio.
And I think this is an example.
I mean, you know, he's now
claiming that he wants to be
treated fairly, but he, as a
member of the Intelligence
Committee was going around
telling people that the
President was an agent of a
foreign government.
And obviously, when people hear
that from someone who's on the
Intelligence Committee,
they think he must know
something, he must know
something the rest of us don't
know when in fact, that's became
a habit from a lot of people
that will go around saying,
well, there's things you don't
know that we can't tell you, but
it's bad. So a lot of that stuff
was going on, it was very unfair
to the President. I think in
hindsight, we see that it was
all not true. And so I think you
can't go around behaving that
way, and then expect that you're
going to enjoy the benefits.
Notice
how he says, in hindsight, I
guess it wasn't true, after he
was probably peddling some of
that misinformation.
So a lot of that stuff was going
on, it was very unfair to the
President. I think, in
hindsight, we see that it was
all not true. And so I think you
can't go around behaving that
way, and then expect that you're
gonna enjoy the benefit of the
download. Look, there are
legitimate questions. I'm not
accusing anyone of anything. It
is perhaps exactly the way he
says, and I hope he takes up
your invitation to come on and
explain it. But the broader
question here is there are a lot
of legitimate questions that I
think are important to answer,
just as a member of Congress to
his constituency, but in the
house, and he wants to continue
to serve in this important role.
And I'm not saying he doesn't
have good answers. I don't know.
But, but there is a tremendous
amount of irony here, obviously.
So here's the Yeah.
Now, was swalwell taken off the
Intelligence Committee committee
immediately after this was
disclosed? Not
yet. No, I think he's still a
wire. Well, you should have been
taken off immediately. Yeah. But
that's, that's all he's been.
This is a problem that no one
knows how to deal with it. And
he's pushing it ahead, pushing
it out of the way. Like, let's
just see if we can keep moving
forward without dealing with it.
Although I also, you know, you
there was the
leadership is that,
well, they're weeding it out. So
die. Dianne Feinstein, also, who
also has a china problem.
You don't need to take a cop off
the beat immediately put them at
a desk, you find something else
for him to do you don't leave
them on the Intelligence
Committee, whereas he has secret
access to or classified access
to all kinds of material.
No, my What are you expecting? I
will run government. Please.
Please,
yes. Haha. No, no,
no, this is no good.
Yeah, so I don't know why that
hasn't. But we we can only
surmise why that hasn't
happened. But there's an attack,
Dianne Feinstein is is also out.
She's being pushed out. What was
the article in The New Yorker, I
think, big article about how she
senile Chuck Schumer calling her
out. And she's she's confused
now. So we got to get rid of
her. And you've got to wonder
how does someone like that get
reelected? If if it's such
common knowledge that she
doesn't have all of her
faculties together?
She got reelected?
No. How can she get reelected?
She can get reelected? No, no,
California for God's sake. Yeah.
Yeah. Let's see who's on the
ballot. Feinstein democrat click
i-man.
And while we're on that, how
sincere is Kamala Harris and
being the vice president elect,
seeing as she still has not
given a percentage seat? Don't
you have to do that eventually,
isn't there? Isn't there?
Ever thought of that one?
Isn't there a time where you
have to kind of consider doing
that so
that you know about this? I have
an idea. Yeah.
Keep it.
Do Yeah. Why not? Is there a
rule you can't be a senator and
a vice president.
I don't know of a rule like
that. Maybe some we must have
somebody who's a constitutional
lawyer. That might give us some
insight but I'd say Just keep
it. Why not? What is the vice
president do most of the time?
Nothing? Does she could be in
the senate doing some work?
Well, the thinking is that this
current, right, you have to vote
says, Ah, no, she's gonna have
to quit.
You can't have two votes. You
can't have a vote in the Senate
and then be the deciding vote.
Right. But still, it's kind of
protocol that when you call
yourself the vice president
elect that you then give up your
senate seat so that they can
figure out who's gonna take
over. This is interesting that
she hasn't done that yet. I
don't know if that's it's an
oversight.
Well, or maybe she's going back
to my thesis that she can have
two jobs. Yeah, if the if the
republicans win the one of those
two seats in Georgia, which
you're probably going to do,
then she could do two jobs,
because she's not going to be
the head of the Senate.
Right. Okay. Yeah. So maybe
she's waiting for that. That
would make sense. I mean, she's
not gonna be a tie breaker Is
this right? Or maybe she could
be in the stance, she still is
the head of the Senate. I want
to know, she's probably working
it out with their lawyers. I
keep both jobs if I were her
back to China for a moment
foxnews pushing the China
intelligentsia meme as hard as
they can, I think kind of the,
if there's any plan or strategy,
it's like, Alright, you know,
we're just gonna do all this
China stuff cuz it hedges us
like if Trump does something and
still kind of prevails, we've
still been against it, number
one enemy. And also, look what's
happening. Everyone's talking
about China, and it's gonna make
all these other networks look
bad. And know that sky Australia
who broke this, the Daily Mail
and all these, these are all
Murdoch properties. Wall Street
Journal has a big story on it
this morning. So Murdoch is
probably the Murdock's are
probably in it for themselves.
And likely, whatever faction of
the Democratic Democratic Party
is, is not compromised, would
like to have some of these
people exposed as well,
thinking. But fox is pushing it
as anything we can get about
China, and brought in as
relevant and as relevant. I like
rebel news seems pretty good.
stuff that they do up there. The
good and Ezra had broken the
story earlier, which we didn't
get to on Thursday, about the
Kanda navy and military training
the Chinese military and this
being at the direct order of
Justin Trudeau. So he went on
Tucker and explained it.
I read this, my first reaction
was this cannot be true. Your
Prime Minister offered to train
Chinese troops in Canada. Why
would he do that?
It's a shock to Canadians to
that cold weather warfare that
you're referring to was just one
of 18 different joint projects
the Canadian Armed Forces had
with the People's Liberation
Army in 2019. Alone, Canada is
training one and two star
Chinese generals in our war
colleges were chain training
lieutenants and majors,
commanders. We're sending
Canadians over to China, we're
bringing Chinese, I think
they're not just soldiers.
They're spies as well, to
Canada. And I don't know a
single person in this country
who knew about it, but it's been
happening. And we found out
about it really by accident.
When the government sent me
freedom of information
documents, and forgot to black
them out. Or maybe frankly,
someone inside the government
wanted to blow the whistle on
this incredibly upside down
relationship. In those same
memos. You're talking about?
Trudeau, his office was
supporting China and condemning
the Trump administration, it was
upside down. It was inverted
morality. It's seeping all the
way into our bureaucracy, our
diplomacy, and they're trying to
get the military on side too.
I love this. This is this is so
interesting that all of this
pops up now, right at this very
moment when there's certainly
plenty of other things to talk
about, but also know that the
Trump administration or Trudeau
about the Chinese infiltrators
and spies.
Well, in fact, in these memos,
you can see that the Trump
administration warned Canada
that this winter warfare
training would transfer
knowledge to China that could be
used now they don't explain
would it be used to take on
wiggers in shinjang Tibetans to
fight India in the Himalayas or
even a fight us. And when the
military the Canadian military
said our American allies are our
allies are concerned about this.
Trudeau staff pushed back and
said, Is it just the Trump
administration? Or is anyone
else worried about it? So
there's an antipathy towards
America that seeps through all
these secret documents, and the
overarching goal is to let
China's President Xi Jinping
save face I want to tell you
though, Tucker, that is not the
view shared by grassroots
Canadians ever since trying to
kidnap those two civilians two
years ago today, actually,
Canadian public opinion has
hardened against China and the
last Pew poll I saw actually
says that Canadians are more
hostile to try and win American
Farm.
All right, Canada navion
brothers and sisters are going
to help us out fight the China
man.
You're gonna help us step by
what reelecting Trudeau again.
Fight the China man, you know,
we
can listen to my wife moan and
groan about Jay Inslee, the
idiot governor up in? Yeah,
Washington keeps making these
edicts, the most recent of which
was no singing.
And like, he won by a landslide
up there. He went by a
landslide. What do you bitching
about?
What is the singing have to do
with it then?
Oh, because singing transmits
COVID.
Right. And what does that have
to do with him winning by a
landslide?
Oh, no, I'm just saying when you
bitch about somebody that you
keep voting in office, and I
would say Trudeau falls into
this category. Yes. You don't
have a lot of complaining to do
now.
As it turns out, the Democratic
National Party had Fang Fang on
the payroll.
Fang Fang, who did the bang
bang? Yes.
taking her 12 $174 by bi weekly.
She's double dipping in more
ways than one.
Yes. I love these stories. It's
just like, are we completely
infiltrated by the Chinese
Communist Party? Well, it sure
seems that way. And I think it's
intended to make you feel that
way. But it may not even be that
far off. I love the Did you see
the trader trading cards that
are going around? Now? These are
cool. Yeah,
yeah,
I put some of those in the show
notes.
What do you think?
I don't know. It's just an it's
lame. Personally, I think is
lame
thought is funny. If the
question is, are those governors
who are on the trader trading
cards? Are they going to be
implicated in the database?
This hope so
that's hope something's in there
of some value. And this plays
plays right into President
Trump's I think overall plan,
have lots and lots of lawsuits.
let everybody see the the fraud
that took that took place. And I
think it's successfully moved it
from baseless to not widespread
to no evidence of widespread and
then of course, to the Supreme
Court. suit that was filed by
the state of Texas and joined by
I think 16 other states and the
president joined in. And well,
obviously cnn had something to
say about this, because even
before the Supreme Court did
look at it, we knew that it was
obviously racist.
So we reached out to Greg Locke,
the pastor,
from Canada. I'm sorry, that's
the wrong one. Damn it.
They came up with racist.
Oh, wait, it's very easy. It's
very simple. Here it is.
The President tries to undermine
democracy, and seems to identify
with insurrection. The President
has joined a lawsuit from the
Attorney General of Texas
himself under federal
investigation to try to overturn
the results of the election, he
lost the President's filing with
the Supreme Court states, quote,
our country is deeply divided in
ways that it arguably has not
been since the election of 1860.
So leave aside the circular
logic of decrying division when
he is the one stoking it, but
that reference to the election
of 1860. You know, why the
country was divided by that
election? Because Abraham
Lincoln one fairly in slave
states were pissed about that.
And they succeeded. And there
was a civil war. So by the
reasoning of the President's
crack legal team, Joe Biden is
Abraham Lincoln here. The guy
who won in the president is the
slave state, the ones who
succeeded and then the Civil
War. That's who Donald Trump is
relating to this morning, as
3000 new Coronavirus deaths were
reported overnight.
No, it's interesting. Love that
COVID kicker. Guys, it gets a
douchebag for that analysis.
There's a better analysis. Okay.
It's from the election of 1864
when the democrats try to rig
the election against Lincoln, so
I wouldn't get reelected and
just fell short.
Yeah. Okay.
That's more apt. Unfortunately.
I mean, after they, they tried
to rig the election against, I
would say George W. Bush too,
and they finally got one to work
with Nixon and Kennedy. They
rigged the election and jack
kennedy and
right well, so this is new. And
this is how long it's been going
on. And what's new is, oh,
there's gambling going on there.
Now everyone's eyes have been
awakened, because I think the
Trump platform has really
focused all of its efforts. I
know, I've been getting all the
incoming, focusing all of its
efforts on blanketing every
single alternative media show
that's out there, which arguably
is more mainstream than the
mainstream just in sheer
numbers. And the message is
China. The message is votes
stolen. Lots of corruption. Look
at all the evidence, there's
sufficient evidence. Some of it
might actually overturn states.
It's not getting its its play in
court. But I don't think that
matters at this point, based on
the strategy that I see. And of
course, there's a movement being
pushed. And it's being riled up
because just like 1864, the
President is going to need a lot
of people on his side, and
they're coming out in force. And
I think you have a couple clips
from it. So I didn't clip
anything. But I did get the
opening of the rally that took
place in Washington, DC
yesterday.
All right. You beautiful
patriots. Are you ready to
pierce the heart of darkness?
I thought that was apropos. Are
you ready to pierce the heart of
darkness?
Yeah. Does it feel good? It was
your feel good rally. And Mike.
I got one funny clip from that,
which is they had Mike lindahl
Oh, yeah, I heard about this. I
look for a clip you
found he found him that well,
yeah. It was actually a minute
48 of me. He went on for about
five or six minutes yakking
away. Yeah, but he was funny
because I didn't realize you
know, you get to see his
personality. And he was out.
They caught him out in the he
was in the audience and somebody
found hold him up, right. Yeah.
And the thing is that I got the
clip, but I apologize in advance
for the sound variation, because
it was very poorly miked. But
here's, here's Mike, they found
him out their
recent Supreme Court decision.
I got good news for everybody.
Sidney Powell, I got a text last
night. And they had nothing to
do with their when all they're
doing and they turned all of
their lawsuits to the Supreme
Court last
names and now all the fraud will
be revealed. She has all the
evidence, believe me, she's
still 100% in soy my that Donald
Trump will be our president for
four more years. We're all here
to pray today. That everything
that God opens doors, no man can
shot and that it's gonna be
amazing. We're here to get we're
praying that God gives us mercy
and gives us
the fortune what I believe is
where the greatest time where
everything's getting revealed.
And we're gonna be in the
biggest revival in history for
Jesus.
To see me have any idea about
the timeline, she expects from
the Supreme Court
Justice, just a text that she
said, Why are Kansai would be
able to tell the people that
keep the keep the whole, this is
such an anomaly in history that
nobody really knows timelines
and stuff like that. But I do
know this. I put myself I put
everything I had in the last
three weeks, financial and
everything I put that in,
because I know 100% our lecture
was stolen. Yeah, no, we can't
we we have to stand up as a
nation and we cannot. We cannot
allow this to happen. And all I
know is just just the fraud, the
machines, it's all gonna be
revealed work everybody in this
country. I don't care if you're
a Democrat or Republican.
Everyone is gonna know what they
tried to do.
Yeah, that that that I think
will happen. I know you do the
job. Well, I just want to give
you a little rundown of what I'm
seeing the GA machines, that
forensic evidence is going to be
allowed to be shown even though
it was initially locked down,
couldn't show it. And that
apparently will show some, some
differences. There's there's
other interesting things coming
out about Biden's brother in
law. The firm that he works for
stable street capital, they are
part owner of Dominion systems.
Kamala Harris's husband, Doug,
he was a partner in Lord Mark
Malloch Brown's firm, which is
biggest law firm with
representation in China. I mean,
it's just, it's all it's all
being brought to a head, and I'm
just waiting for what I think
will be the ultimate play which
at this point, I would have to
be pence stopping or delaying
the the count of the electoral
college votes. And from what I'm
understanding constitutionally,
once the Supreme Court said,
we're not, we're not a part of
this process, even though I
think arguably, they're supposed
to work on disputes between
states that they probably can
intervene with Pence, saying,
for instance, maybe says, Oh, I
want to have a, you know, simple
majority vote, whether the
alternate slate of electors
should be allowed, there's a lot
of leeway for him to do stuff.
And that's
what a lot of stuff they could
be done. I don't think anybody's
gonna be done. But that's just
my opinion. Now, the thing
that's interesting now is that
the media is getting all bent
out of shape, because the 12th
was the day that that the
Supreme Court ruled against Al
Gore. So now everything after
that it's new, his bad thing,
it's bad new history, but but
nobody wants to recognize the
fact that if you remember Al
Franken, when he was num elected
to the Senate in Minnesota, nine
months went by before that was
finalized
nine months if that was in the
presidential election
was beside the point it does
happen these jobs and could go
on, but on the 18th of December
is when when Trump Trump, I do
have to have a clip of this. You
mean
the executive order We've been
living under since 2018? That's
for decorative order. This
woman Lee Dunn, this is a lawyer
go. Yes. I saw you've seen this
skip. Yeah, it's good. Pete
talks about it. And on the 18th
is when the reports was to go
into the
well, it's no later no later
than the 18th. It was 45 days
after the election. So it could
come
at any time. You want to play
the lead done. disclose? Yes.
Yes. I think it's I think it's
very good. She
goes a little Wait, wait, wait,
what but before we do that,
since we're on the rally, I
don't want to jump away from
that. Because at the rally was
Alex Jones. Yeah, this rally was
a was a Christian rally.
It was the Jared Avenger. The
Jericho rally, I
think is what it was, yeah, the
Jericho route. And so I always
really was kind of disappointed
alex jones pandering to this
audience. You don't. If you're
talking to a Christian audience,
and you're not, you know, you
don't have to, you can talk to
them, like regular people. You
don't have to pander to them
just because they
know, he always does that. And
he uses my number one pet peeve
of Christian virtue signaling,
which Steve Bannon does, is by
saying, Well, today is the 13th
of December in the year of our
Lord 2020. That's the virtue
signaling.
pet peeve, I probably would have
caught it. I'm sure alex
jones doesn't all the time.
But I have two clips from judge
one of him pandering in this
second line, which I had to edit
way down. I was a funnier clip,
because he's got some lines in
there that are just just rich.
Well, let's play clip one.
Rockefeller,
not Bill Gates, not Barack
Obama, not Joe Biden, but Jesus
Christ. And God gave us and rose
up Donald Trump to stand against
the enemy and draw out the
enemy. So as dark as some of
these days are, understand, this
is the beginning of the great
revival before the Antichrist
comes. World Government,
implantable microchips, Satanism
is out of the open, the Bible is
fulfilled. Revelation is
fulfilled. Jesus Christ is
fulfilled. God Almighty, is in
charge.
Mighty God. Yeah,
wow, I've never heard him like
that. That's pretty.
I haven't either. I considered
it pandering and the whole thing
was like that. But I was
listening to him. And as he
could probably become a preacher
is not quite so good. I could
No, I know. But this guy, I'm
talking about the screaming can
where you blow out your lungs?
Well, just just one thing. And
one of our producers sent in a
note about the, you know, the
mark of the beast and all that.
And it also what what Jones
would just say, I think he's he
probably was talking about the
vaccine as well. And, and really
the 666 and then what is it the
the actual, this is all for the
end of times when you get the
the mark of the beast either on
your forehead or your right
hand. which is which is maybe
why Fauci is out there saying in
your arm, it's not in your hand,
not in your head. So your arm,
it's in your arm, that's where
it's gonna be good, don't worry
about it.
Let's listen to part two.
You look at the miserable
globalist. You look at people
like Bill Gates, and you look at
people like Mark Zuckerberg and
the rest of They are miserable
slaves of Satan. And we pray for
them, and hope that the Holy
Spirit can still touch their
soul. But more importantly, we
pray for President Donald john
Trump in this incredibly serious
moment. And we pray for all the
women in America with a system
trying to lie to to kill their
babies, and we say, don't kill
your babies. The enemy wants to
keep the whorehouses open and
the liquor stores open and the
Walmart's open and the targets
and the Amazons while they tell
you, the churches are not
essential. We will never get up.
We will never surrender. We will
never back down to the satanic
pedophile globalist New World
Order. And they're walking dead,
reanimated corpse, Joe Biden.
And we will never recognize him.
Trump. President Trump had zero
connection to Russians. no proof
for years investigation. With
the Biden's it's open and shut.
So I don't know who's going to
the White House in 38 days. But
I should Oh, this Joe Biden is a
globalist and Joe Biden will be
removed one way or another.
You know, he's really been on a
tear lately. And I have a little
bit of insight into what's going
on. You know, he's been on
Rogan, he had Rogan on his show.
Then he went on Tim Poole on
Friday, which was pretty over
the top. He's even through
channels asked if I would
interview him and just use
snippets. I'm like, shit, man,
we didn't have you never
listened to the show. You don't
need for me to interview you. We
play plenty of snippets. But the
the deep platforming hurt him
very, very significantly. So the
only have to the only Avenue he
has is to go on other shows. And
then you know, Garner up
interest. It's his version of a
newsletter. He's got he's got to
get his he's got to get himself
out there. And yes,
I do. I will say I will say
something in regards to that. If
he had developed his audience
from the get go outside the
system,
he'd like certain people you
know of,
yeah, there are people that have
managed to do this. They've
decided it's a slow it's a slow
process of intelligence,
slow path to peace. But yes,
it's possible.
I think it would have been
better off.
Now. Did you get anything from
General Flynn? Oh, wait,
whenever we talk about General
Flynn, we have to we have to the
bugle.
General Flynn, he was
there. So I thought it was
boring.
He was very boring. That's why I
only brought the bugle because I
was like, Alright, what are you
gonna say? And he said pretty
much the same thing that he's
always said. And then the
President did a flyby in marine
one, which. And Flynn spent a
lot of time working on that.
What I heard from my channels
about Flynn, right after the
Texas lawsuit was not taken.
Rejected is not the right word,
but on procedural for procedural
reasons were not taken up. Was
it? mF is not worried about
anything. First, he's General
Flynn, why would you be
perfect.
I will say that the reason I the
most exciting thing in that in
that rally was Alex Jones. And I
will say that his his Brea
animated corpse line
is very good. I thought
it was the best line of the
show.
As I said, it's a big show
between now and but we have, we
have the 18th. And this this is
gonna have right now we have
military all around the country,
Ford you know, devil storm,
which obviously isn't exercise,
they do it every single year.
It's very nice how it coincides
with Operation warp speed, which
is kicking off today. And, and
Monday as we come to plunge the
needle into the arm of hundreds
of millions of Americans. Who
knows what could happen? There
could be under this, but I want
to play this clip now under this
executive order from 2018. We
are in fact, under the executive
order under a national emergency
which we've been under since 911
is all kinds of national
emergencies that every president
including this one, just let me
re up that one and get to do
cool stuff, get the fly the
drones don't want to get rid of
that one. And everything that
took place in the 2018 election
when right after this executive
order was written took place in
2020. And we'll see if we get
some kind of tribunal from the
military or what's going to
happen. Here's where she from
this lead done this is she from?
But I thought she was a DC
attorney, but I'm not sure. Yes,
I know. She's an attorney.
Anyway, here's here's her.
Here's her view of the the
executive order. Hey
folks, human rights attorney
Litem this year, I want to talk
to you
a little bit.
What's the Hey folks, come on.
Hey, guys, is what it is.
Alright, guys, come on, folks.
Human rights attorney Litem this
year, I want to talk to you
today, a little bit about a
recent declaration of a national
emergency by President Trump to
deal with the threat of
interference in US elections,
and how this intersects Trump's
legal team statements in the
last 48 hours on the election
irregularities, if you will, and
what this all means taken as a
whole. So recently, Donald Trump
issued an executive order that I
was actually not familiar with,
entitled imposing certain
sanctions in the event of
foreign interference in the
United States election. In that
order, he noted that people have
the ability to interfere in or
undermine public confidence in
the United States elections.
These are direct quotes, this
ability included and I quote,
again, the unauthorized
accessing of election and
campaign infrastructure, which
was defined to include
information and communications
technology, as well as systems
used by or on behalf of the
federal government or a state or
local government in managing the
election process, which
specifically if you look at the
definitions of what this all
sort of devolves down to
includes, and I quote, again,
voter registration databases,
voting machines, voting
tabulation, equipment, and
equipment for the secure
transmission of election
results. Trump further noted
appointment come back to later
in this little piece, that
people have the ability to
interfere with elections
through, quote, distribution of
propaganda, and disinformation,
and quote, the President went on
and later paragraphs of the
executive order to state that
the, quote, proliferation of
digital devices and internet
best based communications has
created significant
vulnerabilities and magnified
the scope and intensity of the
threat of foreign interference.
And then he opined that such
constituted quote, and unusual
and extraordinary threat to the
national security of the United
States, after which he
unequivocally concluded, I
hereby declare a national
emergency.
Right. He's got a lot of leeway
under national emergency and it
all falls under the military
intelligence. So the Director of
National Intelligence will give
us a full load down sometime
this week. I don't think we have
to wait until the 18th.
It'll be on the 18th is my
prediction. Um,
whatever it is, the President is
definitely riling up magga
country to be at the ready to
fight for him. This is I think
this is much more serious than I
think certainly you think
because it tears are going to
come and we will see some
attempt at trials, tribunals
some attempted arresting people,
again, it'll all be tied back to
China to the illegal voting and
we'll all be done under this
executive order. And it's going
to get crazy. I can I can feel
it happening.
I know. Well, maybe
you can feel it in Texas. I sure
don't feel it here.
Well, no. What? Hello, did you
not see where we want to kick
you out of the country? We were
creating our own country over
here, son and we don't need you.
If you would take in the clue
and the cue from your fellow
Californians and moved here.
Holy crap. We just got Oracle.
We got Oracle. We got Hewlett
Packard. We got Tesla. Oh, my
goodness. What's left? You get
all the
crap a lot. All the Google for
one.
Yeah. Well, apples got a big
campus here. You've got all the
latest flying saucer that
landed? Oh, no.
Well, congratulate
Congratulations. You've got it
there. Well, I'm certainly
hoping that the President
prevails. Because if there's one
thing Well, there's a couple
things we've been called
throughout the past five years,
the worst of which is
Republicans, which I find very
insulting when someone calls us
Republicans. But the overall
it's very and so I've never
belonged the worst ever. Well,
I have been I will say I'm going
to repeat for the new listeners,
because there's always two or
three of them. I began my whole
life as a Democrat. I was raised
as a Democrat and I was raised
in a Democrat. I was a Democrat.
Pretty much. My earliest career
as a working person, I became I
became a Republican. during the
Reagan administration, I did not
think Jimmy Carter was a good
president, I thought that I
decided the democrats were a
bunch of people that botched
everything, and then became
republican and it was republican
for, I don't know, 10 years or
longer or 1516. And then I
decided that the Republican
Party's a bunch of douchebags,
too. And so I became an
independent, and then I
registered as an independent and
stayed as such until I realized
that you can be something as
even beyond independent, non
affiliated Yes, that's what I am
today, is it?
Is it unaffiliated or non
affiliated?
I think it's unaffiliated, but
I'm also like, non affiliate, so
just a bit more dramatic.
I've never belong to any
political party. I don't I just
not
all of them share peace or
freedom. Now, I consider myself
a libertarian after I
think that's, yeah, I
think that's just that's that's
a cop out. I mean, I shield for
Ron Paul.
I don't I'm not registered as
such.
No, no, I'm just saying that I
shield for ron paul in 2008. I
didn't register as a
libertarian, but I thought he
had the right idea. I was just
learning about the Federal
Reserve from him. Like, oh, so I
was, I was late, late comer a
late bloomer. But now one of the
things so we're not
Republicans.
No, but we have also been called
apologists, Trump apologists.
And this has you and me, my
friend on the list on the target
list. We have been Trump
apologists
tell you something about the 69
million people that voted for
Donald Trump. These people have
revealed themselves for the
racist that they are for the
tribalism that they are viewing.
That's every Trump voter. They
voted for this consciously
knowing what Donald Trump stood
for for the last four years.
You are being targeted, but not
because you're victims, because
you're victimizing the rest of
us. And I don't think that they
should be forgotten. And I don't
think that we should look the
other way. I think we need to
remember people must remember
and hold you to account. I do
think that people need to be
held accountable.
How much are we gonna just
let past five you cannot come
into this White House with the
idea that these people aren't
the enemy. They are
the hottest places in hell,
reserved for those who are tired
of moral crisis. remain neutral,
Shame on them. They are going to
lose way more than this
election.
We want the prisons so filled
with Trump's and Trump flunkies
and Trump apologists and Trump
enablers that we have to convert
Trump buildings into new god
damned Trump prisons. We want
enough of them in there that
they can hold reunions and
birthday parties.
This is some ugly ass talk, man.
These people are sick.
That's pretty ugly.
That is some of the most sick.
This is they're talking about
fellow Americans and then
they're supposed to be the big
igniters Oh, we're gonna unite
everybody. And this is the
rhetoric that we hear. Mm hmm.
And then we Yeah, we can be
called apologist but I want
people to pay careful attention
to this type of talk.
And this is embedded in the
system. It was it was amazing. I
found amazing interview with
Rachel Maddow on Cole bear. And,
you know, she's, of course, you
know, she is the, the mack daddy
of of cable news. And everyone
fawns over her loves her so
much. But just listen to how she
explains what her job actually
is and how it changed with the
Trump administration. She's
admitting it now that it's
coming to an end. To some
degree.
Do you have any perspective on
what it's done?
Are you asking basically did
this break me?
No. But it did it did it in some
way change your chemical
composition?
It might have changed what I am
able to digest and how I mean, I
feel like this was, I mean, this
is a great time to be in the
news business, because we've
never been more vital just to
learn these basic rules. Vital,
I am vital. I tell you, I've
never been more vital than
during this election,
and that if we didn't know them
before, you know, don't listen
to what they're saying. Just
watch what they're doing. You
know, don't don't don't take at
face value, something that you
got from a government official
just because a government
official is saying it.
How about all those people who
are familiar with the
President's thinking and sources
say Holy crap,
those rules became very easy to
remember all of a sudden again
in the Trump administration,
which is good, but they're good
rules for us for all time. I
just feel like to a certain
extent, like training to do this
work means you like learn the
rules of the road. And you learn
how to operate safely and you
like build up your skills, you
know, you take lessons you learn
from the best you do. It's like,
like getting a commercial
driver's license, like, I'm
going to be a big rig driver,
I'm going to be out on America's
highways, I'm going to convey
myself down that Highway in a
way that is safe for my fellow
travelers. And then you enter
into this administration, and
instead of getting your big
Reagan getting on the highway,
it turns out his bumper cars and
all the cars, what you're gonna
do all day is smash into each
other and try to hurt each
other. And that's your driving.
That's your job. Now,
I see that my job is to get in
the bumper car and go and drive
into people and hurt them.
This is the thinking.
It's a fast fitting analogy.
Yeah. But that's that's the
thinking here. It's like, oh, it
wasn't the way it wasn't the way
it's supposed to be. So I might
as well just go do the same
thing.
It's a lot more fun. psychos.
Anyway, According to NBC, Trump
is all but admitted defeat.
Tonight, a rare acknowledgement
from President Trump that he'll
soon be out of the White House
tweeting the Biden
administration will be a scandal
plagued mess for years to come.
A reference to the federal
criminal investigation of hunter
Biden's finances. Authorities
examining whether the younger
Biden violated tax and money
laundering laws in his Chinese
business dealings. Hunter Biden
says everything was handled
legally and appropriately.
President Trump has often taken
aim at Hunter Biden, but now a
new target his own attorney
general tweeting, why didn't the
DOJ report the Biden matter
before the election, all of it
as president elect Biden
announced a number of former
Obama officials for his
administration. They know how
government should and can work
for all Americans, including
former Obama National Security
Adviser Susan Rice to lead his
Domestic Policy Council, former
chief of staff for Veterans
Affairs.
I was gonna put a pool together
nooses and rice was somehow
gonna get into this
administration. It was
not formal yet but it seems like
she's in looks like she did it
who
did the hell wants her in this
administration? She's a creep.
Well, I
think if I were to guess Black
Lives Matter is mad. They're mad
because the administration is
not taking their phone call so I
think maybe it's like got him a
blacks
are really part of Black Lives
Matter. Doesn't
matter. What color did you vote
for me?
You're black.
All right in in what else could
it be to lead his Domestic
Policy Council
Domestic Policy Council on us
and
what is what is that exactly?
It's just a way to get the black
lady in.
What she gets your foot in the
door she's Ambassador next
thing, you know, Domestic
Policy Council. Let's see what
it is. Let's see what it is.
including former Obama National
Security Adviser Susan Rice to
lead his Domestic Policy
Council, former Obama Chief of
Staff Denis McDonough for
Veterans Affairs and former
Obama Agriculture Secretary Tom
Vilsack to lead that department
again. A big moment for Biden on
Monday when 538 electors will
cast their votes in all the
states to certify his victory in
the Domestic Policy Council. The
United States is the principal
form used by the President of
the United States for
considering domestic policy. All
right. Let's see who's on it.
Right now. pence bar a czar Chad
wolf.
Okay, so it's it's based
drinking,
basically the whole cabinet.
Additional participants Wheeler
from EPA Mulvaney Larry Kudlow,
okay, it's it's it's like a
drink like a Friday at Club five
to Friday afternoon club. We
have a little drink.
Yeah, Friday afternoon drink.
Yes, once a week. I just get
together what are we going to
call it well, what can we do?
What can what can we convene
that so we can write off our
drinks? Oh, my God. Oh, we had
the Domestic Policy Council.
Let's have a meeting. Ah, yeah.
Meeting meeting bringing the
drinks. If people are you know,
it's been we've been talking
about this so long about about
China and the infiltration into
the into pretty much all of our
big areas, all the ones that the
President has been made to look
like a dunce.
Of course, the media is top top
of the list, but I love
the someone sent me a couple of
sound clips from a game from a
video game. This is not even a
new game. It's the Command and
Conquer. I think this one was
the generals and it's the US
fighting against China. And just
listen to I don't know who
programmed this thing. Listen to
some of these quotes.
China has been generous.
Then there's this building the
Chinese Empire. Yeah. And then
we have big plans. I like that
one a lot. That sounds good.
I know we'll grow larger.
Mm hmm. And then there's this
one without
the protesters Get out of my
way. I'm
busy.
Don't trust
my way.
Isn't that the best one?
The best one. You just play that
routinely.
It's so good
day protesters Get out of my
way. I'm
busy.
I'm busy. That's how they think
about you. Ah, all right. So
we'll see. But I love that
Thursday will be our show day. I
hope nothing happens on show day
itself. There's so many cool
things happening this month. On
the 21st we have a rare
Christmas star occurrence, which
happens only once every it
happened 1000 years ago where
Jupiter and Venus can join in
the sky visible from Earth.
Yeah. And it will look like a
very bright star, which some say
might have been how the Star of
Bethlehem came came into play.
Yeah. And then on the 21st of
January, just some other crazy
astrologers going nuts. It's
nuts.
Excuse me. So all of this stuff
should obviously behoove Donald
Trump since it can't be the star
of Bethlehem. If he's not going
to defeat evil. Hello. so
obvious. so obvious. Yeah,
that's it?
Yes. Well, you know, I I do not
underestimate the American
public. And I think that there's
a significant portion that have
been riled up and I'm not going
to take it. And they're going
they want to see some fireworks
from this president, regardless
of the outcome. They want to see
some fireworks. And I think to
be fair about it, so do I. I
mean, we've been waiting for the
1000s of totally sealed
indictments for five years.
That's now when the over 200,000
give us one or two before you
go. If you go
one, anything but you're gonna
get nothing.
Okay? I it ain't over till it's
over. So he on the 21st on the
twin argue that pretty hard to
top. It ain't over till it's
over until the fat lady sings.
But
we shall see. Okay. And this is
really nothing left to report
other than hopefully today,
we'll have some of the names on
the Chinese Database List. I
think that's that's,
I just want those names. Who did
well, I have
the whole database. I got the
dump. It's too delicious to
believe. Oh, we need to talk
about the COVID for a moment I
watched the brand new movie came
out on December 11th overhyped
the Michael Bay produced
songbird about the COVID 23
locked down. I figured there
might be some messages in there
something that would give us a
clean a thing. Yes, I did. The
movie is a humongous piece of
crap. It is really
disappointing. I mean, yeah, it
looks great, because everyone is
locked down except people who
are immune, which is a small
group and the immunes get an A
yellow immune armband, which you
need is scanned by the
authorities. And the movie is
pretty much about a bike
messenger guy who's immune who's
fallen in love via video text
with a with a young woman. And
it's about their romance and how
he then tries to get her a
yellow badge to get her to live
free. And that's it is it and
there's no social message other
than you're going to be shipped
off to the cue zone. I kind of
like that. The quarantine zone
they called the cue zone. And,
and everything else looks like
it is now except just crap here.
So is boring. It's
very boring. It was especially
like, watch,
you actually managed to watch
the whole thing. And it was that
it was dull. I watched the whole
10 minutes I'm done with these
movies.
I watched the whole thing as a
public service. So no one else
has to spend their money on it,
please. I did I do that. I do
that. I
admire that. Yes. You can still
watch 10 minutes and tell people
not to watch it.
No, but I like going for the
full thing.
And
like to get people to whole
load.
I do like people to give the
whole load. All right, let's
talk about some bullcrap with
the COVID because it's really
getting laid on thick
everywhere.
All right, well, I have a series
of clips on the rollout dissolve
yesterday's clips.
Oh, wait, roll. Before we do the
vaccine, let's just do a couple
more situation. Awareness
because I want it the vaccine is
our Savior. So we need to save
that for the last.
Yeah, okay, you can do the thing
and now we're off the vaccine
but I should at least give you a
good idea where this is coming
from by doing this Saturday
rundown on NBC. Yes. And see we
she just wants you to play this
rundown to listen to the
difference in tone. It was
always Oh, we're all gonna die.
We're all gonna die and Trump's
an idiot and he's he won't leave
office.
Oh, drinking bleach. Yes. Okay,
UV lights. Yes. All right, DME.
Yes.
Sorry. Now the rundowns a lot
different.
Breaking News Tonight, the
moment we have been waiting for
the FDA authorizes emergency use
of a COVID vaccine, calling it
safe and effective. D day was
the beginning of the end.
And that's where we are today.
But now the unprecedented
national effort to produce and
administer the vaccine, as the
death toll hits a new one day
record. The first vaccination is
now set for Monday. We're on the
ground with UPS and FedEx as
they begin this massive
challenge delivering the most
important packages in history.
This is a monumental event. It
may be our finest hour.
Hospitals first in line to get
the vaccine, how doctors and
nurses are getting ready amid a
brutal surge in communications.
One state has just run out of
ICU beds. Supreme rejection,
the latest attempt to overturn
the
second that was great Did I hear
like a crash cart going when you
said running out like a like
someone coding in the
background. One state has just
run out of ICU beds.
Well done boys patients.
One state has just run out of
ICU beds. Supreme rejection,
the latest attempt to overturn
the election shot down by the
Supreme Court mid year report
card. We've been following these
high school students since the
first day of class their raw
emotions in this challenging
year.
With Jose Diaz balart Yeah, so
Texas is still open. Although
Mayor Adler has now announced I
think from his timeshare in
Cabo, that we could be going
into stage five we've never been
in stage five but now apparently
we're going there and that would
of course mean we have to shut
everything down which I don't
think it's going to happen he
has no leg to stand on. We went
out last night to to Verna,
which is an Italian restaurant
downtown which closed for
several months during the Rona
and they did a complete
renovation. And it's now kind of
turned in from like a just a
regular old Italian restaurant
kind of looks like an Italian
restaurant woody on the inside.
It's turned into a you know
white marble top, a hipster
hangout with the with the club
music going I mean throw some
sand on the floor and then hang
up a mirror ball and you've got
a santro pay club. It was
fantastic. But social
distancing, no. Was shoulder to
shoulder packed in this place.
No one gives a crap. The waiters
and waitresses walking around
with with mass hanging off their
chin not on the you know, under
their nose. No one cares. But
the news tells you something
different. The news is telling
you we need refrigerated trucks
for the dead. More eggs are
fall. We need refrigerated
trucks because the marks are
over silver filled with dead pus
filled bodies. And this report
is
this is second time and you did
that last show too.
Because that's how they make it
sound.
And no, I'm talking about pus
filled
Well that's because I know you
don't like it
with the end of this colony on
it because I
yeah, that's sorry I got another
one later.
Oh, by the way I got we got just
I don't want to interrupt your
train of thought. But the
apparently thing has a sister
term. You know he's saying
apparently too seemingly.
Seriously? Oh,
I don't like I would rather have
apparently than seriously Did I
say cereal?
My daughter pointed this out.
She said you guys are saying
seriously, you in particular
pointing at me. And so she
catches that she kisses me
around the house. If I'm upset
in the house, she'll call me out
which I think is great. I always
think that's what you want.
Yeah, that's
what you want. What people don't
realize that that's what you
want. But I I just keep an eye
out if I say seriously, please,
please. Okay.
Same same with me.
All right.
So in this clip which is about
Terran county in Texas, it
starts off the same way. But
then they they give away the
clue as to what is happening
here. It doesn't really have to
do with your morgues being
overfilled with dead bodies from
the infectious plague. Quite
Hello and Good evening. I'm
Steve vigor it's nine o'clock
Tarrant County is preparing for
an increase in COVID-19 deaths
are now overflow registered
refrigeration units outside its
morgue. Fox fours David from
kendry has more details from the
county judge tonight David.
a steep turn County Judge Glen
Whitley says conversations about
bringing in refrigerated trucks
outside the medical examiner's
office have been going on for
months. He says it's been a long
time since this has happened but
that it points to these times
that we are living in Tarrant
County reported 15 deaths today
it reported 13 deaths yesterday
that 15 death count today is the
highest number we have seen
since August when you take a
look at the footage we have
you're going to see these wooden
walls that are placed up at the
Medical Examiner's Office. These
are what is surrounding those
trucks. The body count at the
Emmys office is not only related
to COVID-19 but judge Whitley
says it does make up a part of
it. He also says some families
are slowing down the process of
having a body transferred from
the Emmys office to a funeral
home because they're waiting to
make funeral arrangements in
hopes that pandemic conditions
will become safer.
Hello. And that's the same
everywhere you hear this story.
The funeral homes are not really
in business people want to have
bigger ceremonies Hey, keep him
on ice for a while we want to
have everyone hang out. Oh we're
locked down can't go. But now
let's let's make it sound like
we're all going to die. Because
oh man oh so horrible.
Here is an interesting story. By
the way, it's what's really
happening is so it was like the
story we played on the last show
that woman that runs the
hospitals. There's no COVID
people in here right
now this is a pastor Greg Locke
from Tennessee, who is talking
to was a CNN report and he
thinks this this is just a bunch
of crap.
So we reached out to Greg lock,
a pastor and conservative Wilson
County Tennessee who says he has
grown his congregation by
protesting COVID control
measures.
We're not gonna close our church
ladies.
There's a lot of sincere people
that are doing their best to put
out a vaccine but that doesn't
mean I'm gonna take it. I don't
believe the government can tell
me you know when or how I can
stick a needle in my arm or my
kids arms super government
overreach. Knox's he's moved his
services outdoors,
not to limit the spread of
COVID. But to handle all the new
people
who've come
to fear.
I'm saying the sickness is real.
I'm saying the pandemic is not.
I don't understand what you mean
when I say pandemics not real.
pandemic is not real.
But what do you think a pandemic
is? Not?
Not COVID-19.
But what it is,
is,
I think we're stuck on this.
There's no pandemic COVID
what is the pandemic then?
Not what we're experiencing?
I'm 44 years old. We've not had
one of my lifetime. So I don't
know. And this is Nadia.
I love the millennial kid.
Well, you know, this is an old
news trick that was been
discussed in the past. You find
somebody with a with a kind of a
thick real country accent and
make them decide you want to
vilify? Yeah, and then you talk
to No, I'm not gonna hear
martial kick. Nobody's putting a
needle in my arm. Well, don't
you know how safe vaccines are?
Nobody's gonna put a needle and
mom I'm not new. But I mean that
dude, you get a guy like it this
is just part of the propaganda
mechanism is and it's really
shameful. It's
a redneck red herring. It's
horrible. What they do with
these people.
redneck red herring is it shows?
Yeah,
thank you trolls. Meanwhile,
over on MSNBC, there's the guy
who kicked it all off. I think
he was highly responsible.
Michael osterholm. He was the
guy that was on Joe Rogan show
in March when I was out there.
And he was telling Joe millions
are going to die. Well, he he
earned his stripes. boy. He's
everywhere. Now he gets to show
up and he's on the the the
president elect offices Advisory
Committee for the COVID and he's
got a message and it ain't
pretty. But you know, I've been
very critical of the advice for
giving people for Christmas
holidays. You know, if we expect
That we're going to get out of
this without having a big
increase in cases and
acknowledge that we're going to
have all kinds of new friends,
family members who have not been
bubbled up quarantine for 10
days to our house for Christmas.
What we're going to do is I will
guarantee you that
grandpa or grandma won't be here
for Christmas. Oh, we have to
get that kind of messy chairs.
This is our COVID year. This is
our COVID Christmas, not like
last year, and I really believe
with vaccines won't be like that
next year. But this year, if you
love your family, if you really
care about your family, we won't
have these get togethers, which
I know will be difficult,
they'll be very difficult. But
we've got to start telling the
public Exactly. You know, you
can't sugarcoat it anymore.
It's all about human life.
Yeah, yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
You know what? You know what
this guy? This guy reminds me of
this reminds me of 1999. And the
same kind of guys that were all
panicky about y2k. Ah, yes, he
sounds just like one of them.
Oh, my God, you know, we got to
do this or that we're all going
to go all of my, there's gonna
be no money. On January 1,
it's right fill up your bathtub.
There'll be no water. I remember
it. Right. I had my cash in the
freezer. I had my water in the
tub. I was a believer, I was all
in, bring it to me bring it to
me. The downside of doing the
best,
by the way, it's interesting
that they it's almost a 20 year
cycle on that y2k to this and
there was a huge stock market
collapse, around margin mean
rolling next year, you just say
and write that down.
The downside of being from the
future and doing the best
podcast in the universe is that
many of the things that people
see now, we have talked about or
played clips from or discussed
months and months ago, to see
China. It's not like we haven't
been all over that. But with
PCR, very early on analysis,
understanding the cycle count,
this is now still relatively new
for a lot of people, but also
played several clips from the
inventor of the PCR the
polymerase chain reaction
process, which is now
fraudulently been turned, I
said, we'll say fraudulently
turned into a test. Certainly
when it comes to accuracy, or
what it's really doing, or being
able to use it as a test at all.
Kary mullis. So a lot of people
are sending me the same things
we've done months and months
ago. I mean, I even came across
an email the other day, I can't
believe you haven't said
anything about event 201 you
know, so we so add, please,
before you email us that go to
Bing, it.io bi n gi t.io. And
just type in your term that you
can't believe and it's a very
good search engine, it did
parses all the show notes, all
the clips, so you can always
find what we've been talking
about, or at least was on the
docket. So Kary mullis, the
inventor of the PCR passed away
late in 2019. Sadly, he would
have been a nice voice to have
here, certainly around these PCR
bits test. And there was one
interview that he did. And this
was an AIDS HIV AIDS activist
interview because the PCR was
used to diagnose people with
HIV, and it was the exact same
people who are going to get the
Magical Vaccine, and who spent
hundreds of millions, if not
billions of dollars, coming up
with pretty much nothing. And he
talked about these guys in
particular Fauci so I wanted to
replay that everyone can hear
what the inventor of PCR said
about the credibility of Anthony
Fauci,
what is it? What What is it
about humanity that wants to go
to the all the details and stuff
and listening, you know, these
guys like bounty, get up there
and start talking to you know,
he doesn't know anything really
about anything. And I'd say that
to his face. Nothing. The man
thinks you can take a blood
sample and stick it in an
electron microscope, and if it's
got a virus in there, you will
know it. He doesn't understand
electron microscopy, and he
doesn't understand medicine in
that he should not be in a
position like us in. Most of
those guys up there on the top
are just total administrative
people, and they don't know
anything about what's going on
the bottom. You know, those guys
have got an agenda, which is not
what we would like them to have
being that we pay for them to
take care of our health in some
way. They've got a personal kind
of agenda. They make up their
own rules as they go they change
them when they want to. And they
smugly like Tony Fauci does not
mind going on television in
front of the people to pay a
salary and lie directly into the
camera. You can't expect the
sheep To really respect the best
and the brightest, they don't
know the difference. Really? I
mean, I like humans. Oh, don't
get me wrong. But basically,
there is a there is a vast the
vast majority of them do not
possess the ability to judge who
isn't who isn't a really good
scientist. I mean, that's the
problem. That's the main
problem, actually, with science,
I'd say in this century, because
science is being judged by
people. The funding is being
done by people who don't
understand it. Okay, who we
trust bouchy thought you didn't
know enough to know if Fauci
wants to get on television with
somebody who knows a little bit
about this stuff and debate him,
he could easily do it because
he's been asked, and there you
go, kind of
a damning review of Fauci as a
medical doctor sounds more like
a bag man for the pharmaceutical
industry. And it's too bad Kary
mullis is not with us today, I
would have loved to have asked
him what he thought of Bill Nye
the Science Guy, who clearly who
clearly wants to tell the
children of America what to do.
Greetings, Bill
Nye here with more on masks.
Here's a map of the United
States, the
reading shows where people are
wearing masks, and whacking
shows where people are getting
sick with Corona, I hope you can
see the fewer the mask the more
of those six. And there's a
perception that a virus can
travel through the fibers of a
mask like this red dot, because
viruses don't travel by
themselves. They travel on
droplets of spit,
and snacks not in the fibers are
tangible. So when the droplet
gets into the fibers of a mask,
it gets trapped. This is not
that hard to understand
everybody. That's why we have
rules about wearing a mask. Now
you know about rules, you pay
taxes on the whole road, but you
only get to drive on one
side at a time otherwise.
So everyone, please wear a mask.
And there's my end of show ISO
candidate drunk.
And not
I just I couldn't not bring that
to the table.
I know. You didn't say plus.
Now he didn't say that. Now, um,
Fauci is not as dumb. I don't
think as Kary mullis said in
that interview, I think Fauci is
very, very smart. He knows
exactly what he's doing. And I
have some examples of that. I'm
going to play a little slip he
made and then I would like to
get into the vaccine delivery
clips you have and then we'll
rip it all apart. So here is
Fauci. And where it was, he was
in Vermont, for some reason
doing a press conference about
the vaccine, and he of course,
trusts it. So
I would think that we trust the
FDA, they have pledged that they
will do what the science tells
them to do. So I can tell you
based on my experience, and what
I'm seeing, if there's a
vaccine, which I'm fairly
certain there will be that safe
and effective.
I for one, would not hesitate to
take it, nor would I recommend
nor would I hesitate
to recommend that my entire
family do
it so I feel good about it.
Truth wants to come out anybody?
I don't know. I would not I
would. I would not recommend
that to my family. That's the
best.
I trust the FDA. A just take one
word thalidomide. Yeah, doubt up
people.
Yeah. Well, the thing that that
most of the anti vaxxers I will
say, and I know many, what many
of them say is the problem with
Coronavirus vaccines, which they
have tried in the past. It has
always ended in disaster when
the inoculated and they've done
this with the animals. When the
inoculated then get the virus
again from the wild. They get
much sicker than they would have
been without the vaccine and the
and the animal trials were
skipped in this particular
process. And they killed all the
mink I don't know if it's
related, but it feels that way.
Hmm,
did you see this?
I'll play a clip out of the blue
which is up from my series on
the vaccine delivery. Okay. Uh,
this one I found peculiar. This
is a Dr. Torres or as our friend
Jose pronounces his doctor. Yes,
in fact, let me play the Medley
first before I even play this is
this is this is it sounds like a
nbcs move to Guadalajara. This
is. This is Dr. Torres medley of
Jose the host the the person
that's running the show today,
yesterday saying his name he
just love saying Torres and
Roland er. All right, which
which one is Dr. Torres medley.
Oh done. Okay, it's in a whole
different I'm sorry. I got it.
Senior medical correspondent dr.
john Torres joins us. Just voted
on recommendations for the new
vaccine including advice for
pregnant women. And Dr. COVID is
the CDC is now seeing exactly
how far apart these two shots
need to be. Dr. Torres, thank
you very much.
I couldn't even listen to the
report. I was so distracted by
the third is,
as the second is we actually
unfortunately a stepped all over
the second pronunciation which
he exaggerated. Well,
I want to hear it again can bc
senior medical correspondent dr.
john Thoris joins us now. Dr.
Torres, the CDC just voted was
on recommendations,
including advice for pregnant
women. And Dr. Torres, the CDC
is now seeing exactly how far
apart these two shots need to
be. Dr. Torres, thank you very
much this
Dr. Thoris. Did you like your
total last?
Did you see the the Australia
vaccine? Yeah, this was That was
good. But I know, I know what
happened. This is so tell us
yeah. Brazil. So Australia had
developed their own vaccine. It
is my belief it was an
attenuated vaccine. I don't
think it was one of these mRNA
vaccines. And we know from the
genome and the breakdown, or
we've been told what the hell do
we really know that the COVID is
a SARS cov two virus has little
bits of HIV in it, which is part
of the mechanism that uses to
deliver the protein spikes into
the system, which is also why it
makes it highly suspicious as
something that was not created
in the lab. But in order to
deliver a vaccine and attenuated
or dead virus, you've got to
have all pieces in it. And so
that means you have to have
little pieces of HIV. And lo and
behold, people started to show
up with testing positive for
HIV, which Australia says are
false positives. So and then
they stopped the whole fact.
That sounds like yes, sounds
messy to me.
Well, back to Dr. Total, as he
did say something in this. He
went on about all the stuff that
everybody pretty much knows if
they listen to any of these
reports. But he did drop this
little bomb in here, which I
thought was interesting, because
nobody's talking about this.
This is the this is during this
moment where he's saying Taurus
and Taurus over and over. This
is the Taurus report on 90 days.
Listen to this carefully.
The CDC also recommended the
vaccine even for someone who's
already had COVID, although they
could wait 90 days after getting
the disease to get the shot.
Since in those three months,
it's unlikely they'll get
reinfected with the virus.
Wow.
So that so that pay careful
attention to what he just said,
Well, I heard a couple of
things. But it sounds that if
you've had it, then you can't
get it for another three months.
But then you can get it again.
Well, wait, here's what he said,
is kind of what you said. But
what he said was that, should he
answering the question, should
people who've had COVID get the
vaccine? Now, under normal
disease theories, you would
think that if you've had it, you
don't need a vaccine? Oh,
no, no, this is everywhere. This
is everywhere. They're all
they're all saying. And I have
Fauci. I don't know if I clip
though
they're promoting taking the
vaccine, even if you had it Oh,
yeah. Then Then they say, This,
to me is extremely dubious. What
does it mean? It means it's not
a vaccine, it's a piece of crap.
That means something's amiss is
what it means. And so he says
that, well, if you've had it,
you can wait 90 days and then
get to move vaccine because
after 90 days, it's unlikely
you'll get COVID. Again, us
which Kant's that or implies
that you'll get COVID. Again,
after having it 90 days later,
which makes it what kind of what
is this? Or even after having
a vaccine?
Yes. Now, so this is very, very,
this really makes you wonder,
did you
see the surfer dude explained
the Madonna vaccine.
Yeah, you got that? Yes. It's
very good. Because what he said,
I mean, he's clearly a he's more
like a dude, let me tell you,
he's in front of a whiteboard.
And he does it in two minutes.
And he I think it's spot on. I
think he has it exactly right.
And it's worth listening to
because it's the first person
not wearing a lab coat, or I
think many went okay, I
understand what it's doing. I
don't want that our
genetic information can be
carried in three main ways. This
first begins with DNA that
encodes the blueprints to make
RNA that has the instructions to
make proteins, which are then
going to function in every cell
in our body. Now, the Pfizer and
biotech or moderna vaccines
against Coronavirus. Focus on
The second branch of this past
pathway mRNA or messenger RNA.
Now this has been used in the
past for gene therapy, or for
cancer treatment, but is now
being used for SARS COBie two,
and the Coronavirus has 29 main
proteins, but the specific
protein that's found on the
outer membrane is known as the
spike protein, which is really
important for to infect a
healthy cell. Now, what these
companies did is they looked at
the entire genetic makeup of
SARS COVID, and found the single
mRNA that encodes for the
instructions to make this spike
protein, they isolated out this
mRNA that can now be injected
into us in the form of vaccine
to make one of these 29
proteins, thus not giving us an
actual Corona virus. Now, this
mRNA is important as it's been
structured, three prime and a
five prime UTR, a coding region
and a place for the ribosome to
start.
This is literally gene splicing
what he's showing now and stop
Well,
you know, this is no different
than the explanation I gave that
nobody No,
no, no, you're right on. That's
why I, you are exactly right. He
just adds a few more
technical, more scientific, I'm
like to go ahead.
I think it's useful
and been packaged into a lipid
nanoparticle, which is critical
for it to fuse with our human
cells, not allowing the vaccine
or mRNA to now enter into
ourselves, this recruiting the
ribosomes and initiation
factors. Since this RNA looks
just like endogenous RNA that we
would make ourselves, it will
then use amino acids that we've
consumed to build the spike
protein. Now, that's when our
cells begin to say, Wait a
second. We haven't seen this
protein before.
Yeah, that's when the super
painful part comes in, or
an immune response to bring in a
macrophage to come and destroy
the cell that just got the
vaccine. But before the
macrophage destroys the cell,
it's going to remember that this
spike protein was different. It
was a foreign antigen, that it's
going to send the information to
our lymphatic system, which is
composed of B cells that are now
going to make antibodies against
this antigen and T cells, which
are now going to be on the
lookout for this antigen in the
future. So if we are newly
infected with Coronavirus, the
antibodies that we've now
produced are going to bind with
the antigen present on the
outside of the COVID-19 and
direct the Coronavirus for
destruction by macrophages
before the Coronavirus can
infect ourselves. So what
are you waiting for get in line
sounds good by the way. This is
nice or sorry?
I think this is pretty screwy to
be honest about it but if it
actually if such say it works
and most people most being the
operative word Sure. I think it
will prevent anyone from ever
getting the common cold again
well that's what they want
except it seems that it's one or
the other. I mean, how many Vax
yeah there are boosters you do
know that trillions of dollars
and cold remedies that would be
affected adversely by this
oh my goodness.
Is that been taken into account
by any of these geniuses?
Wow, that's a good point.
Because that is such well no
that's all Yeah, that's a very
good point.
I think it's it's destructive. I
think it's a destructive view. I
mean, in terms of the if I was a
shareholder in a company that
really relied on the common cold
for my my income, I would be
very concerned about the value
of that company after this. If
this thing works, let's just say
it works. Let's be on the be an
optimist. That's to say it
works. That means that all the
Coronavirus is because they all
use that Corona that those
spikes all of them should be
disabled by this unless of
course it wears off or something
which is still the part that
they won't talk about two things
one, if they've desist if the
body is all jacked up about
this, and again, the
coronaviruses are all over the
place in terms of the common
cold and other things. So it
should never really really
relent. If you continually fight
these off, it seems to me it's
not going to wear off in 90
days, like they they're fearful
of that's never been fully
explained to me. And the second
thing which when we get to these
vaccination delivery stories,
these this virus is started like
63 degrees centigrade below zero
minus 60 degrees, which is 100.
Something plus minus 100 or
more, very high, very cold. Do
they inject it cold? No.
In fact, they give you a the
they give everyone a little kit
and you have and the whoever's
administering the shot has to
dilute the frozen it has to thaw
out for I think two hours. Then
they dilute this because it's
I know they concentrate to one
yeah I don't like that either. I
don't want any kind of like
doing lab
work some dude at Walmart is
mixing my vaccine. Yeah man good
and and let's just be very
clear. This is going to be
Madonna is the one you want.
This is being signaled
everywhere. I know it's not the
one that's rolling out first,
but you do not want the Pfizer
one because I don't know China
pharmaceutical giant Pfizer and
its German partner beyond
hackers saying that hackers have
stolen data related to
development of their Coronavirus
vaccine in a cyber attack on the
European Union's medicines
regulator. The European
Medicines Agency has confirmed
they were targeted in a cyber
attack but gave no further
details and the incident is the
latest in a string of hacking
attempts against healthcare and
medical organizations related to
the pandemic response. Reuters
has previously reported on
allegations that hackers linked
to North Korea, South Korea or
Iran, Vietnam, China and Russia,
on separate occasions tried to
steal information about the
virus and potential treatments.
Pfizer and beyond tech said they
did not believe that any
personal data of trial
participants had been
compromised and had been assured
by the agency that the attack
will have no impact on the
timeline for its review, which
is due to be completed on
December 29. It was not
immediately clear when or how
the attack took place, or who
was responsible.
It noticed that she implicated
Iran, North Korea, China,
Russia, everybody and then said
well, we don't really know who
did it. But I think it did it.
It's just more messaging. It's
like no, no, it's got to be the
Madonna make it Madonna people
nothing else.
That's interesting analysis of
and and for people who are
stupid.
And this is as evidenced by the
governor of West Virginia is
there's a couple things you
should not be doing but listen
carefully.
People to vaccine reminders are
just as the COVID vaccine will
protect us from this virus and
save lives. There's no question
no question
clinical trials with 10s of
1000s of people have
demonstrated that the
vaccination is how effective and
safe these vaccines will require
will crap require to guide and
it is extremely it is extremely
important to receive but I think
he just had the vaccine
doses of this vaccine. You will
not be able to cross pollinate
one or the other. You will not
be able to take one vaccine from
the Pfizer and go to moderna and
do the other have to stay
Pfizer, Pfizer or Madonna my
gunner I could only
I could only wonder what would
happen if you took if you took a
Pfizer first and then a Madonna
next you probably grow a third
arm as well right
three months your dick falls off
and do the other you have to
stay Pfizer, Pfizer or Madonna.
Madonna Madonna.
Another end of show cat
candidates Madonna,
Madonna,
Madonna, Madonna Madonna.
And by the way,
even when you take it, you take
another one you keep the mask
on.
And again again until you and
the people who live with with us
are vaccinated. Our best defense
goes back to wearing that My
name
is famous doing the social
distancing.
And that's not over you know,
the mask is not the mask. The
mask is here to stay. Yes.
So I've got two ISO clips. So
unless magga prevails Yes.
I say this one. Oh, no. Ooh,
okay. Oh, no.
I like it.
And then met a lesbian.
Have they ever met
a lesbian?
juvenile but I it is low hanging
fruit. I'm liking it. Okay. I
don't know if
that's you want to go through
these vaccines? Yeah. Working
out or wait?
Oh, so everybody can enjoy it
all after we thank some people
is that your you're thinking?
That's what I was thinking
currently.
Hold on. Let me thank you for
your courage and say in the
morning to you the man who put
the seeds in? Well, two of them
in vaccine john C.
Well, in the morning to you Mr.
Adam Curry. Also in the morning
all ships and sea boots on the
ground feed nears, subs in the
water and all the names the
Knights out there
and we've got a whole rack of
trolls. Hey, trolls Hands up.
Let me count y'all. Let me see
how many we have 2121 Ooh,
that's a magic number is the
inverse of 1212 Which was just
yesterday, special 1212 I like
it, trolls.
That's pretty astonishing.
Good to have you all here in the
troll room at no agenda
stream.com where you can listen
to this show live on Sundays and
Thursdays, we have tons of shows
that are produced live, it's a
two for one deal, you get into
the troll room. And you can all
can listen to the same thing at
the same time, often and it's a
it's a real time stream. So at
least you're commenting on the
same thing at the same time. But
it's also just fun, go in there
and just go I'm a troll and just
run around and just say horrible
things and people will enjoy
your presence.
So what they doing there,
and if you are there, hit
everybody up and ask him for a
invite to no agenda social.com.
This is our federated social
network. It's completely open
source software. There's no
algos hiding around, it'll try
and trick you into clicking more
because you're angry, you pretty
much come in and you look at
your notifications. When you see
something you already seen. then
you're done. And then you can go
back to the top and there's
probably not going to be
anything other than pure
unadulterated signal to the
noise, no agenda, social calm.
And then we would like to thank
the artist who brought us the
artwork for Episode 13 102 1302
episodes. We titled that one the
mink road. And this was a comic
strip blogger who came back with
a vengeance after many drawings
of butts and farts. He finally
was the
bus and hold on.
Comic Strip.
Comic Strip,
comics jam,
comic strip,
comic strip blogger, he hangs
out on no agenda social.com
he submitted three or four
pieces that were all pretty
decent. We picked one. That's
pretty straightforward.
This was interesting. And it was
it was very straightforward. It
was a read Thought Bubble with
Chinese styled letters. That
said that's what g said. Now.
Apparently, Scott Adams had seen
that on his Twitter timeline
earlier in the day. And it said
he was pissed that he hadn't
come up with it himself. Comic
Strip blogger emailed me and
said, just so you know, this
joke is eight years old. So He
resurrected an old joke right on
time it fit people loved it, and
a well deserved coveted album,
art credit for Episode 13 102.
Spot on. That's how it works.
You get the low hanging fruit
steal if you have to. Well, no,
no.
It says public domain phrase
was a good phrase. And I had not
heard it, you would not heard
it.
I not heard it. I
thought it was fantastic.
And just I don't know why Scott
would be upset. I mean, there's
plenty of stuff you've done.
People do especially in chat
rooms. But 23 and G was another
one that was another or she
should be pronounced she 23. And
she Yeah, she was decent. But it
was like the art itself was a
little all over the place
looking. So that didn't work
out, um, by there was a lot of
interesting pieces. That was one
of the days where there's a lot
of I thought there's a number of
pieces that could have been
accepted. So it wasn't like a
last
No, no, no, no, we looked at a
number of them. And we had
agreement
muslin, which is simple,
straightforward was upon. It had
it had ramifications that would,
she said, had ramifications of
the swalwell controversy, which
recovered extensively in that
show.
Yeah, it had, I don't know, but
sometimes the simplest things
when and if you're using a
podcasting 2.0 compliant app,
you will see not only the
artwork we're discussing right
now flipping, buying the
chapters which you can
contribute to yourself. But Dred
Scott, who has taken on the role
of the community chapter
managers or whatever people
submit, he's managing it. He
started putting in other artwork
from the from the art generator
that pertains to the topics in
the shows but but weren't used.
And that's actually quite cool.
Because artists make artwork
based upon the things we're
talking about. In that very
episode. We choose one right
after we're done. But there's
this whole slew of things that
really go along with the topics
as now he's putting those in,
which makes it fun. We got
enough to do that with Yeah,
exactly.
It's a very fun experience. new
podcast apps calm you can find
an app that will work for you. I
like pod friend, but there's
hyper catcher and pod verse and
a whole bunch of different ones
new podcast apps, calm
and of course, something other
than Spotify.
I'm gonna make my prediction
here. Joe Rogan show will come
back on the open podcast market
within a year within each Within
a year, I don't think they I
don't think they can fill the
orders for the for the ads that
they've sold them on. I think
they need to do it. It's going
to be very hard for them to keep
their advertisers happy. So
we'll see
anyway, because of the because
of the reach just going to Yes.
And yeah,
well, you know, the podcast, the
Spotify podcast app is poor.
It's just a poor experience. And
I'm quite sure most people who
use Spotify, let's use it to
listen to music. And if they're
listening to podcasts, they
probably already use something
else. So now they're going to
have to switch back and forth
the video does not. It's my
experience with the video is not
great. And I think on features
the podcast in 2.0, will kick
everybody's ass. No Apple is
thinking of coming along with
us. But who knows they're,
they're there, I'm sure that I'm
quite sure they're going to do a
podcast plus and hire a bunch of
high end people who will make
shit no one wants to listen to.
And they'll put that behind a
paywall, because they think they
have to compete with Spotify,
which I think is the wrong
thing. They should be on the
side of the creative people, the
crazies, you know, the one that
you had in your ads? No, no, go
ahead and try and be like
Spotify. Okay, we'll keep our
40% of the market share out here
in the free on cancelable world.
And that brings us to the people
we'd like to thank for bringing
us their treasure in addition to
time and talent, because there's
no way we could be doing the
show we would be in fact
canceled if we had
advertisements or corporate
money, because that would go
away very quickly. All you have
to do is go bitch and moan to
the advertisers. And you get
canceled. That's how it works.
And we have our own
infrastructure works. It's so
easy.
It's a mechanism. It's
beautiful. Get the golf Yeah, I
don't like this guy won him off
the air. Yeah, to let me go
bitch and moan to the advertiser
calling the Sleeping Giants
kids. They'll do it for you pay
him a little bit of money
though.
about them.
Yeah, they're still active.
They're still out there. So
we've really appreciate our
producers who helped us in a
financial way. And we'd like to
thank the ones who came in
Bigley with an executive
producer, associate executive
producer credit right in the
show kind of the way Hollywood
does it.
Well, the top of the list is
Alexander Pellegrino for
$667.00. From San Diego,
California, I cannot find a note
from Alexander Pellegrino and I
cannot find it might be
something somewhere, but it's
not under the subject line
donation. So I'm just gonna have
to wait for him to come along
with something he wants us to
do. We're saying he might even
want to be anonymous, which is
really with this sort of thing.
He put something in that box on
PayPal, and some people well,
you know, you can't do on a
phone. Well, if you're gonna put
in a big donation, you know, get
to a real machine and do it that
way. If you want to be
anonymous,
now he sent via PayPal. What do
you see? He sends it through
PayPal? Yeah, yeah, no, I don't
have anything from either. Well,
thank you very much though.
Alexander Pellegrino, Mr.
Pellegrino
Mr. Green all wet.
True. Well, we
are pre watered down.
Yay. Yay. This much.
Sandra Walker's Next on the list
for $333.34 from Roswell,
Georgia. Now de Roswell, but
Roswell, Georgia. Hey, guys.
Hey, guys. Hey, guys. I've been
listening since July when I
heard Adam on the Tom Woods show
another Tom woods.
Convert good.
Another Tom Woods show. It was
perfect timing as I suddenly
found myself with much more time
on my hands due to the COVID
lockdown. I'm embarrassed. It
has taken me so long to donate.
I cashed out some Bitcoin during
the recent spike as a birthday
present. And myself which on
December 14, please add me to
the list. You're on the list, I
think. Yeah, we got a big list
today. Yeah, I wanted to share
some of my favorite podcasters
Adam and john, I appreciate you
guys doing the work exposing the
bigger picture that the M five m
seems to ignore or intentionally
cover up. Question mark. Do they
cover it up? Or do they ignore
it? I don't know.
Yes, the answer is yes.
unequivocably. He
has one of the two Yeah, I've
been called a trapper and a
conspiracy theorist since I was
a teenager in the 90s. It all
started with Art Bell on Late
Night FM radio. My friends who
used to make fun of me are now
asking for prepping advice.
While water goes
up best Do I need to save salt,
MRIs and blood clotting gauze.
I hit a few blood car. Yeah, I
think there's a good one. I had,
gosh,
I have that blood clotting.
I bet you do. I mean If you have
them in the mountain is made our
conversations so much more fun.
I don't have to worry about
saying something too far out. By
the way, this note is too long.
I want to mention that to you
prepper. Bringing the
conversation to a screeching
halt is interesting enough, I
can read it, but I've noticed
something. I wonder if you've
heard of this before, it seems
when sheeple start to step
outside the herd and look at the
bigger picture. They go through
almost a grieving process. I
think I went through this
myself. At first, they're
outraged and lose themselves in
research trying to figure
everything out. Then they tried
to share this info with others,
but no one would listen. So they
withdraw and go through a bout
of depression. Then they go so
deep down in the rabbit hole
that they are consumed with fear
and rush together their preps
after a while they become
overwhelmed, and they go and
they give up hope. Eventually
they make it back around to
being contented just sit back
and enjoy the show. is where we
come in crazy. Exactly. Bingo.
You guys seem to have a way of
making the great reset in the
New World Order funny. You know
why? Cuz it's
funny. That's why
anyways, I keep hitting my I
keep trying to hit my husband in
the mouth. Poor guy. He hasn't
taken the bait yet. However, our
three Human Resources don't have
a choice. No agenda is now
required listing in our home
school. Yes, my tweens try to
act like they aren't interested
but I catch them quoting the
message to get like I I can't
see him quoting the show all the
time. Sorry, says shown I got
lost to get propaganda talking
points. I'm sorry, show all the
time saying things to each
other. Like shut up slave. And
we're all gonna die. Even though
we don't watch you're listening.
By the way. That's the takeaway
from America's children is shut
up slave. We're all gonna die.
We're doing a good job.
Yeah, it's making it even
funnier. We don't watch or
listen to any m five m in our
home. They still managed to get
propaganda talking points from
their friends. Of course. That's
that's active friends. And that
was dangerous. Yes. Now, thanks
to the no agenda show. They get
to hear the clips from the real
news sources along with the
deconstruction It sounds so much
better coming from someone other
than mom. Yeah. Which makes my
job so much easier. Thank you a
couple of weeks ago, you joked
about broadcasting your show
over ham radio. I have recently
gotten my first radio, and I'm
studying for my technicians
license. Oh, excellent.
And you'll be
away quickly. Take a lot of the
take a lot of the tests because
you Okay, I know, it's too long
for me to give you something.
here's, here's the tip, it is
important. All you need is the
FCC practice test for this year,
it will be the exact same
questions and the exact same
answers as the real test. The
only difference is the answers
will be in a different order. So
if you can, if you can get the
practice test, which is
available online, you'll Ace it
because you'll know the answers.
It'll be it'll the answers will
be there for you.
Yeah, that's pretty much it. If
you can take the test over and
over and over again, you'll see
which ones you missed. There's
more questions available than
the ones you're going to get
true. But they do give them all
to you. All the answers are
available. All the questions are
available, they change it every
year. And you just take the test
over and over until you nail it
three or four times in a row and
just go do it.
It's kind of like the helicopter
test.
Yeah, exactly the same
license to learn how to fly.
I'm trying to Can she continues
her note, per lengthy note. I'm
trying to convince my friends to
get radios to so they will have
a way to communicate when
censorship and cyber attacks
take down the internet. We will
all need no agenda more than
ever. So I'm seriously
suggesting you figure out a way
to broadcast over shortwave and
get it going. Now it's not
possible as sort of a backup
plan in case of emergency.
Sorry, this note has gotten a
bit long. Okay. Just one more
thing to I have a question for
Adam.
Yeah,
I hear you refer to your wife as
the keeper. Yes. I always assume
that you met she was the one as
in one you decided to keep. But
with the recent talk of the
crackin keeper. I got me
thinking maybe you mean she's
your keeper as an atom keeper.
Which is it? No jingles no
karma. Just get on with the show
love in life. Sandra Walker.
Well, in fact, it is Jhansi
Dvorak who coined this phrase,
after a during our courtship
mine in Latinos, when he learned
that she is an outstanding
minimalist suitcase Packer and
immediately coined her as a
keeper. Yep. And as the
courtship continued, I
discovered there were many
reasons she is a keeper. So she
is in fact a keeper. And yes,
she also was my keeper. But not
an across the way. Yeah, I
said she's the keeper. And the
reason I you're right I forgot
the exact reason I knew I called
her that. But the reason was
because there's something about
women that know how to pack for
travel, especially when they go
to Europe. They really are rich.
They're there, you know, the
women who carry out a suitcase
the size of a refrigerator with
full giant balls of shampoo.
Those women should be dumped.
And, and and you even you
proclaim this, you gave her the
keeper tag, despite being
extremely upset that I had found
love and was not going to enable
you to live through my
escapades, vicariously as a
eligible bachelor.
Yes, there's some truth to this
too. I will I'll explain what it
was Adam was dating all these
different women and he had these
ribald tales to tell me after
the show was over, and I was
getting a kick out of it. I
thought it was it was hilarious.
And I was very disappointing
when he settled down.
And Sandra, we really appreciate
you asking that question. Stop
by anytime okay.
You've got karma.
I don't take the next one since
that was long. This is Emily
balls. 333 from Cottonwood,
California. Ah, dear john and
Adam. Just got some jingles here
for terrible terrier karma
science build back better for
someone else. This will be my
first donation but the de dushi
and executive producer credit
will go to my handsome man. His
name is Adam. It's his birthday
this Monday, so please put them
on the list he is. This donation
will also be the start of his
journey to becoming sir Lemurian
of Mount Shasta. Adam hit me in
the mouth last December when we
met but I really started
listening in earnest in March
during the beginning of the
COVID madness. Keeping small
amygdalae is a part of how we
stay together in society and
that keeps trying to tear us
apart. As someone who has always
felt overwhelmed by the super
apparent fakeness of the news. I
finally feel like I can pay
attention to what's going on
without losing my mind. One less
uninformed or under informed
millennial Yeah, you may be over
socialized though we're not sure
yet. We have to run you through
the battery of tests. Thank you
so much. Emily concludes for all
the work you do in the community
of rational minded people you
have created Well, they really
created themselves around us.
And thank you to my amazing
partner Adam for always taking
care of me and our three
kitties. With T's kitties. We
are fearless and resilient here
in Northern California Happy
Birthday to my love and Merry
Christmas to all Emily ball of
Cottonwood, California.
beyond your freedom
super
Jana Houghton in McMinnville.
Oregon's next also, it's rated
at $33 credit. Michael Riley is
the producer, please this is his
Christmas gift.
Oh,
what's a nice gift. That's
very nice. Now there's some love
happening there.
John's this executive producer.
Yep, we'll make Charles we're no
w e AR n where n are where and
he's got to be weird. What else
could it be in Chicago, a
Chicago $333. Another donation
of 333. My wife and I listened
to your show and try never to
miss an episode. We are part of
the liberal elite. Graduates of
the top MBA program work in tech
and we're surrounded by people
who parrot the headlines that
you discuss on the show. We find
it super valuable to have
counter perspective. We're
donating to celebrate my wife's
30th birthday. So Happy
birthday, Sonia. from Alex. Or
from Alex. Yeah, jingle
requests. And Alex. Do you do
She needs a D Dushan. Someday
both jobs karma. Shut up slave
note. Please enter the birthday.
She is on the list she's in
here's the best jobs,
jobs, jobs and jobs.
Let's vote for john
Carmack.
Thank you.
Where's Alex's Charles but okay.
Keith sorrow Asara loose. 333
bucks he was on.
Yeah, this is this is your wine
guy that you
you visited is the wire. She's
got the saarloos Winery down in
Yeah, yes. down south of me.
Dear john adams, thank you for
reading my note. I was excited
to be executive producer however
I can see my note read as an
advertisement rather than the
spirit that it was intended. I
apologize I'm such a douchebag
please de douche. Oh no he says
please do me No we can't
do for that. This is how you get
induced for this and it's also
that's producers can call other
producers that we don't
regularly douchey Yeah,
by the way. It was I find a plug
your winery? Yeah,
really? What's your problem,
bro?
I'm matching my donation from
last week. He continues and only
asked for you to hit my friend
Jeff. Yes, si si k in the mouth,
meaning he needs to be dished.
He's a douchebag
Oh, okay.
I guess
we can do that. I guess. Yeah.
And play. They don't eat me Bo
Jaiden for my son. The wine is
on the way. Your winemaker
friend Keith sorrow loose.
Yes. Very nice. He also
contacted me he's going to send
me some some wine as well. Good,
good. Yes. Good. Good. Yes. I'd
have to give him my actual
address. It can't send it to a
Pio box. It's
a wastage is way too valuable.
Yay.
Thank you. Okay.
And there we have Martin Vanden
Indian who is our guy in old
trashed?
Yes. molland Mark Tang. fonden
enden. Mark paying
303. Dear Professor devarakonda
right honorable ambassador to
the Netherlands. Mr. Curry. More
humor than most people imagine.
No, it's I am listening to the
show since Adam was on Joe
Rogan. Oh, this is not your
right or wrong guy. Not really a
Reaganite because I specifically
went to the episode to listen to
what Adam had to say. Oh, well
as was the whole episode.
Yes.
I lost track of Adam Adam since
the left countdown or I stopped
watching I can't remember since
then I'm a frequent listener
appreciating your media
deconstruction which is
especially helpful in these
challenging times already
donated once but I couldn't
really follow up since the
runner was severely attacking my
travel business. Ah, yes. But
now we were building back better
what possibly could go wrong? On
a serious that by the way,
that's the right voice.
Yes.
Look advisedly, go wrong. On a
serious note. The vaccine even
what I might think of it will
hopefully save my business. So
thanks, Joe. Joe got to do with
it. Wow, can I have a new you've
got pharma for building the
business back better? A TPP jobs
karma for our staff and I don't
eat me Bo Jaiden coincidentally,
just for the fun of it. Cheers
from trashed.
I think we can do that and I'll
even roll out the bill back
better for you. No problem.
beyond your free
you've got pharma.
I'm glad someone asked for it.
chiseled distinctly is next with
260 dot 60 in Maryland. Please
de douche me.
I saw this note earlier. I got a
kick out of it. I know you'll
like it. I found your show two
years ago after searching Apple
podcasts with the keywords fake
moon landing. I was instantly
hooked beautiful. I work as a
skilled Trek. Craftsman in the
Maryland DC and Northern
Virginia area that time last
year was anticipating the
starter restoration product
project at the US Capitol
Building. I was annoyed when
they postponed it because of the
impeachment. It was then
supposed to begin in mid March.
But as you will know, Corona
Hmm. Fortunately, work has been
steady in residential and
commercial construction sectors.
Unfortunately, I live in
Baltimore where the newly
elected mayor Brandon Scott has
shut down all indoor and outdoor
dining until further notice due
to COVID-19. Yeah, this caused
the city's tourism agency to
suspend its we're ready campaign
aimed at stopping the
hemorrhage. That is the
hospitality industry. Right.
Ready for what? There isn't even
in person attendance at the
Ravens games. I would be remiss
if I didn't call out Rhino
government. Larry butthole I'm
sorry, Larry butter being Hogan.
We've had him we've had clips
from him on the show. He's a
total douche for being a cuck.
During this pandemic, plan
Bowman plan democrats plan
demmick Thank you both for being
a brilliant beacon of light
during this era of extreme gas
lighting. Could you please play
you've got Corona Fauci is
wheeze followed by orange.
Love to You.
Especially
as beautiful Keith Larson in
Long Lake Minnesota nuts 250 ITM
quarterly donation, keep doing
the work Jcd I'm not a wine guy
but I took your advice in the
2016 Bordeaux and it didn't
disappoint. Up be Christmas
knees, jobs, karma
jobs,
jobs, jobs and jobs. That's
karma.
That was a big hit. I got a lot
of responses from people saying
they really have been enjoying
their 2016 Bordeaux upon your
recommendation.
Not hard to do in any one year
started to do a blanket
recommendation like that. Well,
you did it. You did it my
friend. You are missing out like
this
been my experience. You know,
I've been stunned by some of
these cheap lines I bought.
Exactly beautiful. Mike. Mike.
Sam is next on the list in San
Marcos, California. $200.33 as
we round this up, gentlemen, I
hope to get you in time for
Sunday show. I will listen live
which really happens as I
migrate from San Diego to
Central New Hampshire after
seven years of nagging my wife
to get out of this beautiful
weather. San Diego by the way is
the weather capital of the
United States. Sorry, Florida
and go back to the cold woods.
She finally jumped on board. I
don't know why she did that. All
it took was a pandemic well,
California probably helped
losing our social life
homeschooling our kids on zoom,
and too near nervous breakdowns.
If you get this in time, it
should be somewhere in Arizona
when you're reading this I we
sold everything and bought a
nine room in across from a lake
and tucked away in a quiet
little town. Oh, after we
complete our remodel, I'll send
in another donation so
shamelessly plug the end room
until now you gave me a big
bundle of karma for this road
trip. Until now. Oh, can you
give me a big bundle of karma
for this road trip and the move?
Thanks for keeping my amygdala
small cheers, Mike.
Of course. Here comes a big
bundle OTA karma.
You've got karma Good luck
with a nice trip.
Yeah, good luck with the end.
Yeah.
Take your time remodelling. Let
me tell you, Baron dirty dick
bangs of DC in Washington $200 I
had to delicious 70 Oh, would I
be and I chatted about
I was gonna say when I read this
note I was somewhat confused as
I everyone's been vitalizes like
like the toilet paper scare.
There's no more sick 2016
Bordeaux anywhere on shelves and
here. Dirty dick bangs comes in
and says he's getting 2017 and
did he get some secret advice?
Yeah, got some secret advice
2017 something you can't have a
blanket blanket recommendation
for but he has a kid Born in
2017 and he needed a wine so I
gave him one that was very
specific wine that we're
gonna keep it keep it until the
kids 21
Yeah, nice. And he also orders
in 2019 which is which is the
lunch buys which is a stunner if
you can even find it. For my
youngest Colton his birth year
this donation is to cover John's
billable hourly wage rate for
his 10 minutes on the phone to
give me the recommendation.
Adams two minutes to read cover
for john if he miss reads
anything.
I guess I'm cheap.
Outside of the show's over all
value, I felt like I had to
donate for the inside baseball
and wine value for value shout
outs to Team ABC Archer Campbell
bangs age three loves goats
Green Beret Barrett Alexander
bangs newly turned five loves
the drone takeoff sound effect.
Oh, I
wish I was ready for you. Okay,
keep going. And Colton Reed
bangs age 19 months president of
the goat scream fan club. Just
big sales karma Baron dirty dick
of DC.
Ah Where is my drone? Gosh darn
it. Don't have one. I will just
give him the
drone when you've got
a drone. Here it is. I know I
got you your dirty dick bang
kids.
thing out of here. All right?
No, that's anyway, that
concludes our list of executive
producers associate executive
producers for show 1303 right.
Yes,
it is indeed. Wow. 1303
protesters Get out of my way I'm
busy.
We really appreciate this. These
contributions from our executive
producers and associate
executive producers, you can
probably display these credits
anywhere credits are recognized.
And even IMDb, as you know will
vouch for and there's plenty
more you can point to to show
that it's for real, but also
know that you have truly helped
produce the best podcast in the
universe yet again, another
episode outside of the entire
take down canceled culture that
has become the the internet as
we push forward in our vow to
bring you the best
deconstruction of mainstream
news anywhere in our 14th year,
we plow ahead, we stand on this
hill. And we would love for you
to join us on the hill on
Thursday, because we're going to
have a lot more fun stuff to
deconstruct I just saw out of
the corner of my eye. General
Michael Flynn calling for the
President to enact his executive
order. And you know, when he
does that on the money, honey
show, it's always going to
happen. So join us on Thursday
and support the show
boomerang.org
slash and a all we
ask for is your time your
talents and your treasure. You
brought it in spades. We
appreciate it. Thank
you. formula is this. We go out
people in the mouth.
Yo, okay, vaccines, everybody.
So all the network's all
dedicating their whole shows to
promoting the back vaccine
delivery is a major, major,
major, major major. It's a it's
a greatest thing that's ever
happened to this country. Yes.
And of course, the real reason
is to get people to take these
vaccines, because who needs a
bunch of vaccines sitting there
on a cold storage forever? And I
think most people, I think the
majority of Americans will take
the vaccine, and we'll see what
happened.
And also, a big part of the
mission for this vaccine is if
it works, which I'm sure it will
95% efficacy, they will be able
to roll out vaccines for
everything that ails you,
because this is the new
messenger RNA system. So what
you got, you got a problem you
got, like a week left foot,
we'll just vaccinate you for
that. It's gene. Basically it's
gene Moto,
really a vaccination?
No, it's it's it's gene splicing
It is truly is well,
it's not true. There's no
splicing going on.
No, but they they know but they
are it's that's not entirely
true, though. Even the way the
kid explains it. They look at
the sequence and they build this
one particular messenger RNA
which I didn't call it virtual
gene splicing. Now, except
that term, but gene splicing is
done through injection of
messenger RNA.
gene splicing is done in real
time with the with a gene a
splice?
A Yeah, that's what plants you
know what neither neither of us
really know what the hell we're
talking about. Be honest.
And we're trying that we're ad
libbing our way through.
But it's doing pretty good. We
do
have clips, which
helps helps. Yes.
So let's go on and let's get all
this dramatic. And by the way,
Jose here works on the weekends.
really wants to get get into
acting.
Oh really? Okay. Oh, this guy
that's the guy.
Okay, so let's go with vaccine
delivery. Part one.
Oh, I can't wait. These are the
loading docks for tomorrow
morning. Our record rollout to
begin workers today packing
millions of vaccine doses here
at Pfizer sprawling plant in
Portage, Michigan.
Today is truly historic day. For
seven. Realize the greatest
public private partnership in
modern times.
United Airlines had already
flown in some of the shots to
the US from Belgium that
potentially lifesaving cargo
carefully transported in
sub-arctic coolers.
The first batch is 6.4 million
doses for now. Operation warp
speed is stockpiling 500,000 of
those
and splitting the rest into the
first half delivered now the
rest in three weeks. 150 45
sites expect deliveries Monday
425 on Tuesday 66 on
Wednesday, we think as early as
about three weeks from now, we
can be delivering vaccines to
all providers, as directed by
the states overnight. The FDA
authorized Pfizer's vaccine for
emergency use writing that the
known and potential benefits of
the vaccine outweigh the
potential risks are people 16
and older. Oh, notice that
16 and older said there was a
couple of things that wasn't
Jose so you'll get the drama
yet. But big dead guy with the
flat way and can to send a dress
that guy who they keep clipping
dude, the guy's a he's a guy
wearing military fatigues. cammo
By the way, keys were in combat.
Oh, this
is operation warp speed. You do
understand what's the camel for
because the military is
distributing the vaccine.
So what again, I'll ask the
question again, there's a lot of
Okay. All right. All right. Was
the doctor wearing a white coat?
And why does he have to wear
that?
The blend in.
Garbage
me. Wow.
You're very, very astute and
awake today. I like it.
Alright, it's good except to
Good evening. This
is an historic day. What
very well could be the beginning
of the end of the day, Jose. Oh,
he's fantastic. I bet he's gone
from voiceover work. The first
vaccine for COVID will be given
to Americans in less than 48
hours. The CDC today affirming
the FDA is authorization,
putting in emotion. What will be
one of the biggest logistical
challenges since World War Two.
But let there be no doubt this
war is still far from over. We
hit new records on Friday for
deaths cases and
hospitalizations. Tonight, our
correspondents across the
country are going to walk you
through every step of what
happens next.
Is it possible that he's hearing
the the boom boom, boom, boom,
boom, boom, boom, the opening
track and they just didn't mix
it in or somehow messed up. It
sounds like he's reading to some
bombastic audio track that
is missing. I don't know. I have
no idea. And we got the whole
clip.
Yeah, no. With Gabe Gutierrez in
Michigan.
FDA Commissioner Stephen Hahn
says the agency did not cut
corners. We worked quickly based
on the urgency of this pandemic.
Not because
of any other external pressure.
President Trump called it a
medical miracle.
This is one of the greatest
scientific accomplishments in
history,
but just hours earlier, he
slammed the FDA calling in a big
old slow turtle. today. Dr. Han
disputed reports the White House
Chief of Staff told him to clear
the vaccine on Friday or submit
his resignation.
The representations in the press
that I was threatened to be
fired if we didn't get it done
by a certain date is inaccurate
for now,
as Operation warp speed kicks
into high gear.
The latest projection is 40
million doses delivered by the
end of the month.
But gage joins us live from the
Pfizer plant in Michigan. Gabe
you said Pfizer is holding back
half of the supply Why?
Yeah, Jose at least initially
operation warp speed is holding
about 500,000 doses in an
emergency preserved about half
of the rest will be sent out in
about three weeks. That's to
make sure that everyone who gets
a first dose okay.
If I were running Joe Biden, you
know cuz he clearly you have to
program him. If I was running
him, I would have him out on the
tarmac near see 130 you know,
like pointing his finger. like
yeah, that's me, man. I'm doing
he should just take credit for
it. Just jump in there right now
and just pointed guys in army
fatigues loading loading the
vaccine.
They should just do it. He's too
old. He's actually I think
legitimately afraid of getting
COVID
Well, that's why he has two
masks on Yeah, he's always
doubled up.
So that none of this sort of
thing is going to work with him.
That's too bad because it's a
great opportunity. Now Trump's
gonna do it. Hello.
All right, let's go to part
three of this nutty report.
Transforming the vaccine will be
an unprecedented challenge this
massive high tech task to store
ship and track it on the way to
where
you live. In this mission. Every
second counts organ chesky
reports from the UPS worldport
air hub in Louisville, Kentucky.
Tonight shipping giants
nationwide ready to roll out
Pfizer's COVID-19 vaccine,
the next 24 hours crucial. The
first dose is moving from a
Pfizer plant in Michigan, to
FedEx and UPS hubs like Memphis,
Tennessee and Louisville,
Kentucky before going out to 636
locations nationwide. Ups mostly
covering the East Coast while
FedEx primarily covers the
world. Historic I mean, this is
a monumental event.
I believe as a company, it may
be our finest hour. Richard
Smith is the regional president
for FedEx America's covering
every domestic delivery. He says
the company is using real time
tracking to follow every vaccine
shipment from start to finish.
There is a distribution that's
essentially
broken down into different
states different metropolitan
areas, we'll go to FedEx versus
ups. But we're prepared to
deliver from anywhere to
anywhere on a time definite
basis overnight,
just as we do every, every day
out there ups using a similar
strategy, or we can be very,
very agile and how we handle any
kind of shipments coming into
local ups healthcare
president Wes Wheeler says each
box like these that went to
Canada, not only packed with dry
ice, but a Bluetooth device
tracking at sub freezing
temperature and
active location. Every time the
package hits one of our
locations anywhere in the
country, it will be able to see
it and will be able to monitor
its location. And if we get
stuck for whatever reason, we
can recover.
The one question that is not
answered in all of this.
logistics, which just sound My
goodness, have we ever seen
anything like this before? I
mean, I want to know, do we
still get our two day free
shake?
They make it go? Apparently not.
I went to the post office box.
There was nothing in there. And
by the way, when he says, Well,
if something happens, we can
recover. What is he talking
about? If you listen to at the
end of that last clip, again,
explain what he's talking about?
Well, that's
an interesting point, hold on a
second, let me just get to the
very end. They're
packed with dry ice. But a
Bluetooth device tracking its
sub freezing temperature and
active location,
every time the package hits one
of our locations anywhere in the
country. And we'll be able to
see it. And we'll be able to
monitor its location. And if we
get stuck for whatever reason we
can recover.
I guess I think what he means is
it's just they know where it is.
And if it gets stuck, because
it's tracked with some it's with
what are those things called?
The
tags. Usually they're using
Bluetooth, yes. Just
like, just like the tag. It's
just the enterprise resource
allocation tracker. Whoo. Oh,
crap. For us. It's so
impressive.
By the way, this is the whole
show, except for one little
segment at the end is pretty
much about this. And they're
dramatizing. Oh, and I have two
more clips. They're drew and
especially the last one is a
real gem. The they're
dramatizing this, and they're
really trying to I think that
all the networks are doing this
the drill like give everyone a
Oh, great to COVID thing is over
which of course, Biden's gonna
be Jenny after January 20. to
definitely be over. It's just a
it's just watching this rollout
as this amazing piece of
propaganda that is pretty much
overdue
you do you see it? Before you
play clip for Do you feel that?
Indeed, this will be over when
Bo Jaiden comes into office?
Because I don't see that? Why
would they they got a good thing
going here?
Well, they got they got it.
Yeah, I agree they have a good
thing going on the one hand, but
I think if they can dramatize
this, this vaccine ending to
this problem and get to you
know, they can't do big CEOs of
the airline companies and every
travel industry in the
hospitality industry in the
service industry, which is what
all we really do in this
country. And even the
manufacturing industry, they're
not going to put up with this
much longer. They gotta end this
and it's going to end this is
why they're dramatizing this.
This is over a January 20. It's
downhill February 1, everybody's
back in you know back not
wearing masks. Oh, no, no, no,
no, no,
no, no, no, no, we're due for
100 days of masking up. Come on,
man. Okay, well, come
on, man. You're right. There's
gonna be 100 days of mass
wearing and then it's over after
that, but it'll be over on
January 20. And the way I'm
seeing the way I'm
seeing it, the great reset is
bigger than Joe Biden. They'll
keep this running as long as
they need to until they take
care of business and really
destroy everything. Yeah,
they're
a bunch of dead gray reset guys.
Idiot. Yeah,
well, let's go with they're
pushing it man. They're pushing
it for
tonight. After 10 months of so
much despair, new light at the
end of a very dark tunnel for
healthcare workers. It comes as
a nation sites deadliest week
since April, more than 15,000
new deaths nationwide, nearly
200 hospitals capacity and
almost one third are seeing more
than 80% of ICU beds occupied
things.
This virus is so it's so serious
and people don't see it that
way.
from coast to coast hospitals
have been preparing to roll out
the vaccine for weeks. In
Phoenix, this Healthcare System
doing a practice drill in
Louisiana, Austin or health
making sure their storage unit
is ready for the nearly 10,000
doses heading their way.
Those vaccines will go
into these containers that are
cold storage. So many frontline
workers now breathing a sigh of
relief after living in fear of
contracting the virus and
passing it on to their own
families.
I've had doctors come up and
tell me I've not seen my parents
in in six months. I'm
afraid to go home.
Dr. Paul nee works at Danbury
Hospital in Connecticut, where
some 700 medical staff signed up
for the vaccine in less than 24
hours.
Yeah, ma'am.
All right, that by the way,
after they this clip went on a
lot longer, they brought in the
last of the sob stories to
people who died in a girl crying
It was really kind of did they
heartening? Did
they ask did they ask anyone?
How does it feel to have your
grandma died? Just before the
vaccine came out? Does it feel
like crap that you just missed
it that she just had to share
man
Auntie share. So disgust By the
way, so I got a new note from
one of our producers last night
about I guess one of the
hospital local hospitals is one
of our policemen, producers. He
knows who he is. The one of the
hospitals are going on strike.
Because why? Because they don't
they haven't paid
the nurses and they don't have
enough patience.
That's the real reason it seems
Yeah. Yes.
Okay. Whatever you do, just
listen to your news. It's all
true.
So let's go to the real kicker
to this whole thing was at the
end, we take a COVID moment. And
Jose gets to be as dramatic self
and do a kind of a soliloquy on
and you really tell us how
important all this is and what
we have to look forward to our
ladies
and gentlemen, NBC with Jose and
a COVID moment.
We want to take a moment to
pause and note that with this
vaccine, something truly big is
happening. Something that could
change the course of history.
achievements before. Yeah, stop.
Yes.
It started over. I didn't
realize until I just heard it
again. He's doing William
Shatner.
Oh, you didn't realize he was
acting like like, like Captain
Kirk.
I did not until this last play.
Yeah.
Because he's comparing it to the
moon shot. And apparently Star
Trek viewtiful just as real as
Star Trek, everybody who
want to take a moment to pause
and note.
While we're talking broadcasting
stuff, what is this?
We want to take?
What is that? What is this
opening sentence? Who do you
want to take? My goodness?
Do you want to take a moment to
pause and do one? Do you want
vaccine something truly big is
happening something that could
change the course of history?
We've had big scientific
achievements before
often set off with a
bang. This achievement packed in
tiny vials no less spectacular.
But now it's on us. put us in
some historical perspective.
What
is this stack up alongside?
You look over the decades at
tests of America like the world
war two effort or the moon
landing program. These things
show how well we did as a
society. And I think we were
about to see that right now, as
we see whether this vaccine
works and whether it will be
distributed to everyone. It took
25 years to develop a vaccine
for polio 12 years for the flu.
This first COVID vaccine took
just 11 months, the scientists
should be celebrated. This is
probably one of the greatest
public health accomplishments in
my lifetime.
But so too should the volunteers
10s of 1000s across the world
who rolled up their sleeves to
take their shot at helping 100
years from now historians will
look back on this year and say,
did we Americans meet our mama?
I hope they say that we did.
Oh man and you know, just like
the previous pandemic 100 years
ago, we will remember the heroes
such as typhoid Mary,
there will be a Floyd will be if
they don't remember any heroes
from any of that. Yeah, the
vaccine it's it's just as real
as the moon landing.
It's the same thing.
I gotcha.
I gotcha For a second there.
Almost many of our producers
work in health care and they are
being mandated many of them to
take the vaccine. And with this
first round of vaccines and I
have a feeling it's for it might
be for everyone. buddy who takes
this first, first plunge in the
arm, you will receive the V safe
app. And the V safe app is being
distributed to everyone who has
taken the vaccine and you'll
enter your vaccine number. And
you'll keep track of everything.
Texas hospitals are expected to
get their first doses as early
as next Monday, Travis County
hospitals will get more than
13,000 and almost 3000 more will
go to hospitals in Williamson
and Hayes counties. Today the
state announced once people
start getting those vaccines it
will use an app to track side
effects. It's called v safe,
it'll help people log potential
problems that could be sent to
the CBC. And it will also remind
them of when they need to get a
second dose about three weeks
after the first one.
Yeah, it really it reminds you
every day and every couple hours
to report in is a super painful
yet I feeling dizzy yet or
whatever, whatever it is. And I
certainly hope this works. I'm
extremely skeptical of of this
newfangled technology. And the
big problem is the people who
are skeptical these need to be
told to shut up and in the
United Kingdom whereas we know
they are ahead of us. There is a
man named Neil Basu, he is
Britain's top counterterrorism
officer. And he called yesterday
for a nationwide debate on the
introduction of new laws to
punish people who spread anti
vaccination conspiracy theories.
The he said there should be a
discussion about whether it is
the correct thing for society to
allow people to spread
misinformation that could cost
people's lives, as he responded
to concern that false claims
online would undermine the take
up of COVID-19 vaccines. Now, he
did stop short of endorsing the
idea of new laws, but as
intervention will strengthen
pressure on ministers of
Parliament to act against
conspiracy theorists making
false claims about the vaccines.
This is a real problem. You
cannot have an opinion,
scientific or otherwise, that
goes against what you're not
elected, but what your chosen
leaders have counterterrorism
cuz he's gonna call you a
terrorist a domestic terrorist,
I presume? Yeah, you can't have
that Google has now stated that
they will label or remove
anything that does not agree
with the conventional wisdom on
the vaccines, which should see a
lot of more deep platforming and
shutting down we already saw an
animated no agenda get removed,
because we use Fauci his very
own words in his own voice,
actually. But now that's, that
doesn't matter. And the big
problem, so that's in the UK,
and I'm sure we'll get to that
here. In the United States, we
have a different issue. And that
issue is is kind of twofold. And
we have a a movement, that is
telling us that because of
racism, black and brown
communities, as they're known by
the media, we just call them
places where people live, but
okay, it's black and brown
communities. And they have
suffered disproportionately.
Now, there are many reasons for
this. But according to the most
of the political landscape and
the media, it's because of
racism. And so we need to
encourage the black and brown
communities, particularly the
African American black
communities, to get on board
with the shot because you're
dying, we got to save you, you
can't save yourself, we have to
tell you where the elites, the
American black community is very
skeptical of the government,
giving them something and
singling them out for it. And
you need to look up the Tuskegee
experiments to understand what
that is where they gave a large
group of African American men
syphilis, and then told him that
they were giving him the
vaccine, you know, a cure
against it and didn't and then
just followed them for 30 years.
President Clinton wound up
apologizing for that in the late
90s. So we need to go on we need
to propagandize and what do we
do? We got to call our people
together. Let's call in the
National Urban League. This is
the most scripted, most phony,
most disingenuous thing I have
ever seen with Anthony Fauci.
But it started off with his
wife, Christine Grady, who we
have not heard from. Most people
don't realize that she is
married to him. They came in on
the zoom call from different
locations. They never said Hi,
it was never like she's my wife
or Hey baby, or Christine Grady,
just so you know. Her last name
could be Fauci, but it's not as
great No, not a mention. Not
even a wink wink. When she's
introduced Fauci is already on
camera. doesn't move. It's just
If they have no relationship
whatsoever, and she is a
bioethicist, and her job is to
approve vaccines and other
biologics in the National
Institutes of Health based upon
their the ethical nature of it.
So this is really her road show.
It's her job to get black people
in America to take this and not
be afraid of stuff that has
happened to black people taking
stuff from the government in the
past. So she's brought in and
just listen to we have a
thankful
for the work that she does. And
we thankfully you can join us
tonight. That's a great,
thank you so much, Dr.
Frederick, and good evening to
everybody. As you heard, I'm an
ethicist at the NIH. My
colleagues and I and ethicists
in many other places, are
intensively involved in thinking
about the ethics of vaccine
research, vaccine prioritization
and distribution and
utilization, the community
engagement and other things.
We're also very committed to the
ethical conduct of research,
research that respects the
dignity, the value and the worth
of all people, and certainly
including African Americans and
people of color. We look forward
very much to listening and
learning this evening. From the
comments, suggestions, and
questions that the audience
brings.
I love that when they We look
forward to listening and
learning. We really want to hear
what you have to say while we're
stuffing your brain full of
propaganda
night. Now it is my distinct
pleasure to introduce the shill
and then turn over the program
to Ambrose lane, who epitomizes
the model of informed and
principled community based
health leadership. Ambrose lane
Jr. has over 35 years of
leadership experience as an
effective organizer, and
executive organizer. Elaine is
the founder of and since 2013,
the chairman of the Health
Alliance network, DCs largest
community health advocacy group,
advocating for issues of health
equity, health policy, and
chronic disease prevention
strategy,
always noticed the equity word
in there. So he's being brought
in. He is, of course, a man of
dark skin color, because that's
what really works. And he'll
read the script till he is
also a co founder of the black
coalition against COVID.
Ambrose, over to you
over to you so much, Dr. Grady
for that introduction. And I'm
going to introduce Dr. Anthony
S. Fauci. For our audience.
So he goes into a long winded
introduction of Dr. Anthony S.
Fauci. It's so scripted. It's so
obvious what is going on here,
but just when you thought it
couldn't get even more
condescending, Anthony Fauci
comes in,
in my understanding is that that
independent monitoring board has
African American scientists on
it. In fact, he works with you
directly. I don't know if she's
on the board, but we know that
we have,
which I love. In fact, one of
them, one of them, one of them.
Now, it's singled out, one of
them works with you directly.
That is that crazy. You work
with a black person. It's just
I don't know she's on the board.
But we know that we have an
African American science that
works with you directly. So this
is a talk, you can speak about
her work, but also the how
important that is in terms of
breaking down these myths in the
in the historic trepidation,
because it's a new day, it's not
1930 anymore. I've listened
to what Fauci says he really,
let's rip
2000. This is 2020. And so the
Times have changed. And the
input of African American
scientists in this process is
much deeper than one might
think. Talk about that a little
bit. Well, I
think the example that you gave
ambros is an excellent example.
It was also the one we rehearsed
the very vaccine. That's one of
the two that has absolutely
exquisite level 94 to 95%
efficacy,
mind you, he's pointing out one
vaccine is better than the other
against clinical disease and
almost 100% efficacy against
serious disease that has shown
to be clearly safe. That vaccine
was actually developed in the in
my Institute's vaccine research
center by a team of scientists,
led by Dr. Bonnie Graham and his
close colleague,
Dr. Oz mechi, a Corbett or
Kizzy. Corbett
Kizzy is an African American
scientist, who is right at the
forefront of the development of
the vaccine
sounds more like she's the
lackey of some guy who really
did the vaccine, but Okay,
so the first thing you might
want to say to my African
American Brothers and sisters,
the vaccine in
an African American woman, and
that is just a fact.
I mean, that is the fact
that I think that's some of the
things that people don't fully
appreciate.
So, you know, even evil doctors,
as long as they're black, you
can trust him. It's good to go.
And this moderna is made in
Fauci slab I heard him say it
No, no, that was developed in my
lab and it said, and that's it.
So I wonder and I'd like to know
if what was her name the Dr.
Reza. Kizzy Kizzy and the is the
example that you gave Kizzy. Dr
Kizzy is she also cut in on the
patent? Is she on the patent or
the murder? no vaccine? I looked
I couldn't find it. So are you
shortchanging your black doctors
Dr. Fauci, that stuff that was
developed in your lab where
everyone including you is on the
patent is Kizzy on it? I didn't
see it might not be looking in
the right place. I'll be the
first to admit to these guys and
to say, so my black and my black
brothers and sisters one place
to look.
Yeah, the US Patent Trade
Office.
Yes. And that list is right at
the beginning.
So my black and brown brothers
and sisters, FSU Fauci, that's
so condescending. really lame.
So there you go. They think
that's going to work. Good luck.
Maybe, you know, it's doable to
get people to take the vaccine
if you don't do shit like that.
Yeah. Because then it gets
loose, a little suspicious. I
mean, if I was somebody who was
inclined to take the vaccine,
and I know people that are and I
was black, and I saw this, I
say, What is it? What is this
about? Why are they doing this?
This is suspicious. I think
twice about it. Very poor poor
execution.
It's it's what they always do
it. So it's also like, what was
Gil written? Yeah.
And I don't have a clip of it.
But it's the same thing I saw.
Oh, where was this someone as a
as promised that Bo? I'm going
to put in a bill and it will be
for Reparations. We're going to
have a study group. Oh my gosh,
you must love our black brothers
and sisters because you giving
them a study. This has been done
1000 times. It's all I can see
is people really think African
Americans and people as they say
brown and black communities that
they're inferior. That's how
they talk. These are horrible
people. Yeah,
that's a summarize that's
probably exactly the genesis of
the whole thing. That Yeah.
What they're just actually
racist. They're racist and
worse. They
are that same statement. That
phrase that Dutch phrase you'd
love to say what you said
being yourself, would you cook
though the health does Yakuza?
Yeah.
Yeah. I'm trying to try to
memorize the phrase.
No, it's not. It's not very
difficult to do. I heard a new
one today, which I liked a lot.
metaphor brought it down to it
takes you back on fleeced, which
is roughly translates to a
grilled dove flew right into
your mouth, which is a guest
drilled it has to be
grilled. Yes. Because
it's done. It's grilled. It
tastes good. It's it's the dove
has been cooked and it felt it
flew right into your mouth, the
grilled dove.
And what's what it was the
phrase imply that
you were looking for something
and you got exactly what you
wanted? It flew right in your
face. The grilled the grilled
dove. Man, the Dutch man they're
filled with stuff.
Where they get these little
phrases. They're
cute. Let me see these. Let me
just see them. rechecking this
patent. Are you sure it's the
one up front? Oh, here it is.
Yes.
Yeah, it would be at the
beginning now. Now there's no
kids in here unless it says at
all at the end.
Which wouldn't be no good. Oh,
they don't have an at all.
No, they usually put everyone's
name there.
They have a Justin guild from
Massachusetts, Medina, Texas, of
course. That's the assignee, the
inventor Antonin de feu gatos,
from Waterloo. Oh, that's from
Belgium. I don't know exactly
how they how they do this is
Fauci even on the list. He's got
to be on the list.
Not necessarily be having a
piece of the action so far as
the stocks concerned doesn't
mean you got to be on any lists.
You're already on a real on the
important list. No, this is
true.
But for sure Kizzy is not on the
list. But you found she always
gets a piece of this. So I don't
know if if that goes to the NIH,
the disclosure documents are
there. They're in the show
notes. You can take a look at
it. I was just looking to see if
I could see anyone else. Nope.
Anyway, so it's common and what
can we look for now I say in the
next day or two, we will have
the typical shots of lines
around the block. All the
videos, huge lines are lined up
and ready to go.
And if and half the lines will
be some of the technicians doing
the shot because the lines will
never be long enough till I make
a million mile long line to show
that to the public over and over
and over again. So you see, oh,
there are people, I don't
understand their mentality, but
they see a line they get in it.
And, and I've been
thinking this must be a good
night club. There's a line out
front.
I've been thinking Yes, the
velvet rope concept. But a
Walmart is going to be one of
the big distributors for this.
And to me that adds a little
interesting twist to our holiday
favorite item which we kicked
off on Thursday, we had the
first secret santa paying for
everyone's layaway at Walmart.
And I've just
always well Monday ever do it
anywhere else.
Well, I'm just thinking it might
be an extra draw for people to
come to Walmart. And you know,
once you got them in the door
they'll have their greeters and
telling them hey, hey bro, hey,
black brothers and sisters. You
should come over here will give
you that shot. And right on cue,
the second secret santa at
Walmart
11 tonight shoppers at a tri
cities Walmart got a big
surprise this week.
And almost $70,000 layaway
balance paid in full and just in
time for Christmas.
I'm still in shock Actually, I
really I couldn't believe it.
And I still can't
shoppers who put their Christmas
gifts on layaway at Walmart in
Bristol, Tennessee couldn't
believe the news. I got a
notification on my email
that my
layaway had been paid for and I
thought well that's kind of
weird. On Monday someone walked
into the store not to shop but
to pay off all the layaway
balances the total for
everything $64,995.51
she said yes somebody came in
this morning at six o'clock and
paid everybody's
layaway. But he wants me to tell
you that he loves you.
God bless you. And Merry
Christmas. Those whose bills
were paid may never know who
gave them a Christmas blessing.
But they say they will always be
grateful this man this man made
my son hate he says he
loves you too. But we love
No clue who gave the gift we are
told according to Walmart The
deadline to pay off your layaway
balance is December 14. Sara
still little time for others
maybe who you know are getting
the idea tonight to go out and
do the say
what a great way to pay it
forward a great gifts during
this holiday season.
What a great way to pay it
forward. Yes, come
on things. Yeah. First of all,
how'd they get ahold of that guy
got the email says it was paid
off. And did they get him on?
interviewing? Just going on
here?
No, no. I just want to give you
the facts. The the guy who paid
him off less that no, you heard
a guy who got his balance taken
care of he received an email
from Walmart saying that his
balance had been paid. Yes.
Well, how do they get ahold of
him?
They because he because he has a
balance at Walmart.
What is the media say? Hey, give
me all your give me a list
everyone that balance at Walmart
which no stores going to do
Walmart does.
Hello. So
the second thing
is ad buy. Hello.
Did you know The ad buyer the ad
buy? You got $64,000 This is a
multiple ad buy. This was a you
have to see what the what the
price was, let's say the local
five stations to do an ad buy
each one of them is the amount
of $64,000. And I still wonder
to this day whether this is a
native ad, or are the stations
just suckered into running this
story?
Yes, it would be my I think yes,
it's both of them. It's probably
a hell of a lot cheaper to do
the 64,000 $4,000
spread out over maybe 1020
stations in the whole state.
Because it's such a feel good
story.
They got no agenda show to run
the guy on the no agenda show.
Got on the no agenda show.
There's
another good example of some
free advertising for Walmart.
Yeah, although we do in a
condemnation sort of way sort
of. Still, you know, no
publicity is bad publicity.
Yeah, hey, here's an idea of
Walmart. Why don't you? Why
don't you spend some of that
over here with us. We'll talk
about how great your store is
some
cash. Yeah. I'm gonna show
you Imagine all the people who
could do. Oh yeah, that'd be
fine.
So before I started my list
here, I want to thank a few
people but I want to start by
saying Baron dead. The Baroness
Silicon Valley, sir JD did send
a note in because he's got he's
got his father in law on the
birthday list, but he needs some
f cancer karma for me. It starts
five weeks of radiation
treatment.
Yeah, let's get that right away.
You've got
a good one. So, we start off
with Clarissa, Milan, Milan,
Milan, and baxton Virginia
$160.16 Christina's strict and
we have a lot of unbelievable
number of birthdays in today's
show. Yeah, that's Christina
Strix was on this list for
someone Yeah. Jacksonville,
Florida. 133 69 sir silver due
to the silver dolphins and other
birthday Severn Marilyn 130 31.
And he gets some good karma put
at the end. Sir Behringer,
Silicon Valley, sir JD already
just mentioned his note 130 31
Carrie Walker in $100 in viola,
Idaho, Mark Martin in Sterling,
Illinois. Jonathan which 100
sorry, Jonathan Rivera another
100 from Sanford Florida. Love
you guys. And he and his wife in
the mouth. Michael de and I you
know, I I should know how to
pronounce it's $100 fU qwave
Arena. I'm sure I bought. That
sounds sounds good to me. sounds
right. But get out of my Marina.
It's in North Carolina and we'll
get a correction in the mail.
Sir Kevin McLaughlin to Duke of
Luna and locusts North Carolina
lopsided move doe Nathan 806.
richard clark and Joshua Texas.
7370. threes of case g five d dX
7370. Texas.
You go five. Charlie Charlie.
Got a call for a smokin hot
wife. Andre Picchu in Okay, let
me try it. Let me give this a
shot. Andre. Pete you in real
quick. Holland 66. No,
no, you when I say you'll be
pissed because you know at first
it was Andre Pico. Pico. And he
lives in the rice vague.
vague. Okay, close.
6969 from him of course. Sam van
hoorn. Enough. Who are Sam Ben
Warren in Amsterdam quarter
6633.
So many people with the birthday
especially a lot of 30 threes.
It's It's like going crazy with
the 33
very suspect. Birthday. Sam has
a birthday. Sir not appearing in
this podcast. in Richland.
Washington is 3678 Brandon
Turner Valley at Velez in
Kingman Arizona. 5555. Matthew
dropped Cohen Delaware Ohio.
Yeah, got
here. He He's getting
gallbladder his gallbladder will
be removed on Monday and he says
Hey, guys, I mean in the
morning, gents, Monday I have
the distinct pleasure of having
my gallbladder removed by one of
the finest robots money or my
insurance plan could buy. I'm
sure you know, people that have
had robotic laparoscopy sorry
robotic, robotic, laparoscopic
koleos something bad to me.
Please make an exception to read
part of my email on the show to
get the power of the no agenda
energy going well, I think we do
need a little bit of karma there
needs that
you've got karma.
For sure, yeah. He sent us the
robot when it goes on the dime
from him. Yep. Patricia Kiernan
in Dublin, Ireland. Hey Dublin,
Ireland. I
5333 and she's got a birthday
too. Well, she says she's
donating for her douchebag
husband mark so and it's his
birthday.
Oh, it's his birth but
I think he can get a deducing
then if she's donating for her
douchebag husband.
He didn't ask for it.
Okay, and then he remains
douche.
Sir chaotic mass in Dallas,
Texas. 5120. Sir big Papa moose
of the Ogallala Aquifer in
liberal Kansas 50. These
following ones are $50 donors
name and location in the
shortlist today, overall. Big
Papa Rawson Kotlikoff in London,
UK. Kimberly redmon in Toronto,
Ontario sir lab rat of the hill
country in Universal City,
Texas, Dame Patricia Worthington
in Miami, Florida. She had a
note she sent in about
something. wanted to go dig it
up. Sorry, damn. It's just some
requests that she had about
Robert Robert curl back in Essex
Ville, Michigan. Clayton Dunn
event in Greenfield, Wisconsin,
john hight in Folsom, California
with prison, his big prison,
Johnny Cash, sir Brandon serinus
of law. I'm in Port orchard,
Washington. And that would
conclude our list of well
wishers and producers for show
Yes, and I'm still Oh, here we
go. This is thinking about me
doing a Christmas search. And
she's talking about a meetup
here. I do not have i the only
email I have is from the fifth
of December. So I don't have a
current one. So maybe she didn't
have a note as possible. She
certainly is royalty in our
book. So we know she's been
around. Oh, yeah. And around
these parts. Well, thanks.
Thanks, you all, thank you very
much. These these messages of
support, and these donations are
incredibly valuable to us. They
quite literally keep the show
going. I also know a lot of
people because of 1212. When you
sent the email decided to up
there are 1111 donations to
1212. We don't mention those
under $50. Primarily because
people want to remain anonymous,
at some guaranteed level. So
anything under 50 is never
mentioned, which is why we do
have people showing up with
4999, etc. But we understand,
and we appreciate it and we'd
love for you to consider
donating your time your talent
or your treasure for the next
show. That'll be 1304 episodes
of this grand experiment. Where
really you are the producer,
you're not a listener, you're
not our fans, you're not our
audience. You are the producer
of the best podcast in the
universe, an experiment that
shall continue for the
foreseeable future.org slash and
no karma is for everybody who
needs
jobs, jobs, jobs and jobs.
That's
karma.
And quite a list we have I think
is one of the biggest birthday
lists we've ever seen a lot of
30 threes in here and we start
with Lorraine Hart, who says
Happy Birthday to her husband
Alan, who celebrated on December
3 sir JD Happy Birthday to his
father in law dawn who turned 80
and he still reads the newspaper
without his glasses. Mark from
White Bear Lake Minnesota. It's
52 days, sir cesium 137 maybe
the same guy turns 50 today,
Gabriel sangwan Happy Birthday
to Black Knights easier. 137 who
is celebrating today?
Christopher from St. Mary's
Idaho, will be 51 on December 14
Emily ball says Happy Birthday
to our handsome man Adams
celebrating the 14th as well as
his Sandra Walker. Charles wern
Happy Birthday to his wife Sonia
turns 30 on the 14th he's named
might have been Alex but that
was just confusion in the notes.
Christina Strickland Happy
Birthday to her dad grumping
green guy turn 34 and the 14th
sir silver dude will be
celebrating on the 14th Richard
klare Happy birthday was smokin
hot wife Mary she celebrates on
the 15th as does Sam fun whore
who turns 33 magic numbers on
the 15th. And on the 16th
Patricia Kiernan says Happy
Birthday to her douchebag
husband Mark Kiernan and we say
happy birthday to everybody here
from the best podcast
in the universe.
Ooh, baby. That was a long one.
No nights though. No title
changes but we do have an
overview of the meetups.
Before we give you the full
rundown here is a meetup report
the no agenda meetups are
actually protests you know if
there's any kind of hassle with
the local Popo, just talk to him
like you went to a protest. I
went to no agenda protest calm
it was organized man. Okay,
you're good to go. And you might
find yourself at the NA local
512 meetup where Black Knights
are Scott of the black bear and
I think sir Scott of the armory
once again brought the
austinites together
your black Baron of the new
agenda armory Scott Morgan here
we have a nice little group
that's come in December. Well,
well, for the new agenda FEMA
Region six meetup deep in the
heart of Austin cost in the long
run better to introduce
themselves.
What's up
douchebags? It's
Phil Gibson. You're gonna need a
Bitcoin or have fun stands for
peace.
Hey guys.
Hello guys my name is amino
demento I came all the way from
Lancaster County pa here down at
a Texas state of mind when I
want to know what the fringe is
going on I listened to the
crackpots in the buzzkill
is Eric when I drove to Dallas
for his protest, let's run like
a party.
God man, as I
say I support mandatory mass
requirements only if they're
made of leather
in certain clubs. Hi, this
is Dan I'm
planning the no agenda post
pandemic party
while we sit here at the no
agenda meetup sir chaotic mass
keeping safe in a post
in the morning, john Adam, this
is Josh Magnuson from Austin. I
have nothing to say but I am
totally triggered in Blackburn
signing out one more time.
Right beautiful crowd sorry I
couldn't be there. I did a four
hour episode with no facts did
not come of it. Here's what's
coming up on the no agenda
protests.com no agenda meetup
calm calendar for this coming
Saturday. Toronto no agenda
peaceful protest super spreader
event is six o'clock. Now see
the website for details. Also on
the 19th Quebec City Carol,
Carol and troll that'll be 11 in
the morning chocolate showed and
festivities it's a rock okay? On
Saturday tiny amygdala of
Anchorage one o'clock an Alaskan
time at Mountain usco brewing
Midtown Anchorage. Also on
Saturday flight double o double
noteflight 01 o of the no agenda
Garden Grove and that will be
indeed in Garden Grove. While
it's on Saturday, Nashville Noel
agenda meetup six o'clock at the
party filed downtown valet
parking tip your valet says rich
B was organizing and the Western
New York meetup stay negative
seven o'clock at bucket bar
Odessa, New York on Saturday.
And what else do we have in not
much else in December the 27th a
very fine people meet up in
Charlottesville, Virginia, at
the Trump winery that should be
a hoot. And for more for
January, what's on the horizon
for our no agenda meetups where
you can hang out with people who
won't trigger you you won't be
you won't trigger them. You can
just have a good time, crack
some jokes, sing some songs,
talk about better days, and just
have a good time with people we
really need and don't know that
you're privileged really are
privileged in these days not
many people get to find people
that can just hang out with and
just chat with and not be
worried about stuff. So go take
your privilege to no agenda
meetups.com and if there isn't
one near you that you can attend
well, by golly, why don't you
start one yourself? No agenda
meetups.com
Yeah, baby.
I got a Brexit update.
Oh, good, cuz I don't have one.
Yeah. So they went into overtime
in the negotiations, and they
know they're not going to make
it. And so they are going to
push even a little bit further.
The President of the European
Union's Ursula Thunder Lion came
out and she looked a bit demure.
But she feels like at least
we're trying and remember, any
one of the 27 euro states can
veto this deal. So it's highly
unlikely considering it's about
fish. That's the final dispute.
It's about who
now that he vetoed, the Brits
already have their warships out
to protect their water fish.
Yeah, it's gonna block the
people fishing.
Yes, they're going to block
people from fishing. Here's the
Ursula
despite the exhaustion after
almost one year of negotiations,
and despite the fact that
deadlines have been missed over
and over. We both think that it
is responsible at this point in
time to go the extra mile. We
have accordingly mandated our
negotiators to continue the
talks and to see whether or not
reach an agreement can be
reached. Even at this late
stage. The negotiations continue
here in Brussels.
Well, no one's no one thinks
it's likely they'll come up with
any kind of deal which would
mean a crash out no deal Brexit
here's Bo Joe
we're gonna continue to try. I'm
gonna try with all our hearts
and we'll be as creative as we
possibly can. You know, we we
remain willing to talk will
continue to do so. But in the
meantime, let's get ready for
the WTO option. And that's what
I told the cabinet
WTO. Babe. That's it going World
Trade Organization going
outside, then you know what? I
guarantee you British residents
will not be allowed into the
European Union until the COVID
is over. There'll be they'll be
shunned. Because, you know,
there's going to be a lot of bad
blood.
I think so I
think they're really going to be
mean.
For the EU, you mean?
Yeah. The EU is going to be
mean, they're gonna be like, No,
I
think they're gonna be mean.
Yeah, I agree. Because this is
like a humiliation of the
highest order, kind of,
you know, It's humiliating. I'll
tell you what's humiliating. I
told you, we went out Saturday
night, downtown. And I was
excited, because I'd been
downtown with the dinner on
Tuesday. And I said, Tina, you
know, love it, and it's
beautiful. It's all Christmassy,
and everyone's all jacked up
about it. And as we're driving
across the first three bridge,
there's City Hall is green. City
Hall is illuminated in green.
And I think that there is that
what they're doing for
Christmas. Is that this thing?
Well, no,
Austin City Hall is all lit up
tonight to commemorate the fifth
year of the Paris Climate
Agreement. It's an agreement
within 100 countries to achieve
net zero carbon emissions by the
middle of the century. And
President Donald Trump pulled
the us out of that agreement.
But leaders with the City of
Austin say they're still working
to reduce carbon emissions.
So the verse you signal with the
green light
brother gets a class Hey, we
don't even do that. What
are we gonna do?
some green light man
that'll do a green lights in
California
green light.
douchebags.
greenies. Get out of here. I got
it really democratic Texas.
I got a depressing clip as long
as you have something to go out
on a high note I
do have one I have the Hitler a
Supercuts.
Oh, that can't be depressing.
Let's play that first. That's
gonna be great
this week, so not Trump.
ago, Kristallnacht happened, it
was the Nazis warning shot
across the bow of our human
civilization. After four years
of a modern day assault on those
same values by Donald Trump. I'm
gonna
use an extreme example. Think
about Hitler, so many stunning
parallels
to what Hitler was doing
describing
Hitler's psychological profile
and this only pertains to Adolf
Hitler. There is so much that
has resonance of the Third Reich
in this administration, many
tendencies like Adolf Hitler,
does this look like Germany in
1932 we're getting close and
this only pertains to Adolf
Hitler and pertains to nobody
else
90% of what he says I'm like,
this guy gets it if you read
anything about the rise of Third
Reich and Adolf Hitler, you will
see the parallels
is a true psychopath
solid that sounds a lot like a
certain leader that killed
members of my family.
Wow Jews of how Hitler came to
power he came to power under
fair free elections talking
about Adolf Hitler and that's
all we're talking about.
Donald loves Nazis.
CNN say that
he came with it Wow.
We always knew it wasn't Did you
hit upon a a super cut database
or something? So I'm super,
super gut roll.
You You just landed in some
beautiful pile of supercut This
is a very distressing clip from
CBS The show is called who's the
neighborhood? Yes the
neighborhood and as you know in
most of these big Hollywood
productions we have the Norman
Lear
let me I know that show very
well. I'm gonna explain the
premise
Oh, thank you.
A white kind of a liberal white
guy young white guy millennial
older millennial moves in with
his wife into the middle of a
black neighborhood, bro. Okay.
And he and his black neighbor is
a jerk. And he and the white
guys just this naive guy loves
everything because he's a lover
not a not a fighter. And he's
just the most optimistic guy and
he sees everything great and he
thinks is fantastic. deliver
this black neighborhood because
it shows what what you know as
great white liberals are really
like, and it's and comedy
ensues. It's a comedy.
Yes. Well, here comes a great
comedic bit. Now this is here's
the scene. I guess they have a
kid. At least one younger kid.
And this kid's friend who lives
in the neighborhood. And this
into the kid is white with the
white family. His friend is
black. He was arrested by the
police or harassed by the
police. So the white mom has to
sit down with the white kid and
have a talk.
organised one after. You know.
She got beat up by the Popo.
Hey, I know there's a lot going
on right now. You want to talk
about it? I understand where the
police beat up. Trey. Did you do
something wrong? No. The police
are the ones who did something
wrong. Supposed to be the good
guys. Yeah. But there's some bad
ones too. So if there's ever an
emergency, should I still call
them? Oh, yeah. First, sweetie,
they would never hurt you.
Right? Because I'm a kid.
Actually, it's because you're
white. You see the police in
this country have a history of
treating us better than they
treat black people. But that
doesn't make any sense. Why
would they do that? That's a
good question. The answer is
kind of complicated. Oh, that's
what you said when asked for
babies come from I find
this so despicable
Yes, it's it is a it's
despicable is even the right
word for it.
And basically just threw all
police all across the country
under the bus like oh, yeah,
it's just because you're white.
You know, I was like we got a
history of that isn't how it is.
This is Norman Lear Hollywood
foundation. Crap, man. That's
what this is. shoved right into
the to the narrative. Oh, you
know, that was nice. No, I
disagree. I really just was. I
don't think it was necessary.
You don't have to go to Norman
Lear to pull that stuff out of
it. Yeah,
I agree. I agree. That's true.
This is just a Hollywood crap a
bunch of virtue signaling
douchebags, but decided to do
this. And they've been there was
the regular staff. I'm sure
there was no input from anybody
outside effect. I think if there
was, they would have had them
back off a little bit.
Yeah, cuz it was a bit too much.
I agree.
All right. Now I need something
happy because I'm depressed
about this.
No. Oh, well, I got a three
parter here. If you want to hear
about gay Christmas.
Oh, yes. Let's roll. Yes, I do.
Correct. I do want and, and just
so you know, don't say to me
later. We were too long.
Well, you're the one asked for
the additional material. I'm
gonna say we're too long because
we were too long. But don't you
have a single clip? No, this is
three clips. Okay, three parter.
I mean, you can just play part
one I think would be good. But I
also have a Rand Paul rant and
then Cheney, which has been
around
No, no, no, I want gay
Christmas.
I bet you do. Okay, so let's
play now. This is from the CBC.
And this is from the reporter,
they, the guy who's the reporter
seems gay to me, but I don't
what do I know? And he also said
he separates the gays from his
group, which is us. But But
apparently, I said, apparently,
I said it. I heard it, I
caught it. Us versus the gays. I
hear. Okay,
us versus the gays. And what is
going on is that Hollywood's
decided to make Christmas gay.
So they rolled out a bunch of
gay movies and everything, all
these Christmas movies that are
Oh, I start starting with the
one movie with Kristen Stewart
and they call Happy holidays or
something. I can't remember the
name.
I didn't get the memo about the
Christmas being gay this year.
Well get a clue. This CBC
Canadian broadcast
a whole new crop of Christmas
movies, LGBTQ films, released
for this holiday season, part of
a trend that caught Eli's eye.
So he's back with us from his
home, getting set for his
holidays and looking to these
holiday offerings. As I said,
it's a whole new landscape, Eli?
Yeah,
I mean, you know, it's
interesting. So happiest season
really kind of kicked off this
discussion. You know, there was
a time a few weeks ago, I
couldn't open Twitter without
being just like enveloped in a
discussion about who Kristen
Stewart's should character
should have ended up with how
did Harper behaving people had
so many feelings about this
film, and it seemed to really
strike a chord in audience, you
know, certainly wider than just
LGBTQ. And so this which was
originally released on Hulu and
streaming in Canada, turned out
to be quite the success and
also, I think part of this new
wave of content that we're
noticing in the traditionally
very traditional holiday genre
and so other films that are
popping up under the mistletoe
This year Christmas house from
the Hallmark Channel featuring a
gay chant a gay couple. It's a
very big change for the channel.
There's dashing in December
Paramount network, there's the
Christmas setup on the lifetime
network. Now I reached out to
Christian Baker in Nashville.
She's the producer and director
of a couple of holiday films
made for queer viewers. Last
year, they made a movie called
season of love, which got a
great response for their
audience. She was getting a lot
of her customers saying, you
know, we want to see our own
selves in these Christmas films.
This year. They're releasing, I
hate New Year's but a lesbian
couple in Nashville. And what
she was telling me is a part of
the need is that we have had a
lot of great, powerful dramatic
movies with gay and lesbian
storylines, but they are quite
serious and there was something
that was missing for her
audience. You know, I
can almost see the Hallmark
Channel commercial.
This year celebrate in
style with a Hallmark Channel.
We've got twinks in my tree. We
have Are you sure this is
eggnog?
This is great.
Let's listen to what this
producer has to say this clip to
their
unrequited love their, you know,
like, I can't be with you
because society tells me that or
I'm coming out but my Mormon
parents are gonna hate me.
And, you know, it's it's all of
that
that's that we absolutely
experience and some people still
experienced that. But I think
what was also missing was sort
of this classic trophy,
fabulous, happy love story.
Everybody wants their serving of
holiday mush. Bees movies are
comfort food, and why shouldn't
gay and lesbian audiences be
able to enjoy that, like the
rest of us? That was really what
she said is we want our happy
endings. You know, we want our
fun, cheesy stuff. No one is
saying that this is Hamlet. But
they certainly want to see
themselves represented in the
genre along with everyone else.
So is that, you know, that
desire to see that Hollywood,
that Hallmark moment? Is that
really the explanation? Why why
the change and the broader
industry change a lie?
I mean, from the from the
audience? Yes. But from the
industry. I think actually,
interestingly, it's a business
case and a convincing one. So I
talked to glad CEO and President
Sarah Kate Ellis, this is the
gay and lesbian advocacy group.
And what she has noticed is a
real big ship. You look at the
demographics in America, for
example, I think if you look at
like 18 to 34, you're seeing as
much of the population as 30%,
identifying as LGBTQ in one way
or another Wow, look at
representation on television,
it's changing. But in terms of
characters on screen, it's still
in single digits. But what Alice
was telling me is what really
has changed for the creators and
the producers and the executives
is a shift in that business
model. And what now makes sense.
Take a look.
She's saying 30% of the audience
is gay is that what he said?
in the in the younger debt in
the millennial demographic,
you know that Tina and I we saw
the trailer for that movie with
the the two girls as he said,
oh, let's be in love. But it
wasn't a good movie. It wasn't a
it was about her coming out or
not. It wasn't a you know, you
Christmas miracle type movie and
every there's multiple
storylines of love. And it just
wasn't that it was all about
coming out very stressful. I
didn't I didn't like it at all.
I can. I can hardly imagine
anyone like that one was just
weird. is just a one with
Kristen Stewart. I don't
remember
it. That's the hot movie that's
triggering a lot of this.
That's the new one. Let me see.
Tommy No. I think that is the
one because we saw it. Yeah,
what is the name of this one
though?
Yeah,
I think that's the one well, it
just looked boring. It didn't
look like a fun and I don't
care. It was two women who gives
a crap but that's not the story
is not a Christmas story. It has
to be all it's about coming out.
which I understand is something
very important, but it wasn't to
me. It just really wasn't a
Christmas movie. The happiest?
You're the last
guy interacting with the glad to
woman's
Yes. Oh, come all ye faithful.
It was risky to show LTP
Hold on a second. I don't think
it was all come all ye faithful
is the Christmas story movie.
No, no, that's that's my new
movie that I'm putting together
for our gay for our gay
holidays. Hello.
It was risky to show LGBTQ
people in Their minds, because
it could cost them business. And
now what they've realized
because of the population growth
because of the younger
generation, because it's been
proven time and time again, that
it is actually a really good
business model to be diverse and
inclusive. They're realizing
that the real risk is leaving
communities out. You know,
circuit
Ellis was reminding me that it
was just last year that the
Hallmark Channel they had a
commercial featuring same sex
couple at a wedding, and it was
pulled down because there was a
backlash and they removed it.
And then they apologized for the
removal. And she had to explain
to her children why that
commercial was pulled from air
and then contrast stop the clip.
Just a few
that is bullcrap. Okay, have you
in your entire you raised the
kid? I've got kids, you have
never heard a kid ever say, hey,
Mommy, Daddy, why did they pull
that commercial? First of all,
that would be notice.
Never.
It's a bull crap story. This is
the CBC lying to the public. By
the way. No Kid ever says hey,
why did they pull the ad with a
the kid would know they pull the
end? Why would the kid cares and
add For God's sake. So let's
back it. I'm gonna go sorry. I
just couldn't take that. Take
it.
Can I ask your question? Is is
Kristen Stewart? Is she gay? She
loves me. Yeah, she is. I didn't
know that. Yeah,
she Oh, no. She went she came
out like a couple years ago.
Oh, okay. So that's why she's
allowed to act in this. I was
just wondering,
okay, well, she brings this up.
By the way, I know what you're
going with this? Which is why
why are we allowing straight
actors to play gay character?
Yeah. She brings up the fact
that we're gonna if we go to
she's actually wise in this
regard. She says, we can't
really adopt that policy,
because we won't let straight
actors play gay characters that
we can't let gay actors play
straight characters.
Yeah, good luck with that
argument, moved it. And then
they apologized for the removal.
And she had to explain to her
children, why that commercial
was pulled from air. And then
contrast that to just a few
weeks ago, where Sarah Kate
Ellis, and her wife and her
kids, got out the hot cocoa, got
out the cookies, sat down on the
couch and watched happiest
season with these big fancy
Hollywood stars. And I asked her
if he felt like Piglet.
I literally couldn't believe it.
You know, I mean, having grown
up LGBTQ.
I think oftentimes, we haven't
really known what life was going
to be we didn't see a path in a
lot of ways. And I would have
never thought that moment would
have ever existed if you asked
me at twit would have ever
existed if you asked me at 21.
And so it was it was kind of
amazing.
What a difference of a sea
change that we're seeing. And
that's not to say the work is
done. You talk to creators, you
talk to critics, there's still
more that needs to be done in
terms of people of color in
these films, kind of a wider
spectrum of characters in these
LGBTQ storylines, and that's the
challenge of the winning you
only have a few of these films.
They have to kind of shoulder
everything they have to
represent all things for all
people but as we get more we'll
start to see more of those
issues solved on screen and
everyone can enjoy their missile
tomash Okay,
again,
it's a bad movie. It's not a
good Christmas movie. They
missed the mark as far as I'm
concerned.
They really miss this this is
they're gonna dis just missing
the mark is gonna continue as
long as identity politics sneaks
into the movie industry. And
like he said right at the end
there because he's all in on
this idea. Oh, well you know
what? We got to get some black
gays in there. Oh, yeah. We got
to get all these different kinds
of gays.
White gay or not the right gay
you're wrong gay. Oh my
goodness. It's Yeah, you're
right this to say it's sad. Sad
does happen. Look, I'm a sucker
for a great rom com Christmas
movie. This was not it had
nothing to do with the sexual
orientation it was this the
storyline? I want Kris Kringle.
That's Chris
screen. Kris Kringle has to be
gay.
That's right. Hey,
no to sell for next year. Dana.
called Dana. We got a great
movie. Kris Kringle is queer.
Mm hmm.
sit on my lap little boy.
Okay. All right. I'm shutting it
down. Now.
Remember that we
do have another show coming up
on Thursday. It's gonna be jam
packed, no doubt. So make sure
you support us by going to
devore act.org slash na up next
on the no agenda stream. Fletch
and Dave Blaney will be bringing
your hug story. And since we've
run out we've got a little bit
of time left to enter show mixes
Jesse Coyne Nelson and
Archimedes Johnson. Think you're
liking both. And coming to you
from Austin, Texas capital the
drone Star State here in
opportunity's own number 33.
FEMA Region number six in the
governmental maps in the
morning, everybody.
I'm Adam Curry, and from
Northern Silicon Valley, where
rain like a son of a bitch last
night. i'm john CWA
we returned on Thursday right
here on no agenda. We expect you
to be here, remember us at the
vortec.org slash na until then,
adios mopho. And such
I never forgot what President
Kennedy said about going.
You know why? Because I refuse
to pump
no breath.
Get out of the rain. God bless
you all. Thank you. He's cried.
And
I took on in terms of Iraq. I
mean, excuse me in terms of what
was going on in Ukraine to
pressure
the electric press by
acclamation.
Right
down the swamp is
I'm gonna give you the whole
load that watch the hair come
back up again.
Why not include members of the
VI
transition team, as part of this
summit? We are hosting today to
see who the next administration
is because we won and those
swing states and there was
terrible things that went on. So
we're gonna have to see who the
next administration is. We have
put together the most extensive
and inclusive voter fraud
organization in the history of
American politics. So I learned
about roaches I learned about
kids jumping on my lap.
Today 1000s of President Trump's
supporters gathered in the
nation's capitol. CBS Jeff
Deghayes was in the crowd,
including them recently part in
former National Security Adviser
Michael Flynn. This is the
President's loyal base when you
have constipation unlike hot
stools, a soft stool is easy to
pass
the pressure Welcome everybody
to a brand new program on the
pot show network which would be
titled a number of things we
chose no agenda, but it couldn't
be the show with no imaging No.
Agenda show no show exactly.
mcenany Mic drop
reprimanding money shot it Him
you will obey China ozy MBA
noodle gun on mac and cheese
douchebag famous freedom New
World Order little girl
drunk or not drunk
cash audio smoke both farming
with Monsanto he said to you
Come on man I love bugs bugs go
toe to toe
foundation
should be ict jobs jobs jobs and
jobs look it's true
to map Jeb Bush to climate
change turbo charge sounds
pretty good
shut up safe
Epstein caught up with the
terrorists and get
Bitcoin as the world said
no no no
coincidence I think not youtuber
adventurous guy we can we saw
that he died nice.
My gosh. Choose to send Ben and
Bernadette contradiction is
true.
JOHN C
and j
Hey Warren peace Georgia Bella
Don Lemon. WCC says that PCR
tests as shown by
Fox News run by Democrats who
didn't come from NPR.
voting booth COVID vaccine Rob
Ryan is Twitter. Separate
couchbase turn your mic down.
The only thing is is to guys
with an idea of putting together
a
agenda list show agenda lists
show exactly. Agenda lists show
mopho.org slash and
have they ever
met a lesbian