podcasting 2.0 for December
12 2020, this is episode number
15. And Hey baby, we're with the
band
all around. But it is
a Friday time once again for a
meeting of the Board for
podcasting 2.0 podcast
index.org. And now, ladies and
gentlemen, the man who put the
auto in autocomplete the
developer Dynamo, Mr. Dave
Jones.
Was the band, the band.
The band, we were the band. Were
the band. Yeah, this is
something. First of all, how you
doing? Man?
I'm sad. You're sad, is
extremely depressed. What's
wrong? And nobody appears to
like us anymore. We had two
donations this week.
Oh, honeymoon is over.
No. Yeah, yeah, it's Yeah, it's
the cold hard. Facing the cold
hard reality now of the dark
winter. Yes, it's dark winter.
Yeah, it's dark winter. Well,
then let me say right off the
bat, if this is a value for
value projects, podcast,
index.org and the accompanying
podcast. And if you want to
support it, if you get any value
out of what you're seeing, maybe
you're an app developer, maybe
you're just a podcast listener,
maybe just listen to this
podcast. Who knows? Maybe you
just like free speech. And that
kind of stuff and fighting
against canceled culture. Put
that into a number put in just
keep it in your head, go to
podcast index.org and hit the
big red Donate button and send
us some value. We'd really
appreciate that. We did get a
nice sponsored value returned
from RSS calm.
Yeah, totally. And I've put that
into the donation since he was
already so sure.
That's one of the two. Yeah,
let's
not talk about that right now.
You gotta save it.
Okay, that's not
one of the two. That's the nest
number three, like two and a
half. Yeah.
That was in pod news. And I and
I do want to say now you're sad.
I'm a little bit Earth.
Oh, yeah. Because
I know. James Cridland pod news.
dotnet. He has a podcast, which
is that called the pod news
podcast. Is
that what that is? But there's
that and then he's got a new one
called pod land.
I don't know which one I was
listening to maybe was pod land.
And all of a sudden, he's like
stealing our material he's doing
he's doing hot namespace talk.
Excuse me. Yes, that's not okay.
It's like horning in on our
business. Dave?
Yeah. No, we get there's only
one podcast that gets to talk
about namespaces for an hour
seriously.
I mean, we are the porn hub of
namespace.
And it's so appropriate.
Appropriate. I know I saw a Ryan
Gentry from lightning labs he
was he posted in one I think
Tales from the Crypt tribe on
swings chat, says Does anyone
know anyone over to Pornhub
asking for a friend
is like okay, they need a Visa
MasterCard. For exactly the
processing. Let's get in there.
My immediate reaction was well
get ready for Bitcoin. 100,000.
Yeah, is it's going up baby.
And Tina right away. She's like,
oh, Bitcoin. There's your
answer. That's what you got to
do.
That was funny. Yeah. That was
funny. Yeah. deeper on on social
media.
She knows man. She knows
that. If she does. She needs to
send them an invoice. That's
good. material. Reminder,
insulting.
She should send us a Yeah, when
she can send us a lightning
invoice. We'll pay it. Yeah.
When she can. She has a wallet.
So does she Yeah. Oh, yes. I
want a wallet. Okay. You go. And
what she needs is a podcast that
wallet. That's what she needs.
And that's true. I want to ask
everyone who's listening to this
in a in a lightning enabled app
to crank up the value sliders,
please peg that to the right.
thing. Go to whatever whatever
your value settings should be.
And I was thinking now that we
have Dred Scott, doing community
chapters for the show, which is
dynamite. I don't know if you've
seen it.
Oh, yeah. Yeah, it was awesome.
I saw it. The one I saw earlier,
the chapters were rolling
through. And it was like, just
links to pay like iframes with
pages and it could scroll. It
was awesome. It was that love
that article? substack. karate.
Oh, yeah. Last week it was in
there. You could just read the
article right in the app. Yeah,
cool is that pause the podcast,
read the article and then
unpause it. Of course, that
article was like 500 miles
an article. Yeah. And if you're
wondering how you can witness
all this beauty, go to new pod
stamps.com that's where, where
you can find all the apps and
services hosting companies that
are podcasting 2.0 compliant,
and certified as an idea.
I just had an idea. Okay? If
that happens, you're sitting
there listening to a podcast and
the chapter comes through, and
has something you can read or
something like that. We get a,
you get to have some way to have
like a lightning payment into
things. So you can see you could
like, help the person, this
stuff you're linking to.
So okay, two things. And this,
and we'll just get this out of
that we have guests hanging, so
I don't want to take too long.
But I had dinner with Paul from
Sphinx chat. He was in Austin,
the other day. And so first off,
yes. What I'd like to do with
the show right now, since Dred
Scott is doing our chapters, I'm
going to get him a node. And we
should cut him in on the value
block for what 5%?
Oh, yeah, sure. Should
we do that's great. Yeah. So we
can also show how this actually
works and, and have him enjoy
some of that. I mean, that's the
whole point is, you know, we are
eating our own dog food here.
And coming back to what you just
said, We're with the band was
something that Paul identified
at our dinner, he said, what's
happening with the community
chapters that people can add to
it, but also in Sphinx chat with
the boosts and with the chat
itself. That's all additional
content that is added by the
listeners, I like to call them
producers. And it makes you feel
like you're with the band. And
so Dred Scott is truly with the
band right now. And the Lee with
the the amount of creativity he
can put in with still very
rudimentary tools is quite
astounding. And what he's what I
see him do on no agenda, where
he's doing the same also gonna
put him in the value block for
that show, is he'll get images,
appropriate images from no
agenda, art generator, and put
those in topics that we're
talking about stuff because most
of those images come up from a
topic that just not picked up
the album art. So now he's
putting that in. So now that
that now also brings in the
other artists, I mean, it's, you
know, who you're with the band,
and they get to be a part of the
podcast, it's really mind
blowing. And I want to have that
for clips. You know, there's,
there's just so much stuff that
we could add to it. And it's
gonna be pretty app specific the
way it is. Now, unless or until,
you know, every child born is
provided a lightning node ID at
birth, which is really what I
think should happen. I'm
going Somali, I'm
going to lobby for this. Yes. A
shot of every child needs a
lightning
node ID Yeah. And you just
barcode it on your forehead?
Well, that's fine. As long as
it's not on the forehead or on
your right hand. And it's not
the mark of the beast. It's a
good thing.
Yeah, everybody gets a lightning
node. And here's the number
we're gonna tattoo. I don't,
there's nothing wrong with this.
So and this is maybe something
we'll talk with our guests
about. It kind of flows into
what is the end? God, I can't
believe I'm using the term the
deep data file, which is up for
discussion now. Which you're not
liking it. Oh, you're not out of
file. Well, hit me, brother.
I don't know what rule I got
what rule it is. It's the rules.
First, we
need to go back to the rule
book. Yeah.
Yeah, you know, and I get it. I
totally understand that. The
name doesn't match up with
necessarily all the things it
does. The problem, though, is
that it really doesn't matter
what you call it. That that is
in that is one of the rules for
standard makers. It totally
doesn't matter what
right. All right, the then I'm
misunderstanding the issue. I
thought it wasn't just about,
here's what I here's what I feel
is happening. And I could be
wrong. And it's not an
accusatory statement. I feel
there's a push to have an
external data file that will
contain all kinds of extra
goodies. And one day, I'm gonna
wake up and it's gonna be JSON.
That's,
that's what it already is.
Jason, you're living your
dreams. Okay.
I knew it was a backdoor to JSON
somehow.
I say yeah, no, it's Jason. Is
it JSON all the way down, but I
do
see the value in having the
ability now. And it all depends
on what's easier. Is it easier
to have podcast apps, no one to
refresh the feed and get new
information, or is it easier to
have a couple of files in there
that are static that the apple
just reread every single time it
fires up for an episode? That
seems to be the the main crux of
the issue.
Yeah, I mean, the chapters file
is already basically that it's
it's it is the quote unquote
deep data file. And I'm never in
a. That's, that's what it is.
And so that's what like Daniel
is saying is that he thinks that
the the name chapters does not
properly reflect what, oh,
I don't care about file. I don't
care about the name
that doesn't. That's, that's
where I'm at to it. And he, he,
he likened it to with choosing
the name podcast for the podcast
namespace. I think that is that
is different. That is that is
something that's sort of
external as far as the way it
works in the world. And you
mean, it's a name that people
need to understand,
right? They even is, but this
came out of a confusion saying
that clips is identical
information to chapters, or did
I misunderstand?
Well, it does sound I think you
think sound bites? Yes. Yeah. it
so well. My my thing is that
when I say it, totally doesn't
matter what you what you name
it, I don't mean that it doesn't
matter what the Nate what you
call it, ever. Like, in all
circumstances, what I mean, what
I mean, in in, I'm probably not
making this clear either, is
that it doesn't matter what you
call it, when you get down into
the technical weeds? Mm hmm. So
like, we use things called me,
think of a TCP IP is a
meaningless term. It's an
acronym for something and most
people don't ever, most people
don't need to know, it doesn't
matter what it even stands for.
It just does a thing. And we
know what it does. The name
chapters, it doesn't matter.
Because the only people
referencing the chat the name
chapters who even need to know
what it means, or the people
that are doing the protocol
implementation. And so for those
people, they just know that a
chapters file has all these
other things in it. And, and so
it's just fine. I mean, you
could call it, you know, you
could call it block.
Okay. All right. Let me let me
play this back to you. So the
chapters file, could be could be
both chapters file and sound
bytes file or just the sound
bytes file, it doesn't matter
what it's called, that day, that
type of data will be in that
file.
What it's more, it's less about
the soundbite and more about
other types of data like
location, don't you know, that's
in I don't even I didn't even
want to bring that up. Because
location tag is, is not I got I
got all hot and bothered listen
to Cridland about it. So I might
as well bring it up. Yeah, no,
it's the location tag is fine.
It stands alone, it's gonna be
it we get, we get that it will
get over the hump. But there is
also an idea of putting a
location location points inside
the chapters file. So if
somebody was doing a podcast of
like a walking tour, you can put
little pocket. So at that point,
it's like, well, it's not
chapters anymore. It's something
else. But you know, my, my
counter example was bookmarks
and a PDF, bookmarks and a PDF.
Yes, they function as bookmarks,
but they also have other things.
And I'm like, you can put a full
JavaScript code in. Right,
which, which I have, yeah, yeah.
And it resizes the page, when
you click on it changes font
does all this crazy crap. So and
we still call them bookmarks.
You don't know. I'm just saying
that. At a technical level, you
don't have to change the name of
a thing just because it doesn't
necessarily match the
functionality of the thing. As
long as the name sort of
encompasses the idea. There the
the goal, you know, that's fine.
I just don't I just not I just
don't think it's that big of a
deal. Yeah, okay.
Well, I was confused because I
didn't realize was just about
that. What it's called I thought
it was much deeper. So I'm
sorry, even brought it up. I'm
sorry, I ruined your day.
Piss.
Okay.
Before we get past them I know,
you know, before we Anyway, it
was great planning and talking
to Paul. An update on that
front. You know, the breeze work
continues. I've no idea when the
when their drop date is for, for
a wallet with, whether it's
wallet with podcast capabilities
or a standalone app. I'm not
quite sure but they are
developing and they have code on
GitHub. Did you see that code?
Do you look at it at all?
I did I linked over to and look
at the wall had met totally had
no idea what else
could you figure it out?
I could.
I could lie to you and tell you
I was all over it. This looks
really
look real structured to me.
Yeah, I think it looks fine.
Yeah, let's just look beautiful.
And then we also talked about
about nodes and stuff like that,
and I've been talking to
graham@voltage.io because We
witnessed kind of an overload of
our nodes with the with the
amount of transactions and he
confirmed it. I think, you know,
podcast index.org has the most
transactions of anyone right now
on the lightning network, which
is quite bizarre. And something
happened because he
automatically upgrades to more
CPU and we're actually going to
get a dedicated set up from him.
And so channel started to close
and then we were missing keys
and payments. And
now I can't work
no and, and even closed our
channel to Spinks chat. I'm
like, What am I gonna do? And
even though it's discouraged in
the lightening documentation,
which I didn't realize until I
was told later, that
there's light, there's lightning
document documentation.
Yes. Well, yes. And there's
apparently there's there's a
thing that says it's really
quite not done to request
inbound liquidity on Twitter,
which I do it. And of course, he
got like 15 or $20,000 worth of
inbound liquidity from some
great partners and peers
routing. So
you're a rule breaker, man,
I
What can I say? All right, our
guest today,
we're invited. Daniel J. Daniel
J. Lewis. Olivia. Don't hate me.
You are the worst. No one hates
anybody. But we're honest. You
know that. We got no time for
politics. We really don't. We
got no money for politics. How
about that? I got no money for
politics. Sorry, interrupted. Go
ahead. Well know you invited our
guests. So why don't you give
them an intro?
Oh, john, and Justin from
transistor. Welcome to the show.
Oh, damn. Great intro.
JOHN, john and Justin.
Yeah, yeah.
Okay. That
guy. Justin Jackson transistor,
Fei.
Yeah. Dave. I signed up for this
gig. Because those intros man I
would, I would sign up to hear
those all day long.
doing a podcast with Adam. It's
just like, you just turn on the
fire hose. This is great. But
the
auto and auto complete. I mean,
that is? Well,
I mean, this is a new feature
Dave's been working on he isn't
done yet. He got an autocomplete
endpoint, don't you?
This should be a safe it.
There's gonna be a chapter
whenever. Whenever Dred Scott
puts the chapters together? Yes.
Episode is just one of them's
gonna be called Davis sad. face.
Yeah. And the other one's gonna
be called Is it done yet? Every
week, there's gonna be one
called Is it done yet? No, it is
not done yet. Okay, it isn't.
It's not done. I got a curve.
I got some curveballs. See, this
is this is what I know that Dave
is, like, he's a little bored is
when all of a sudden they're
like this new feature is like,
I'm doing this now. Like, holy
crap.
Am I right?
That's what that's that. Justin.
And john, are you Dr. Y'all both
developers.
Now. Now in our partnership,
john is the developer. So this
is making me look real bad,
because now he's going to expect
a similar Adam Curry treatment.
Every time he releases something
new.
Just talk like you're no you're
talking about?
Exactly. That's
what I do. That's what we that's
what we do every week.
All right. So john, come on in
here. You're the you're the
developer of the two with the
with the deep breath with the
deep voice.
Yep, that's me, Kofi.
That's what I was gonna say when
Adam asked if that was true, if
I was bored as well. Yeah, john.
I mean, of course, that's what
happens. You do stuff and you
get you start working on
infrastructure stuff, and it
gets boring. And then you just
have to like, shake it up and do
so I can
I can relate. I have. I've been
I've had multiple projects going
on once and then I just switch
between them until I can finish
one. Yeah, it's like Justin,
Justin knows. Yeah.
So Justin, to the frustration of
everybody else.
Yeah. So Justin and john,
together founded transistors hit
transistor or
transistor, FM. Some people
don't like putting their domain
extension in there. But for me,
that's like free marketing. It's
transistor.fm is the site. But
it's, it's legally just
transistor.
Yeah, I like this name. Because
for me, it triggers all kinds of
radio, visions of a transistor
radio that may not have even
been the intent behind the name.
But give us a bit of the
backstory because it's a
relatively young hosting
company, I think a couple years,
right.
That's right. Yeah. JOHN, do you
want to do you want to give the
guy and try to give a short
history? Let's see. So it we'd
launched officially in August of
2018.
I think that right? Yeah. August
2, yeah.
Okay, so August 2018. But the
actual code it started in the
end of 2017, I was working for
Cards Against Humanity, and they
were doing a big holiday event.
And one of those was a podcast
they were releasing. And I was a
developer there. And it
previously worked on a
podcasting platform. kind of
thinking about doing another one
building my own, again, by
myself. And so with that, I had
the opportunity to sort of build
something simple just for that
one podcast, which then
eventually spun out into
transistor. So they were nice
enough to let me work on side
projects, which they kind of let
everyone do. And then I had
known Justin for years back for
meeting him at Expo Expo down
in, in Portland, OR over in
Portland, whichever direction
you want to go. And we've been
talking about doing something
together for a long time, I sort
of wanted to do transistor on my
own, based on just previous
experience with some with a co
founder. But, but the more I
thought about it, I was like, I
don't really I don't have any
idea how to market this thing.
Right. So it's just me a
developer, I would basically do
nothing to market it. And
Justin, I kind of wanted to do
something starting in 2018. So
we decided to partner up and
made it legal. And kind of been
going from there. We went full
time last summer. I believe,
yeah. Almost a year, exactly. To
a year after we launched
officially. So August 2019. And
bootstrap the whole thing.
That's a pretty generous
retelling, actually, because
when john told me he was working
on this, I begged him. I'm john.
I said, john, you gotta let me
You gotta let me partner up with
you on this. We got to do this
together.
Yeah, I didn't want to mention
the desperation, but
perfectly played perfectly.
Now what now? Why? So john,
you're a developer. So you'd
like to what you were doing you
developed it? Was there a Did
you see that there was a an
opportunity in the market? Or
was the market so small? Because
you know, there's a number of
players out there. Yeah. And
Justin, why were you begging
man? What the hell were you
thinking? Taking a vow of
poverty getting into podcasting?
Yeah.
Well, I mean, I thought there
was still an opportunity. I
know, there were there were even
two, three years ago, a number
of posts. There's obviously more
now, but I thought there was a
huge potential in podcasting. I
just had fun working on it.
Previously, in my in a previous
iteration for a different
service. Guys, I just I really,
I liked the podcasting landscape
I liked kind of who was involved
in it. I like the open nature of
it. It just seemed like they
were pieces of like the original
internet frontier still in
podcasting. And, yeah, it was a
tough business, a fun, fun
project to work on. All the
customers are great, great to
work with. People seem really
excited about podcasting. And
yeah, I just, you know, had some
previous knowledge of it and
wanted to just build something
up from scratch again, and no,
one of those developer pitches
you got to scratch
and just, you were big, you were
begging to get in what did you
see?
Yeah, well, see, I started
podcast in 2012. And I've always
been in software. So on the
product management side, and I
used to have folks come to me
all the time, you know, between
2012 2013 2014 developer saying,
Oh, you know, I got a great idea
for podcasters. And I always
said, don't build that, because
the podcast market back then,
was mostly di wires and
hobbyists and, you know, people
that wanted to do things
themselves, they didn't like
paying for things. And that this
swit the the trend that I saw
developing that got me more
excited, is you still had this
indie podcast scene. But
increasingly, those folks were
okay with paying for posting and
analytics and other things. But
then you also had just way more
mindshare. So when I was in the
coffee shop, people weren't just
talking about what apps they
were installing on their phone
or what they were watching on
Netflix. They started you know,
saying hey, I'm listening to
this new podcast, and it like
when I heard it the first couple
times in a coffee shop. It made
me stop in my tracks like what
nor normals are talking about
podcasts. Like they figured out
how to you know, find a podcast
app and subscribe subscribe to
an RSS feed like what is going
on and so and, and all of these
kind of big cultural touchstones
like cereal and you know, and
then everything that happened
after cereal that you New York
Times publishing a podcasting op
ed every single week, it just
felt like there's this
burgeoning wave. And now and
then companies starting to
invest in it right yet. branded
podcasts and, and even companies
that I knew that like Basecamp,
which is a relatively small, you
know, software company, they
hire two full time people and
built a studio to have a little
podcast, you know, set up,
right? That's, that's at least
$200,000 a year prop maybe even
more, like, wow, if they're
willing to spend that much on,
you know, hiring some
podcasters, then spending, you
know, $99 a month on podcast
hosting might not be a stretch
for them.
So do you. What is your your
target client base? I mean, it
seems like you're, you're
offering everything we take care
of it, make sure that your
podcast is published on all the
platforms and you got your
status, that's still a big a big
draw for customers that the big
one yeah,
to be unlike at first we thought
our audience was going to be
businesses. But it turns out
that there's like the big draw
is people searching? How do I
start a podcast, or best podcast
hosting? And
I see right here how to start a
podcast right on your menu use
you slide little Seo? w.
Yeah,
that's all Justin.
But, you know, there's there is
a lot of people who want that
kind of help. And so they're
looking for a simple tool that
people don't think about, like
most podcasters are not thinking
about RSS, they're not thinking,
all they're thinking about is
how do I get my audio out into
the world? And whatever is the
the easiest, or the most
friendly, or the most efficient
way to do that is what, that's
what they want. We have folks
switching from Ankur, which is a
free product that switched to us
just to get customer support.
Yeah, it's a big one. I've heard
a lot about this. And people
really like the customer
service.
Yeah, yeah. And so I think we do
have a lot of businesses that
sign up. And that's a great, you
know, that's, it's great to have
those folks. But I think what
john and I really dig is the
Indies, people just in their
basement, buy a microphone, and
have something to say and want
to get it I like growing up, I
always wanted to start my own
talk radio, you know, radio
station. And I actually knew a
guy that bought a radio station.
He was a friend of my dad's and
I, you know, I went up to him
when I was a kid and said, How
do I do that? Like, how do I own
my own station? And he was like,
well, it's millions of dollars.
Justin. Are you are you can go
like serve coffee for years and
years and maybe get on the
microphone. And the idea that
now with, you know, a $99 USB
microphone, and then you know, a
service like transistor, you can
have your own talk radio
station. That's an attractive
idea to a lot of people.
Yes, the and the non live nature
of it, I think makes it
attainable for a lot of people,
they just say, Well, if I mess
up, I just go back and clean it
up later. And I don't have to
have you know, I don't have to
have the terror of having live
radio and that kind of thing
that will make you shut down
makes it a little bit more
accessible for the average human
to think that they can, you
know, pull that off and not be
embarrassed about what the final
product looks like. Yeah, yeah.
I think it's cool that he did
talking about it, podcasting,
feeling like sort of early
internet days. I totally agree
with that. Because Yeah, it's
there's this I remember back,
oh, gosh, this is probably been
20 years ago now and are close
to it. And I was heavy writing a
lot of assembly language at the
time. And we're in one of the
one of the things were
you in prison? What the hell
were you thinking?
It's even worse. It was on
Windows. On Windows. Yeah, using
the masm 32 packages. But they
one of the things that was so
interesting to me about that
whole thing, I think probably a
lot of, you know, sysadmin
developer type people think this
way is that you could understand
what you were doing like you
could one of the first things I
wrote was a podcast downloader
and this podcasting was very,
extremely new at the time. And
it was parsing the RSS feed and
all that jazz. And you had to
actually make the HTTP one, you
know, one dot one call it in,
you know, your your hand coding
the protocol
doing this in assembly language.
Yeah, and it's in languages,
right? Yeah. And it's still got
the code out of post. It is kind
of crazy, but you're doing
you're making all the code He
calls and stuff. And it felt fun
to actually be able to like,
understand the protocols as
they're being used. You know, in
now, today, your most
development is so many layers
removed from the actual, you
know, wire wire level protocols
and the actual, you know, low
underlying technology that it
feels, you're just like, Oh, I
need to do this, I'll just go
get a library and plug it in,
and I'll just pay no, that's
fine. But then you never, you
don't have that sort of thrill
of being able to kind of get in
and really dig down deep and
understand something to do it on
a protocol level. But you still
have kind of had that in
podcasting. It's fine. You get
to parse the RSS, you get to do
all these interesting coding
challenges. It's, it does feel
like old internet.
Yeah, there's a lot of a lot of
interesting things you can do
around a very simple protocol.
Which RSS, which I really hope
will stick around. I mean, this
has its limitations, obviously.
And
you know, what I heard a lot of
a lot of over the past few days,
people emailing, even saying,
Can I do video with this?
Because YouTube is like, gonna,
I'm gonna take my channel down
and like, yes, yes. All this
stuff works. It's there.
Yeah, that's going to be an
interesting journey. And I've
resisted doing video, but even a
platform comparison between
YouTube and podcasting. And RSS
is, it's kind of having its
moment right now. Because we've
seen what the, the, you know,
the owned platform looks like
YouTube came in, they bought out
a lot of indie video people at
the beginning, they captured all
that market, and now they own
it. And, you know, for a while
creators, were happy to publish
on there, and have YouTube, pay
them add, you know, add, share,
or whatever. But once somebody
owns the means of distribution.
So now that means of production
have been that's been
democratized, everybody now has
the ability to turn on a
microphone, or a camera, and
create their own stuff. But now
what's being locked down is
distribution. And, again, you
know, especially during the
pandemic, some creators saw
their YouTube ad share, get cut,
and you know, all sudden the
algorithm is no longer showing
their stuff. And in podcasting,
with, with Spotify, we now have
the same kind of risk is there's
this big platform that wants to
be the YouTube of audio. And I
do think there's, this is kind
of a pivotal moment in
podcasting, our podcast creators
going to go the same ways. You
check YouTubers and be owned by
the platform? Or are they going
to keep their independence and
figure out other ways of, you
know, making the money work?
Well, that that is partially up
to you partially up to the app
developers and partially up to
us for and I'll take some of
that responsibility to get the
word out there that there's an
entire universe, we are making a
difference. There's been, we're
seeing the uptake, in not only
just apps, they're integrating
who see the see the value in it,
we'll see exactly how I think
the experience is what it comes
down to. And that's why you've
always seen people have their
favorite podcast app, because it
has that one little feature they
love. And sure a lot of people
like I just whatever Apple has
is fine. But once they
introduced to that one extra
feature they like it could be
simple as a share. And features
is where we're gonna win
initially. And money is where
we're definitely going to move
ahead. Which brings me to
podcasting. 2.02 point out where
you guys are, I think, as
integrated and compliant as
possible at this point, am I
correct? in assuming Yeah,
because you guys as transcript
transcripts, of course, the
logtag funding chapters
soundbite
and we don't have we don't have
all that stuff. You don't have
all of that. We only have two of
them
locked in funding, whereas
we're as compliant as we can be.
Technologically because we
don't. Right now have support
for chapters. Shame on you.
That that was Adam's way of
public shaming.
Actually, I was looking at new
podcast apps calm and it says
that you have all those
features. So I guess I was
wrong. Yes.
That's the way to light a fire
under arrest, I guess.
Well, it's on the side. So you
better have you better had a
good luck.
Good luck, by the way. I don't
know which site that is. Yeah.
So we Yeah, we do support
locking and, and funding. And we
do integrate with the podcast
index API directly so people can
just submit with one click.
Very nice. And yet, what is your
roadmap look like? Do you think
you'll be supporting chapters
And transcripts?
Yeah, I think so I mean,
transcripts. Yeah, we have to
build a new way for people to
upload those people often ask
for auto transcription, which I
don't. I mean, we'll have to tie
into a different third party
service for that, if we do
that think otter.ai may have the
may have an API that you can
access for that. Okay.
Yeah, it's it's one of those
things where we kind of want to
do it right, instead of do it
fast.
So what can we do to help?
I mean, you, you guys got to
keep blazing trail. That's the
whole point, just because just
because we're a few miles behind
you, that doesn't mean you
shouldn't keep blazing the
trail,
I guess maybe I mean it
differently. So I realize with
my developer hat on, which is a
very nice paper, I realize what,
you know, when when chapters
comes out, and, you know, it's
like, oh, and here it is, and
you just put this JSON to this
file over here. I realized that,
oh, wait a minute. That means
you guys got to figure out a way
internally to have yet another
file. That is that is hosted and
loaded and linked and cetera.
And I know that takes, you know,
that takes some thought and some
time to integrate that to have
it worked the right way. So yes.
So when moving forward, as we
come up with stuff. Do you have
preferences from your end of the
ecosystem? Like, well, gee, if
we could put it all in the RSS,
that would be better, because x,
y, and z? Or we'd rather have
all this stuff external? I mean,
that's the kind of stuff I'm
looking for. How can we blaze
the trail and not leave just
ashes for you to just sweep?
I mean, I would personally
prefer it not to be the rssb
just because those things get
huge. I mean, if you stuffed the
entire transcript into an RSS
feed, yeah, I would use that I'm
with you. Yeah.
Yeah, that's what all the hosts
are said. Yeah. Adding
on adding on external things
like that to external URLs, I
think is probably the way to go.
Yes, this this was said by and I
was reading this and something
that pod news headset had had in
their newsletter. And then think
Tom Ross, who posted this is a
quote from Dave's Rob. So Rob, I
know he knows his name,
charitable and he said closed
versus open as Spotify expands
their suite of exclusive
content. And others, like Amazon
and Apple enter the fray will
begin to see more competition
between closed platforms and the
open RSS based ecosystem. I
believe that open open ecosystem
can continue to thrive.
Competition is healthy after
all, but the open ecosystem will
need to continue to innovate as
an industry to serve listeners,
creators and advertisers well,
and I think that like, I think
that's right, because my
response to that was, I mean, if
you have, if you have a podcast
that has all, like, if you just
go ahead and think extrapolate
out to the end of phase two, and
let's just say that we are of
the namespace, and let's just
say that we have location in
there, we have person in there,
we have named seasons in there.
And we also have social media
links in there. If you
extrapolate out to the end of
phase two, and you have
potentially 10, new tags that
give you all this extra stuff. I
mean, like that blows away any
closed platform, Spotify doesn't
have all that stuff. Apple
podcast, doesn't have all that
stuff, just Stitcher. None of
them have that on their closed
platforms, that that open, that
paves the way for the open
ecosystem, to not just compete,
but to actually just bypass. I
mean, like, go miles ahead of
any closed system that I know
of.
Mm hmm. And on that note, I
think where we can actually help
you is we were front lines,
we've got customers coming to us
every day that want to
accomplish things. And, you
know, like, named seasons is one
of them. It's like, Why can I
only choose a number? Oh, yeah,
this is a big one for us, too.
And for NPR? Yeah, we're doing
this I
I'm listening to unfinished
right now. And it's unfinished,
but it's that they're short
Creek season. But I just search
for that in a in an app. It's
like, which one is this is
they're stuffing it into the
episode title. It's just, it's
not great. And so I think when,
when folks on the ground level,
like us, are interacting with
customers and real podcasters
and they're saying, they're just
trying to figure out how to get
things done. How come I can't
name a season? Well, that's not
possible right now. And to have
folks like you that are opening
up that possibility, you know,
that's a, that's a could be a
big deal for us. It allows us to
build features that people want.
Now how when so when you have
customers saying well, I want to
be able to name it X, Y or Z and
then we have the and that'll be
in phase two. We have the
seasons tag, a season tag, but
that will be likely require one
of, you know, five or six
different apps that are truly
compliant with it. And I don't
know. And Dave chime in if this
will break. If this will break
ordinate does not show up at
all, unlike the apple podcast
app, you know, so how do you can
you sell that to your clients by
saying, well, it's new, and
here's the apps that do it. But
it's not it's not the Apple App.
Yeah. I mean, there's, there's
no, there's already this mess in
in podcasting. So we're always
having to explain, you know,
why, what, why can't I add a
private podcasting is huge for
us. How come? I can't add it to
Spotify? Well, that's
not the opposite of the
opposite. Yeah.
It's a tricky, tricky thing,
too, when you're building out an
interface for someone to even
manage their podcast with us,
right? So you if we support
named seasons, but Apple doesn't
support that, you did then have
to have like a different input
for specially for Apple season
numbers. And then you have
another iPad, or a named one.
And I'm working
on that, by the way. That's one
of the I'm, I'm hopefully I'm
presenting the namespace to the
Apple podcast team in January.
Cool. So we'll see. Cool, man,
how can we help with that? Yeah.
Show show show up with the mob.
Well show more podcasts that
have this in their feed. I mean,
that's, that's really that's
really the way it's, it's a
chicken in the egg. You know,
it's, it's, and so yeah. And my
next question to you guys, would
be a little bit further down the
road. Are you open to
integrating with other parties
to who do like lightning nodes
specific stuff so that you can
offer that to your customers?
But it would be a third party
that's doing that? Or is that
something you want to do
yourself? Are you interested at
all when it comes to the real
time? Again, totally
honest with you? I don't know
what you're talking about. Maybe
Hey, man, I looked at your
Wikipedia What the hell's wrong
with you?
Just say yes. Just say yes,
john.
I'm sorry. Okay.
We didn't I didn't even know
there was a lightning
documentation until until 15
minutes? Certainly. Yes.
Yes, well, you guys need to see
this because we have, there's a
tag that an experimental tag
that will be in phase two,
what's called the value block.
And in that block our payment
digital payment addresses for
Bitcoin but on the lightning
network, which is kind of an off
chain, and you can stream it in
real time. So at this moment,
while people are listening to
the show people who are on the
Sphinx app, which is the only
one that supports everything
right now, they're sending 100
satoshis or less, perhaps, per
minute to Dave and I, because
we're the host of the show, we
produce it. But also, Spinks
takes 1% and 1% is going to the,
to the podcast index, and that's
infinitely dividable. So you can
say I want 5% of this episode to
go towards the guy who's doing
chapters for us. And so it's
kind of a royalty system. It's a
real time payment system. And
it's all built on the pledge
model, which is similar to
donations except you don't have
to pay upfront you pay as you
go, you really you play, and
then you pay. So it's it works,
whether you have money in your
wallet or not. So that's that
we're really driving that so
that we can get some some real
revenue flowing amongst podcast,
app developers, but also much
more reason for hosting
companies to be involved.
Because, you know, now when you
have streaming, streaming money,
you know, there's all kinds of
services that can be exchanged
for that.
Yeah. Yeah. I mean, with stuff
like that, that really does have
to come from customers,
customers have to be saying,
Hey, we want this this thing.
And that. So I think, I think
we, I mean, we, if it's if it's
relatively easy to implement,
maybe we didn't. Anyway,
I will say that I mean, I think
the the funding, funding
donating whatever you want to
call it, pledging money to
podcasters themselves, I think
that's to make this whole open
ecosystem work. That's gonna be
that's huge.
We're gonna have that we're
gonna have to, because the
eventually some of these other
pay routes will just get, it'll
be too easy to cut it off, you
know, right.
Hey, I just sent you some clips.
Adam. Yeah, I got him here.
Okay, and the see the, the thing
that gets me about that, is that
the, the straight now everything
is there's a push for streaming
ads. Yeah. And they they're
streaming ad insertion or
dynamic ad insertion. Mm hmm.
And I'm just
such as it not work. Not working
for you today. Is it not so? So
the way I understand it, the way
I understand it, and maybe john
and Justin can do a better job
is he got the streaming ad
insertion, which is within
Spotify universe only. And that
is, so you can't Fast Forward
has a whole bunch of hope. It's
their bait, you're not
downloading a file and listening
to it on the fly, you're being
streamed bits that they
predetermine, and the dynamic ad
insertion is where they inserted
on the way out when you download
it, or as you're listening to it
downloading streaming to an app
outside of any closed ecosystem,
I think that's what it is the
difference? Yeah.
Any of those? Are y'all doing
any of the dynamic ads?
We had, we had mapped out what
we call dynamic content. We'd
map this out early on maybe a
year and a half ago. And we
ultimately shelved it partly
because we're a two person team.
And we have to weigh anything we
build, like, is this complexity
worth it? Because we want the
app to stay relatively simple.
And we still want to have a
relatively good life. We don't
want to be maintaining a bunch
of complexity.
Yes, streaming ads, and dynamic
dynamic ads and dynamic, dynamic
content. It's such, it just
opens up such a can of worms,
for support. I mean, it would,
it would have been a large
amount of work to get that to
work. You know, we
interviewed Dan Benjamin from
Firestarter a few weeks ago. And
he he said that the funny thing
is that his the customers that
he has that are the ones
clamoring for dynamic ad
insertion are all the ones that
are probably going to make very
little or no money from of
course,
what we've we've seen this very
thing we've had people say, Hey,
we're leaving, because you don't
have dynamic ad insertion. And
many times they come back 345
months later, because it even
look at anchors ad network,
there's very few people making
any money on on that network.
And it's just ads, there's a ton
of podcasters who want to run
ads, and there's not that much
supply. So and and there's,
there's more big shows than
ever. So I don't think ads for
the indie creator is the answer.
That's really interesting.
Because Spotify has the inverse.
They have jacked up all their
advertisers. And they can't they
don't they can't convert enough
people to listen. So that's why
they had to buy megaphone. Yeah,
they had to get it they need to
be selling their ads in dynamic
ad insertion because they can't
fill the orders.
Because there's a volume like
they need more. Yeah, they
can't.
Well, just because you have 300
million people who use your app
to listen to music doesn't mean
that bringing in Joe Rogan
converts everybody to podcasts,
all of a sudden, they got they
got a little trajectory there.
And yes, and I'm not so sure
it's the same customer.
I honestly don't understand why.
Like, if you look at SoundCloud,
SoundCloud has been doing
dynamic ad insertion forever,
for both music and podcasts.
They're losing tons of money
every year. like
losing stuff. That's that's the
that's the business model.
Look at quarterly reports for
any of these companies that have
advertising. They're all down
right now. So it's not making
the big megacorps any money.
It's not really making that many
podcasters any money. I'm not
saying I think ad should be
completely done away with but I
think host read ads are are
better than dynamically inserted
ads. And there's other ways for
podcasters to make money. They
aren't dynamically inserted ads.
Yeah. So Dave, you had some
example of some shitty ads is
that what we're gonna do here?
Because I like it.
Oh, yeah. So the the play play
clip one now this is not this is
not podcast is not for Spotify
or anything like that. This is
from YouTube. But it is this
video went around yesterday. And
somebody might texted it to me
and I was watching it. And it's
uh, you know, you had these
critical moments in the video
where this guy's given testimony
in Congress. Right? He's he's
about to say something. Bam, ad,
like halfway through a word.
Play clip, one about hearing I
hope your testimony would be as
impactful today. Cory. Senator,
thank you and thank you for
pulling this here.
US Attorney john Durham has
filed the first criminal charges
investigation and
yeah, it's interesting because I
think that that video was
actually taken off of Facebook.
Facebook, was a Senate hearing
was the immediate was like, hey,
screw this, we'll just put that
you'll go away and we'll make
some money. Beautiful.
The best one, the best. One is
clip three that played out on
August 27.
I want to be clear. I am not
here as a politician or to
dramatists or sensationalizing
what I'm recommending. I'm going
to be very clear and very
simple. All I ask Hey,
Have you ever seen those shots?
That's fantastic. So the
podcasters, who are clients who
are clamoring for dynamic ad
insertion?
Do you want your show to sound
like that? a horrible experience
for your customer reminds me so
much of early cable when I was
at MTV in the mid to late 80s.
And, you know, Manhattan, it'd
be channel, I don't know, 23 or
something, maybe a little
higher. But, but, you know, at
the time, it's like, people were
laughing at cables. Like, that's
not real television, no one's
gonna advertise on cable. And it
really was seen as just second
rate dumb. And you'd get these
local ads that would be program,
which is at the time was, you
know, a guy in a room with
pneumatic videotapes. And you
know, shoving them in and
hitting the machines and
switching. So you'd always see
like, half of a local car
dealership, and they'll be boom
and go to a jewelry commercial,
boom, go back to something else,
there's a mess. And it still it
still has those problems.
It doesn't seem terribly
intelligent. I mean, it seems
like there should be insertion
points for some of those
commercials. It's weird that
they automatically choose a
point and throw it in, in the
middle of someone's speech and
not too much tactical side of it
messes up chapters in chapter
timing, and oh,
yeah, that's the thing. This is
this is the sliding II, the
slippery slope is first you
start with manually choosing
your insertion points. And then
you're like, wow, the machines
can just do this for us. Let's
just let the machines choose the
insertion points. And then, you
know, now you just have machines
programming everything for you.
And yeah, it's not very, it's
not good radio,
in the last three in the last
three months, like if this same
thing happens to to to the
podcast platforms, like Spotify.
And those guys, if the same
thing happens there. That
happened on YouTube in the last
three months, YouTube has become
almost unwatchable.
Oh, yeah, it's three ads at the
beginning. It's, it's, it's
unstoppable.
It's all over. And it was quick
to me, like it went from being
sort of tolerable to it was
almost like
overnight. Yeah. You see,
YouTube has the, I've looked at
all of this, Dave. YouTube has
the opposite. They have. I mean,
they have so much advertising,
they have the inventory, but
they just double down. They were
doing political ads on
children's shows. Which is,
which is which is basically
ripping the advertiser off,
because it's not the target
market. This
Yeah, I mean, I see my daughter,
my 10 year old, she'll watch.
Like, those YouTubers that play
video games, she'll watch like
a, it's totally some kids video
game. And she's sitting there
watching it. And it's obvious
that the target demographic for
this thing is like a 12 year
old. And they're in they'll
throw up a, like some kind of
pharmaceutical ad. And what a
waste of money. The bottom
line is that if you don't
control the distribution, you
can't really control the
advertising and take it from me,
I, I started one of the first
podcast networks I saw that was
not possible to do, unless
you're going to just create
junk. There's a whole lot of a
whole lot of problems that comes
along with it. And and we're
trying to keep this open in
this, that's the whole point is
to have it open and just not
really appropriate for the
typical programmatic ads that
they're trying to shoehorn it
into.
Yeah, I think the for the
podcasters, especially folks
just starting out. I mean,
again, we see a lot of patterns
with people signing up, Hey, why
are you signing up? And you
know, some people just want to
try out a show and whatever, but
a lot of people are trying to
start a business, they're trying
to earn some money. And, and,
you know, like, right, in the
United States, I think, in 2020,
there was three times more
businesses started because of
the pandemic, like people are
hungry, kind of metaphorically.
And, sure, sure. And, and so
the, and I think, I mean, we can
be cynical about that and say,
Wow, they're just never going to
make the money. Why even try, I
think the attraction to dynamic
ad insertion, and anchor, and,
you know, these things that
offer the the opportunity for
money, like the idea of although
there could be some money is, is
pretty powerful. And what we
what folks need to see is that
there are other ways of earning
revenue. And, I mean, you guys
are talking about lightning
again, which I have, I don't
really understand but like john
and i have a very simple kind of
monthly supporter program for
our podcast. And it was
basically a show about us
building a software business.
It's, it's, it's,
is that the SAS podcast?
Yeah. Yeah. It's, it's kind of
like branded content and people
were Excited to support us?
monthly? Exactly. Oh, yeah. Oh,
yeah, no, this is and there was
moments where the monthly
support was making more than the
software. So
so so I'll give you I'll give
you my pitch. When when it comes
to podcast listening. So with
the no agenda show, we've
converted between three and 4%
of the entire audience to donate
money. Hmm. IAB numbers, 100
million Americans listen to a
podcast regularly average one
hour per day, I think we can
convert 1% of that 100 million
to give money to a podcast. In
fact, a large percentage of that
1% probably already does it
through PayPal, Patreon. Other
ways.
Mm hmm.
If you value and this is where
the pitch gets fun, if you value
that hour at $1, and everyone's
using an app that will send in
increments $1 an hour to the
podcast or listening to that's a
million dollars a day now that
is flowing through podcasting.
Yeah, I mean, that's a great
dream. And that's
just the bare minimum.
The problem with your pitch,
though, is that you're gonna
have to get those 100 million
people on some sort of app and
understanding No, no, only one
machine, only 1 million, I
don't need 100 million, I need 1
million.
That's true. I mean, well, I
guess it all depends on how, how
it funnels down. If you've got,
if you've got a if you're saying
that one in 10 people are
willing to donate, are you
saying one in 10 are willing to
donate but are also like going
to have some sort of blockchain?
just it just a different app,
just a different app? And you
can put money into the app? It's
it's not. It's not anything
funky? It's just an app? Yeah,
it's nothing. It's not.
It doesn't, it doesn't
necessarily, it could just be
pre loading it in some way. Some
sort of tokens.
You can load it with money out,
you can load it with your credit
card. It's literally that
simple. Yeah, I
think that that that's probably
more palatable. Because the way
people pay for pay for Patreon
right now, is I think they go
well, you know, I could probably
spend about 40 $45 a month on
this. And then they kind of
divvy it up. They're like, Okay,
guys, personally,
this is exactly the same in
reverse, where and I believe
there will be apps that you buy
with $25 already on it. Oh,
yeah. And then anything, you
listen to the payments
automatic, and you can value you
so like, Oh, I want this to be
like $2 a minute. Yeah, it was
150 cents a minute, you can set
that individually, all you have
to do is, is either purchase a
pre loaded app, which you can
then top up or get the app and
then either buy with a credit
card or if you have Bitcoin, you
can put it in?
Yeah, you know, the interesting
thing is, in consumer
psychology, is it feels like
consumers need some sort of
brand space or some sort of
mental space in their head in
order to justify the the
payment. So as an example, like
before, if I came to you guys
and said, Hey, I'm thinking
about building a, you know,
consumer product, and I want you
to pay me $100 before I build
it, and I'm going to go to a
bunch of people do this, folks
would be like, now like that.
That doesn't, that doesn't
excite me. But as soon as you
have Kickstarter as a thing, it
becomes a space in your head of
like, Oh, well, this is a thing.
Like, people do this. And so
then it's like all support a
Kickstarter, that becomes
normalized. Or Patreon, I want
you to donate to me monthly. How
many people in early blogs and
podcasts tried that and it
didn't work? And then all of a
sudden, you have this Patreon
kind of space, and habit, or
whatever it is. And people are
like, Oh, yeah, I'll do that.
Okay, so I'll address that. One,
the donation model has been
working for a long time, or what
we call the value for value
model. With just PayPal, people
are lazy. So Patreon took away a
lot of the issues for people who
are lazy and don't want to do
administration, which is really
software as a service is very,
very good idea. Please
understand that Patreon has
canceled lots of people. So you
know, Patreon is not the end all
be all because they literally
have canceled people from their
accounts. The beauty of
podcasting is that it is its own
marketing machine. So once
there's an app that can scale,
so Spinks app does not scale for
the purpose of podcasting the
way I'm thinking of it. Yeah.
When I say on no agenda, if I
say hey, check this out. I can
guarantee you I'll have 10,000
people using the app tomorrow
and then It'll end they'll
figure out how to put money in
it. And then when that happens,
they'll they will communicate
with the other podcasters they
listen to, and say, Hey, you
know, you can make money out,
you can get money while I'm
listening to your podcast, why
don't you put this value block
into your feed or go to
transistor? And they have it all
set for you? Yeah, that's,
that's how the rollout will
work.
Yeah, and is, it just seems I
agree that that could that could
possibly work. The, the thing
I'm just noticing is that
there's this weird thing with
consumer behavior of, like, it's
just weird to me that at scale,
like Patreon, kind of built
monthly donations at scale, they
gave it a name and a space. And
it happened before. But once
there was a name, and there's
alternatives to Patreon, right?
There's member fall, there's all
sorts of other things. But
people have their little
Patreon, like wallet, you know,
it's like, this is my little,
this is a little stash for
Patreon. And they've created
space in their life for that
thing. And that's kind of my
dream for whatever unit like
that the donation namespace that
you're talking about. If there
was a maybe it's called, or it's
called, it's called the podcast,
wallet, podcast. Well, maybe
that's it. As long as it's not,
as in some sort of mimetic way.
Listeners adopt at scale this
idea of, Oh, yeah, like normal
people, like me have a podcast
wallet that I put money in every
month, and support the shows I
love. Like that's a normal
thing. Everybody's doing it. And
that's the that seems to always
be the the tricky part is how do
you get this to scale? And part
of it might be everyone
broadcasting about it. Although,
you know, sometimes that doesn't
work. I don't know what all the
pieces are. It's there's a bunch
of things that have to come
together for it to work. So we
have a test environment with
just, I think, maybe five
podcasts
as nine nine.
Yeah. And how many people? Do
you think that are? 50? Yeah. So
what are we sent through in one
month? $1,000 worth of value was
running through these shows?
Yeah. Yeah. And that's just
that's just the test group. I
mean, it it's, this is this is
in the station getting ready to
go. I mean, once once we have a
an app that that is outbound on
the sending part was just a
technicality. Mm hmm. I think
it's going to go pretty quick.
It's not something that is it's
not something that's easy. For
me, as far as you know, like,
there's been a lot of plumbing
that's gone into, but then I
think I see what you're saying.
Justin, I think you're, you're
saying that there's a it's more
like a there's a space for not
really a brand, but like a
concept. Word whether
Patreon is a concept, that's
totally a concept that they
become the Xerox of donation, I
completely agree. Yeah, it's
mostly mostly a cultural issue.
Sure. How do you how do you get
exactly how do you get the
culture to okay with
the culture to me is cashapp.
This is this is your your next
if not your current podcast?
listener?
Venmo cash app.
Yeah, yeah. Venmo cash, the cash
app does does Bitcoin, you can
send Bitcoin, you can load up
your podcast wallet with cash
app. Even better if cash app had
a button that said, Here's your
podcast. No. Yeah, they could do
that tomorrow.
Yeah. How many of yours? How
many of yours customers do you
think are trying to hurt our
podcasting? Just because they,
right, just just just for fun,
and versus how many or do you
think are like trying to make
money?
Oh, man. I mean, I think I don't
think any, any of the indie
shows would turn down somebody
supporting their show, like I
but actively seeking it. I mean,
qualitatively, maybe 25 30%.
That makes me happy. That makes
me happy to hear because I'm
like, you want podcast. We all
want podcasting to be an
ecosystem. That's monetizable.
And people can make money from
it. But then, but what one of
the things that makes it
beautiful is that there's also
this very large percent of
people who podcast just for just
because they enjoy it, and it's
fun, and they really don't ever
care about making money. Yeah,
yeah, I agree. And it's one of
the reasons like we we have a
pot, this, you pay a
subscription, but you can start
multiple shows on a
subscription.
Oh, that's nice.
And so the whole idea was once I
started podcasting, I was like,
Whoa, I want to I want to sunset
this show and start something
else I want to, I want to create
a five episode series, and then
to have to go in and pay every
time I wanted to flex my
creativity was like, I'm just
not, you know. So I, yeah,
there's a lot of people that
just do it for fun. And I mean,
those are our favorite
customers, the people that you
know, are are just like the
people that are actually less
fun are the people that are
really trying to optimize? Yes,
like, john, john sometimes gets,
you know, folks that are like,
How come? How come? My download
stats on transistor are two off
what I'm seeing in apple? Yeah,
podcast.
listener from Denmark, but
they're not showing up? I don't
know how to track that one down.
Exactly. But
yeah, there's a whole episode of
buzz buzz cast recently when
those guys were talking about
some stats that all sudden
showed up from like, some
obscure town in Washington. Oh,
yeah.
What was the reason behind that
was some policy server so
he was like a something or, or
maybe some sort of like God, IP
address to like geolocation
errors or something like that.
But it's like, people get so
worked up about oh, my God, I
had 100 listeners,
my favorite story, when this is
in 1994, or five, somewhere
around there, and I built my
company was building Planet
reebok.com for Reebok. And back
then, you know, stats are you
would now have stats, we'll do
some kind of grep the log for
you. And somehow that God, I'm
not kidding. Somehow that,
excuse me, that got communicated
through an account, person to
the client. And the client was
like, holy crap, crap, we got
like 5 million people looking at
us this past month, of course,
these were hits. These were
server entries. You know, like
every image on the page,
everything was a was a log
entry. And then you got stuck.
It's like, holy crap, how do we
tell this person was probably a
fraction of that. And we're
like, fuck it, let them think
whatever they did.
That was the golden age of the
web. I hit count.
All you needed, you just needed
a counter.
We miss you. It is frustrating.
On the one hand, like I get it,
I mean, it's, you know, they're,
they're small time podcasters.
They just want they want an
audience. And they want to know
what
everybody wants the feedback.
And this is, this is why I'm
pushing so hard. Here, where
podcasts and gets his ass
kicked, is in the real time
comments that people I mean, do
on YouTube, when so the one is
streaming live. And even if you
go back, you see the chat scroll
by you know, of what, what past.
But really just the comments
itself is is a huge feature of
what YouTube offers. And you
know, this idea of super, super
chats, you know, where I throw
you five bucks, or 10 bucks, all
of that. And all of that can be
done with the technology that
we're looking at and
implementing. And that's where
it has to come from, because and
I think that that is just the
idea that you have almost like
the hearts being thrown at you
in a in a periscope, or
Instagram Live. That's the kind
of stuff that is that audiences
thrive on. That's how they can
participate, be a part of it.
And
all the big podcasts have chat
rooms. Sure. I mean, sure does.
Take me know, once you get to a
certain size, you know, they'll
want chat rooms because
everybody in this world
would love to have every single
podcast app that I used to just
log into our IRC chat room,
boom, just sit on the app and
and troll along while you're
listening with other people. And
you know, even better if it's
synchronized, but I see that
experience we've we've been
experiencing it for a couple
months now with the Sphinx chat.
It's fun.
Yeah,
it really is.
Think the difference though
between podcasting and obviously
YouTube is you don't your
eyeballs are not a thing all the
time right like my phones in my
pocket and I'm walking around
Yeah, but it's it I mean even
audio people will do this on
YouTube just an audio show just
crazy. How how deeply ingrained
that is. Here's a question
though. are you guys looking at
some different types of
compression etc. If for people
who want to do video podcast
because obviously the problem
with video podcasts is file
size, transfer costs, etc.
Yeah. Have
you been looking at that?
We haven't yet gonna take this.
Yeah,
yeah, we haven't yet. I mean,
there's, yeah, there's a number
of ways to do it. But
I mean, right now is the time
and people are looking for an
alternative.
Yeah, yeah. The end of the day.
The uproar of them removing all
the Joe Rogan videos off YouTube
has been huge, especially
in comments.
Yeah, yeah. And even you think
about going back to something,
you're saying, Adam, if I could
tap my air pods, when somebody
says something that I like, and
it and it rings the metaphorical
Bell, and gives them a little
donation or a little feedback or
something, that would that would
be an incredible audio
experience. And audio first,
right? I'm walking around air
pods are on. And there's a way
to, of course, right, Apple
would have to agree to this. But
there's a way of me interacting
with, hey, let me ring the bell
right now. And give them some
feedback. Like I like that joke,
or that was a good point for
Yeah,
we haven't spent a lot of money.
Yeah, we have this actually,
it's integrated already is
called a boost. So you can boost
in this amount of satoshis.
Which by itself is, is part of
the game is you know, come up
with a cool number, like I'll
boost 404 Dave, I think is doing
133 or something like that. And
then as a podcaster we go back,
you can, you know, see all the
boosts on the timeline, you can
scroll through it and see where
people were, as you would say,
we're ringing the bell.
Yeah, I love that idea.
Maybe listening and all of a
sudden, you'll have like this
string of that come through, and
you're like, Oh, I don't know
what just happened. But
something exact somebody said
something. cool idea. I
mean, I I'll have to look in and
kind of read up on what you guys
have been doing. There's a lot
of seems like there's a lot of
pieces that need to get, we
got to get you in the test
group. So you can gather
as long as long as whatever ends
up being as easy to use for
customers and casters and
platforms at least.
That's your job. We got all the
complicated.
I have fun, john.
really put that somewhere on our
shoulders.
What What do you think y'all
will? What is the next part of
the namespace that y'all think
you will work on?
I mean, I think having a spot
for people to upload transcripts
is that's that's a natural one.
People have wanted that for a
while. So yeah, I think
transcripts is and I don't think
it's that hard. Even if we just
started with like, you can
upload an SRT file or something
like that. Yeah,
you know, let him get away with
saying what's hard and what's
not. Right?
How hard can it be?
Yeah, you just copy and paste of
like texts? Yeah, probably
transcripts. I mean, chapters
are a little we don't support
those directly. I mean, those
are tough, because it does tie
into the actual mp3, the
chapters themselves the chapter
tags.
Now, not in this not we are we
have different chapters now.
Okay, yeah, it's a JSON file.
It's an external JSON file, and
you just you just put an captors
element in there, and then a URL
to the JSON file, and you're
done.
And here's what's cool about it.
If you think of something that
your customers might like,
because this is part of this
podcast in 2.0, where you're
part of the band, or you're in
the band, so I have community
chapters. So this, this JSON
file with the chapters is
external, it's it's referenced
in the RSS feed, and hyper
capture, which is an iOS app
giveaway, a simple way for
anybody to just tap it and say,
Oh, hold on a second. I want to
place a chapter here. And then
there's a back end as a
podcaster, I can approve those
links, I can add a picture to
it. Now there's a few other
things you can do, which will
start expanding. So now now
people can start submitting very
much like a, you know, like a
timeline on SoundCloud, you can
submit either a comment or
chapter marker or a URL link.
And, and in my case, I just use
the API. There's an API endpoint
for each episode. And I just use
that whenever whenever a 2.0 app
comes along, and it finds the
chapters it just puts them right
in right away ended updates on
the fly.
Yeah, yeah, that is that is
cool. I think chapters is a is a
cool. I'm also really excited
about Sam bytes. Yeah, from from
kind
of the same thing as we figured
out.
Yeah, sound bites is an
interesting one. Because in the
discovery, like if podcasts have
a discovery problem, or
whatever, the problem is that
you get to Apple podcasts. And
then there's 200 episodes that
are all two hours long. It's
like, Well, how do I get a quick
sense of what this what this
episode was about? Or what this
man is about?
You want caste coverage? Have
you tried that app yet? No.
caste coverage is the craziest
fucking app in the world. It
gives you you fired up and it
just grabs a random podcast
dumps you in a place in the file
randomly. So you can listen to
Do it and then you don't like it
hit the next one. It's perfect
for finding shit.
Yes, the scan is the Scan button
on the FM radio. Yeah, and
it should have it should be
using sound bites now it's just
taking something at random. But
think about how cool it will be
with sound bites for
discoverability
pod verse two, you know, podcast
is all about sound bites they
pod is a pod first
pod verse.fm. Yep,
yeah. And then you basically
just as community sound bites,
and people are doing it, and it
publishes it back out into
chapters into chapters format.
Yeah, we'll have to look into
the chapter stuff. I mean, it's
I think it again, it has to be
sort of seamless for the
customer. And I don't know if
necessary know if we'd want
people editing tables of chapter
data. If they can, if we can
pull the chapters right out of
the mp3 if they already had it.
That's obviously better.
Oh, that's a cool idea.
Yeah, that's what this was some
vendors, some holsters or do any
pull it in, and then you just
scan the frame headers, and
yeah, Addy three stuff out and
build the JSON out of it.
Mm hmm. That would be that's
what,
that's why we did the Jason.
That's why we did the JSON is
because mp3 embedded chapters
are just, they've never taken
off. Right. And it's, it's too,
I'm not gonna say it's
difficult, but most people's,
like, most people are uploading
their mp3 to the host. And
they're not gonna sit there and
go through there and use an
editing tool to do that sort of
thing. They're gonna upload it
to the host. And then once you
have that point, you really
don't want to do a bunch of re
encoding and that sort of thing
to me. But see,
y'all just I just want to say
you technical boys, don't miss
the point here of the community
aspect. So when you're baking it
into your file, you know, that's
one way only, and people only
get to see that as bookmarks or
whatever you want to call them.
When you get the audience out
there who can say, Oh, shit,
this is a great joke, I want to
mark this here, or I want to put
a funny picture here, I want to
link to something. Now Now
you're cooking with gas, because
that's what people want. They
want to participate.
Cat chapters go both ways. It's
not just like one direction.
No, because you can have as long
as you can, you have an
interface for other people to
edit the JSON, which I see which
still has a back end for
approval. So you know, people
aren't putting porn in there,
although very appropriate in
this show, then I can approve,
you approve it. And it's all
rudimentary. And it's basically
just a list of start types, you
know, start time URL, image URL.
That's it. So yeah, and it's
just, uh, you know, just, each
time you add a chapter, it's
just a row is added to the
interface. So it's, and then it
spits out the the JSON on the
other end. But that's what makes
it cool is that anyone can edit
it. And I want this to be cross
app. If it could be two, I want
someone on one app to be able to
do something on a chapter and
then someone else can add their
own. And before you know it, you
got comments, you know, this
this could move quite quickly
this way.
Yeah, or even the thing I
thought about if we realized
that people the reason people
supported us monthly for our
show, because we had all these
tiers and staff and you know,
benefits. What they wanted was
the shout out at the end of the
show. Exactly. And we have this
big long list of people yeah,
and they want the shout out
that's what they want. And so
now imagine if you know if you
you get the shout out but then
you could you're one of the
supporters you can take a
picture of yourself and send it
back and now you appear in the
in the chapter artwork right?
It's like what like that. That's
good. Dave Jim cat.
There you go. Speaking of which,
Dave let's thank our three
people. Oh, yeah. Because we're
I value if you don't mind for a
second here, john and Justin, we
are done. I
we do that transition perfectly.
Yes, we do.
Our value for whatever you
whatever value you get out of
this project as we are pushing
podcasting forward. We're in it
to make it work for everybody.
And the only way to keep the
machines humming is through the
charity of Dave and myself. a
cast of 1000s and your actual
financial donations we look at
the three T's time talent and
treasure. What do we think today
Dave?
Well, the The first one is not
an actual donation. It's more of
a it is a donation but it's not
just a money donation. It's
thinking Ben and Alberto at RSS
calm because they sponsored on
our behalf for pod news to brand
their tech section of the
newsletter with podcasts index
that was really nice. And it was
it was it that's a nice little
blurb we got Oh, yeah, yeah,
it's a piece of placement. Yeah,
really appreciated that. That's
that's that's incredibly
valuable, that brings people
over. Really appreciate that,
guys.
I've talked a bit A few times
over the last couple of months,
and he's just just a top notch
guy. Great. Very cool. Yeah. And
he and he really wanted to do
that for us. So that's, I don't
know how to value that. But I'm
sure it's not cheap. And we
really appreciate that guys. The
we have a automatic payment a
new subscription. Ah, very nice.
Joseph maraca $5 a month and I
could not find a note from
Joseph, Bill.
Thank you, Joseph. It's
appreciated.
That's Yeah,
it's value. That's all we care
about.
And we also got a one time
donation of $7. From Earl
Hamilton. Again, no note. So
that took a really long time.
Well, we
have we appreciate any support
we get. And obviously we thank
all the developers and people
who are on podcast, index,
social, who are hanging out,
adding their two cents thinking
about stuff, writing stuff,
helping with the namespace with
specs, sometimes just making us
all laugh, it's, it's a lot of
fun. And it really throws back
to what we were talking about,
you know, the, the early days of
podcasting, a lot of that spirit
is, is alive and well
rejuvenated. It's really nice to
see how everyone is coming
together and making this work.
And it's its independence. But I
think, at 40 or 50% of the
market outside of apple and
Spotify. We're doing pretty darn
good. And you can support us
again, your time, your talent,
your treasure, go to podcast
index. org, at the bottom is a
big red Donate button. Or if you
have Spinks app where you got
some lightning payments, there's
a QR code, you can support us
there. And thanks again. It's
really appreciated.
And john and Justin both
personally promised to me that
they would donate $1,000 each.
So that's in there. I guess
that's right. Did I get those
numbers? Right? Yeah.
That's how we that's how we fund
distortion.
I like it. This is the new
model.
I will say I will add a route
the community aspect of this.
I'm in a in a Slack channel for
the open pockets analytics
group. And there is a channel in
there for indie podcast and host
companies. And like everyone is
really friendly and open to
talking about stuff and sharing
ideas. So like, cool. It's
really, it's really cool to see
that I know everyone is a little
bit worried about Spotify and
all these other making, oh,
we're here, we're here to fight
that man. That's what we're
doing here.
We're, everyone's everyone's on
board, I think everyone is.
So all we need is better
features, you know that
eventually they're going to redo
their app, and it will be much
better. But think about I
personally don't know if
they're, you know, their
purchases they've made if
they're going to be on the same
development trade. And they put
all their resources into
streaming ad insertion and
tracking, getting all that stuff
done. But you know, as we know,
there's these little things
like, you know, the 1.2 1.5
times speed, being able to share
something, be able to, to clip
something, there's all these
little features that they're
going to have to catch up on. We
have, I think 18 months
headstart, and if we really
push, they'll never they'll
never really get off the ground.
What's the What's your feeling
about Apple in all this case?
Because they've been kind of the
benevolent. I don't know what
they've kind of they hold a lot
of the balance of power right
now.
Oh, crap.
You don't think so? No, No,
they don't. They're they're in
irons right now, to use the
nautical term. So they are of
course contemplating doing a
podcasting plus a podcast plus,
which will be, you know, talent
and news, etc, which is a
burgeoning business for Apple. I
don't think it's, I mean, they
have to do it, I think, I don't
think they're particularly great
at it. They curate very kind of
middle of the road very safe, at
not really what people are
looking for anymore. They want
to be able to explore the unsafe
stuff. On the other hand,
they're totally stagnant with
with podcasting, and I've been
kicking them, I'm saying, look,
I you know, whatever you do, you
I would suggest adopting to the
new features that are coming
out. If you want to really play
both sides of the fence against
Spotify, you're already under
50% market share according to
the numbers, whatever it means.
So, yeah, go ahead and compete
if you really think that, you
know, the offering you can put
together is going to be worth
some type of subscription Where
again, you know, we're going
exactly the opposite. And
eventually, all these streaming
channels on television or your
Roku and all these apps, that
someone is gonna have to come up
with the universal way to do
that, because you can't have a
$300 bill and only listen to a
couple of shows, or watch a
couple of TV shows on every
different app. It's just it's,
it's very arrogant. We have five
Joe Rogan's outside of these
places. Hmm. And their audiences
are so powerful, that when
Michelle Obama's podcast
couldn't get the audience that
they had sold to the
advertisers, all of a sudden, it
was no longer just an exclusive
to Spotify. It's on every
podcast app everywhere, because
they can't get the audience who
has the audience? We have the
audience.
I see what you're saying. Yeah.
But in terms of like actual
listening apps, Apple is still
outside of Spotify. Apple still
has most of that, that that
market share, and I'm guessing a
lot of people are still like
when they discover podcasts for
the first time. They're not
downloading overcast, their most
normal, quote unquote, are, you
know that they use the apple
podcast app, I'm guessing
well, that the apple podcast app
stats, first percentage of
downloads has been dwindling.
It's been steadily going down.
And I think if you go back, if
you go back 10 years ago, you
would have never convinced
anybody that Internet Explorer
was not going to be the dominant
browser. And that and that your
grandmother would go out and
download a copy of Chrome onto
her computer, you would say,
well, just the thing that it
comes with, is the thing that
everybody's going to use. But
the the power of word of mouth,
it got to the point where people
were saying it became known
amongst everybody, that Internet
Explorer sucks, you need a
better browser, go download
Chrome. And it just became this
thing that everybody knows. And
I think that's happening in
podcasting. The Apple podcast
app is bad. It's just that
people are saying these, like,
I'm using overcast most of the
time, unless I'm listening to
Sphinx. If so when I whenever
somebody asked me, What should I
listen to, I'll just tell them
go get overcast, I think that
read that replicates out, and I
think it's having an overall
aggregate effect.
And, and also don't get stuck in
in the kind of what I call the
the holsters dilemma with and
that's what's been going on for
a decade, as well as Apple going
to support it. So now we have 15
apps that support these new
features. When I when I say to
someone, hey, and I, we have a
pretty big audience, I say, you
know, go get hyper capture, his
servers get overloaded, because
people are getting hyper
capture, and why are they
getting it because it has
features they like they can do
something with it. If I if I say
check out this episode, I almost
now instinctively send them to a
pod friendly, because it's a Web
Player, it comes up fast, it
works fast, that has all the
features in there, and people
are often blown away. It's like
not really, it's not it's a big
step for someone to switch apps,
because someone who's really,
really dedicated to it. And
you'll see a lot of people, you
know, pie pocket casts, you
know, very dedicated podcast
attic extremely dedicated. So
instead of getting people to
switch their apps, the ones they
like, now we have features that
these app developers can upgrade
to an apple, if they don't, you
know, what is NPR gonna do? They
want seasons, the way your
customers want seasons,
eventually, there's going to be
enough apps to support seasons,
that NPR will say, hey, if you
want to find our seasons, use,
you know, pod verse.fm they
will, they will do that. Now,
I've been around long enough to
see it happen. So just like Dave
is saying, this idea that it's
all over now is the browser Wars
was totally driven by features.
Totally, it was all about the
features. And it still is and
developers Thank you, Michael,
Microsoft is now trying to
capture some of that back and
and you know, I think they've
gone totally overboard where now
the browser just runs and sucks
out your life in data full time
but without even open. But yeah,
it's it's it's going to come
down to features and people have
been wanting these because every
other platform has this is your
own platform you can interact.
And so podcasting needs to get
it and let's, you know, let's
see if Spotify does anything
like that? I don't think so.
It's not their purview right
now. Yeah, I mean, I my my
preference would be for Apple to
Apple to adopt this stuff.
Because it would be nice if, you
know, outside of Spotify has
already said you know, their
their path. is clear. But all
these other players that support
RSS feeds my preference would be
like, yeah, let's, let's use the
podcast index stuff. When we
first started, I was like,
what's going on with RSS? Like,
what's, where's the RSS working
group and all that? And that's,
uh, you know, I don't know, do
you guys ever talk to those? Is
that even a thing anymore? I
was a founding member of the RSS
board. It's a piece of crap.
It's like, it's like nothing's
like people running around
talking stuff for 10 years doing
nothing.
Yeah. So So this seems to be the
best approach is to say, let's,
let's enhance RSS to renew open
protocol. I'm totally on board
with that. I mean, my, my dream
would be for Apple to adopt it.
And then, yeah, we don't have
because you're right. All the
only innovation we've had, in
the last 510 years. It's been
when Apple
announces new, you know, new
tags. And so here's, here's,
this is the problem. And this is
why part of why we started the
index. podcast, app developers
have never been in the deal
flow, there's been no money for
them. So what's the incentive to
create a great app? And and
Beside that, in order to create
a great app, you need endpoints,
you need an API that is
expandable, you need someone on
the other end of the API to
create the features that you
need. So we provided that, and
now we have apps that never
existed before. So the longer
Apple waits, the more market
share we're going to take from
them. Yeah,
yeah, that's the way I see it.
And maybe that's the hedge to is
to is if they want eight, to
maintain some space in
podcasting, they, and they are
competing against Spotify. And
maybe that's the hedge, as you
say, like, Listen, like
podcasting is moving on. And we
need people are demanding these
features. Just adopt them. And
then you've got, you've got a
big advantage over your
competition.
Yes, exactly. Right. Because you
think my, my dream of how this
plays out is that Apple
currently has the iTunes
namespace of which is mostly a
standard, and they but the
iTunes brand isn't even a thing
anymore, that iTunes doesn't
really even
nowadays, remember, name doesn't
mean anything.
Just refer to it as iTunes.
I don't know what you're talking
about. The, the iTunes namespace
refers to a product that doesn't
exist. But so so really what you
could do, and this is my
dreaming here, really, what what
Apple could do is they could
look at the podcast namespace,
and they can just merge the
podcast namespace in with
iTunes, and just and just call
it podcast. Branding isn't
giving them anything anymore. So
this could be an industry wide
change.
Great idea. That'd be fantastic
to just merge it in Nice.
Yeah, there would be no
breakage, I think I think would
just roll.
It's gonna take a lot of
pressure. I mean, I think as a
group, you know, between smaller
hosts like us, and people like
you guys, like it's gonna take a
group effort to really think
pressure, pressure Apple, maybe
there's some campaign we can do
all at the same time to just
bombard them with. everyone's
asking for this stuff.
Well, that's that's actually not
necessary, because they're quite
aware of what we're doing today
are, they're very aware I'm
presenting the namespace to them
in January. Yeah, give them
shit. Yeah.
That's I don't, it may not take
as much pressure as we think. I
don't think so either. I mean, I
think I'm gonna lay my case out
before them. It's like, the
timing is interesting. Why, why?
Why even? Why even compete with
Spotify? That's fine. If you
want to do that, you know, it
would be is Apple plus Apple TV
plus really competing with other
things? Is it really?
You said, I mean, Adam, you
said, you know, a couple months
ago that you think that Joe
Rogan will be coming back, you
know, outside of the ecosystem
as well that they'll have to
open that thing back up?
Yeah, I think so. I think
they're gonna have a real
problem getting the numbers that
they that they wanted to get.
Absolutely, based on what I've
seen, are already the audience
his audience reaction, that
that's a very likely scenario. I
mean, and if that happens, that
tells me everything I need to
know about people's about the
successful about whether it's
going to be successful, to
capture exclusive content, and
that your business model,
then that and that's the mistake
that they're making some mistake
that Apple's making is the ID n
and Spotify is the idea that the
success lies with the podcaster
With the audience and the
audience is all over the place.
And by the way, they, Spotify
may come for the podcast apps
next, they may start buying
people.
Hmm,
I don't put that beyond them at
all. So make sure you got all
your damn features integrated
before you become a millionaire,
your damn developers,
does transistor have a app do
have an actual app? There's no,
we don't.
Yeah, just testing, we really
want things to be as simple.
That's the beautiful part about
an open system is that you can
provide one part of the value
chain and then let other folks
do what they're good at total,
is so as a two person company,
we can you know, have a good
business and have a good life
and serve our customers and go
home and eat dinner with the fam
you know. And so I, our
preference is that to encourage
the overall ecosystem have, you
know, we have an API, we, we
want other folks to build stuff
on top of what we've got or
build stuff on top of just pot,
you know, podcasting in general,
by the way, cannot cannot view
source your API documentation
and just steal all of your
styles and all that stuff can
make because our API
documentation looks like
garbage.
You should also use
tailwind, tailwind. CSS is what
we've been using for all of our
stuff.
Okay, cool. So yeah, cuz I was
looking at your API about a week
ago, and I was like, Man, it's
documentation is so pretty, are
just like a dump.
All right. Now,
now we're down into nerd stuff.
Looks. Pretty baby.
I mean, you know, Pornhub got
defunded, so I gotta do
something.
Justin, and john transistor.fm.
Really appreciate the work you
guys are doing in the
podcasting. I'm gonna say it in
the podcasting space. It's super
important. We support everybody
who is who is out there making
it happen, who is independent.
And I really appreciate you guys
taking the time to share your
thoughts with us today.
Yeah, this is fun. Yeah.
Thanks for having us. Yeah, we
really, really appreciate what
you guys are doing to push
things forward.
Well, I want to say thanks to
because you're one of the I
mean, you're very early to
integrate with the artists
submission to the index, I
think. I think y'all implemented
that maybe like two or three
weeks after we launched pod cast
index. So I mean, it's right,
right in the UI, people can
click a button right when after
they submit to Apple, they click
a button and automatically
submit it to the index. Pretty
cool.
Yeah, we really appreciate y'all
jumping on board. That was
great.
And we and we'll, we'll get you
into one of these tests with
some of the the pledge model
apps I think you'll enjoy seeing
it absolutely. will show you the
future. The future is testing
2.0 Ladies and gentlemen, Dave,
anything else I can do for you?
What do you need? Oh,
the day job has been hectic this
week. And yeah, any any coffee
in a good book.
All right, everybody. We are
building the future of
podcasting, podcasting. 2.0
Dave, we'll do another board
meeting next next Friday, my
friend.
I see you bro.
All right, everybody. Make sure
you support us if you feel like
your time Townsend treasure
podcast index.org podcast.
We'll see you next week. Bye.
Bye, everybody.
You have been listening to
podcasting 2.0 visit podcast.
org for more information.