podcasting 2.0 for December
4 2020, this is episode number
14. We've got stats and facts.
No the board meeting
on another Friday looking at
what's been going on with
podcasting 2.0 I'm Adam curry in
Austin, Texas and that guy you
see over there the Brad Pitt
look like it's the guy for
breakfast, Mr. Dave Jones.
Wow.
This is a special is such a very
special episode of podcasting.
2.0 I'm really excited to be
here.
What makes it so special just
because you're here.
You don't remember. This is the
this is the 14th with a 14 week
anniversary of
Oh, honey, I forgot our 14 week
aversary I'm so sorry.
It's like when you're when your
girlfriend or whatever it is.
Yeah, the young love girlfriends
like you don't you don't
remember this is the first place
we watched the sunset together.
I remember those. But I often
Yeah, if I mess up on the on the
month of bursaries. What don't
you remember this is this was
our first date that was that
day, like down to the day? Yeah.
Like, well, I can't remember how
many years ago and I remember I
remember the date. But I don't
remember the you know, the exact
day,
I get a little fuzzy when we get
when we had to start parsing
time time zones.
Exactly. Was that in Lake Como
in Italy? Darling. I'm sorry. I
forgot. I really can't recall
the time zones.
For 1414 weeks into this and
we're we're cruising we
are. We are in cruising. I am. I
am so jacked about a number of
things that are happening right
now. And the first he jacked
about what I was jacked about
right off the bat is I the
community chapter idea. with,
you know, for, for chapters, and
I'm taking the two apps that
that are implement or have
implemented chapters that works
for me, in this case is hyper
catcher, and pod friend, because
it's like an additional
slideshow to the actual podcast.
And I found one of our producers
of the no agenda show. Sir, now,
Duke Dred Scott, and he raised
his hand and he said, Actually,
he I think he because I'd said
on the show, Hey, can you help
out with some chapters? Yeah,
just kind of off the cuff type
thing. Grab, grab hyper capture,
and I think I tweeted at once or
twice, and a couple people
checked it out. Because in hyper
capture, you can actually add
chapters while listening to the
show, which is such a, it seems
like such a simple concept that
you use the same application for
viewing listening as you do for
editing and for adding. Sounds
really nice. Yeah. And so that
shows up in the back end. Now my
problem is after three and a
half hours, you know, I can just
now barely remember after doing
the feed and all this crap,
which comes after, you know,
post production, and I need to
get my stuff out quick, you
know, I can't wait around for a
couple days. You know, I can
drag it over to otter.ai to get
the transcript rolling, which
have to remember to come back
because it takes a couple hours.
But then it's like if I'm gonna
do chapters like now I can't I'm
sick of myself. I can't hear
myself and go listen for another
three and a half hours. I tried
writing down time codes. No,
none of it works. And I just
don't i don't have that
capacity. It breaks your rule of
no post. Well, exactly. I yeah,
certainly no editing, you know,
anything, just, you know,
patching it up and getting it
out. So he had I think he showed
up on podcast index dot social.
And he had a question about the
hyper chat app and David was
helping him out and then I sent
him a DM I said, you know, bro,
do you want to just get you
know, get an account so you can
manage the whole thing and then
you can add images and go crazy
with it. And he said, Oh yeah,
sure. I'd love to do that. So
now what's happened if you look
at the last two no agenda
episodes Holy crap, it's filled
with images funny stuff, phone
boy is adding his no agenda
quotes with time codes, all of
this fantastic. additional
content that's being put in and
anybody can contribute. So you
know, anyone can still get hyper
capture and I think Martin may
be working on this for pod
friend. I think that it somehow
it should be some kind of
requirement that you that you
are able to this even just a
small bits of feedback. It makes
your app very unique.
I'm looking at it right now.
And I thought of another thing
and I think he
knows bill Frank for Microsoft
being
See, I mean, there you go,
you're laughing because it's
funny additional content. I love
that when people can contribute
in that way. And I was thinking,
since just as an aside, because
you know, the chapters, it's
like, Alright, if you're just
listening and you look at the
screen, a funny image pops up.
And you could do to time code
and the host could even refer to
it, or, you know, you can use it
as Oh, I want to, you know, skip
ahead to this segment, you can
tap on it. Well, if a if a
podcast app already has the
transcript, can't you then also
in the app, should you be able
to perform a search on that
transcript, which I would say
presumably, is already sucked
in? I don't know if the app does
it progressively. Or if they
suck, if it downloads the whole
SRT file? I mean, the Can you
then say, I'm searching for
this, and then it says, okay,
tears, five time codes, where
that comes up. And here's a
sentence and you just tap it
into goes to that spot in the,
in the, in the podcast,
that's complicated. And that
that's requires database, full
text search. So you would need
something like Elastic Search
server, or we Sphinx, there's a
few different Full Text Search
server products out there, you
know, open source and various
things. But you have to have
something like that, because the
transcript is humongous. And if
you're talking about, you know,
lots and lots of transcripts,
that's going to get big real
fast. Now, I mean, it's sort of
the same problem with the person
search, because you end up
having to vacuum up all of the
description fields of every of
every episode. And I mean, you
see a 50 million 50 million
episodes, and potentially and
let's just, you know, some
percentage of them have a
transcript and
they can't we just put this on
the blockchain. Yeah. Shame.
Come on, fix at all.
It doesn't even matter which
blockchain just the blockchain,
the blockchain, just the
blockchain, put it on there. You
don't
have to put it on there. You
just say you're going to and
then, okay, I think is fixed.
So in my simpletons, so I
understand what you're saying.
And I was immediately thinking
while you were speaking, is this
something the index could
provide? But now I'm like, holy
crap, no, no, this, this could
be a huge additional project,
which I think is basically what
Apple is now trying to do with
their transcripts. Yeah,
they're making that search.
They're doing it from the full
audio, the way they're meant to
tell me if I'm wrong, but I
think they are actually doing
the speech to text conversion to
get the transcript, and then
they're parsing, like they're
indexing that I don't even think
you have to have a transcript in
your, in your feed.
Oh, fuck those guys.
Well, but see, but I think it's
gonna, but it's gonna be crap
anyway, because, like, if
they're using the same if
they're using the same speech to
taste technology that Siri uses,
that's not an exciting future.
No, but even hotter, does a
pretty crappy job at a lot of
the transcripts, you know, it's
all kind of minimal. It's just I
know how easy it is. Here's the
quote, here's how I'm equating
it in my head. If I go to, if I
go to the show notes for no
agenda show, I have copy pasted
the transcript file into that
page in the outline. And you can
do an on page search. And it'll
it'll, it'll basically highlight
where that hit is. And it's,
it's, of course, it's not regex.
It's just a pure JavaScript on
the page search is very, very
fucking basic. So it can, you
know, it'll pick up words that
are separated by another word,
but that's about it. And then
there's the time code. And so I
do that, if I want to find
something in a particular
episode, I go to that page, I do
a Ctrl F, and I search for the
words, it's just an on page
JavaScript search, I see the
time code, then I go to my app,
or play or whatever I am. And I
forward to that timecode. And
I'm thinking, well, this is
dumb, because this can be this
obviously, this can be
automated. And I was just
wondering if it's possible in
that rudimentary fashion, so not
an overall search across all of
these things, but in one
episode, I just want to search
that one SRT file and then be
able to click on that one time
code in that one podcast that
I'm playing at that moment, if I
switch podcast, it flushes the
cache of the SRT
Okay, okay and understand you
now because typically as a
typical it the developer
whatever you want to call it,
me Yeah, you first you said it's
difficult and then you made it
sound like only you could do it
and then it was gonna cost me a
lot of money. Yes, that was
exactly Do warp 8.40
Wait, they
can. This is exactly what it is.
This is why CEOs fail because
they don't understand this one
dynamic.
Never set, you never tell them
exactly how long it's gonna
take, you know, it's just gonna
cause you always overshoot. And
then when you come in under it
your hero,
it's good to have an edible
before the show. This is
I think, no, I see what you mean
now. So like that. Yeah, yeah.
Cuz then you're just talking
about like a straight, you know,
I don't know how many thousands
of lines? Right. That's that's
the
thinking. Because what I've
noticed, and this is my job is
to notice these things. Is that
the the thrill? The I'm going to
use the word I don't use it
lightly the awesomeness of
podcasting 2.0. is these
interactions you do with the
app? Yes, that's, that's like
Boehner time, because we're
double cream. So where this
really shines, both in
excitement in a dopamine rush,
and in actual value, which we'll
be talking about in actual
digital money. boosting is
phenomenal. I mean, yeah, so
especially when people also
listening to a podcast, if you
haven't done this, if you listen
to the show, for the first time,
get seeds you can get on Sphinx
chat, Sphinx dot chat, and then
find some of these podcast
tribes. Because you can boost as
a as a seal of approval, a
number your discretion, which is
part of the fun. I used to have
1337 for leet. And then I saw my
wallet dwindling, and I changed
it for a four shot. That
was a great one. Thank you. And
it's very identified. Marty,
that tells from over to the no
agenda tribe in did 13 Oh, yes,
I
saw that. I saw that. I saw
that. And what's crazy, I saw it
come in on the index node, you
know, the one percentage? Yeah,
like what is going on here? This
is, that was beautiful. It's
beautiful. But it's that stuff.
And then that being of some
value for analysis for the
podcaster. So in the in the
chapters case, it's Oh, my God,
this is, you know, look at all
this cool additional crap that
was just created. In the book,
we talked about the transcripts,
which gives the listener
something to do like, I'm
looking for this. And by the
way, I'm a heavy user of this,
because I'm always looking for
what we're talking about, I
gotta go find this. And it's a
huge value. For you,
it could be a value for other.
Okay, so just think about, yeah,
no, no agendas, unique
situation, because you have an
army of producers that most
isn't really, you know, core, is
that what podcasting? 2.0 is?
Yes, I think that's Yeah, okay.
It's a good point. Because
podcasting 2.0 the whole
paradigm could mean what we're
trying to do we talk about it in
terms of our you know, value for
value, and in, in flipping that
model in and you get, you get
kind of sidetracked into the
money part of value for value.
But if, if, if our goal is to
revolutionize podcasting, into
podcasting, 2.0 across the
board, yep. And that would
encompass like every show,
having a small or some various
size army of producers that are
related, are able to do those
things.
I speak from some modicum of
standing, that every podcast has
listeners who are doing stuff
for that show, which I just for,
for simplicity, say they're a
producer, whether it's promoting
the show, this is, you know, you
should be able to wish in, you
know, in most podcast apps, hey,
I can promote this at this time
code. And I can tweet it right
away. And, you know, you get in
one case, you get Martin, snazzy
little timeline player, which is
just a piece of joy. You know,
these are all differentiating
factors of cool features that
you can do with this app, that
that helps out. So these people
just like Dred Scott, you know,
there's always going to be
someone who raises their hand
and says, Yeah, I'll do some
chapters. And you know what, he
might burn out? They usually do.
And then there's five other
people who will jump in and
maybe he'll come back and you
know, that, that I'm not worried
about that at all. In fact, I
see it as a necessary part of
expanding what we're doing Is
this okay? Other media ecosystem
has this.
Well, that's the strength of.
It's interesting because that
that is the strength of
podcasting. And one of the
differentiators of podcasting
from other forms of media is the
direct engagement between the
podcast and the podcaster. And
the audience. Like there can
there's a level of engagement
there that just doesn't exist in
really any other form of media,
you see it a little bit when you
get like a little bit of a
popular was it morning Dr. Show,
in a certain in a certain
market, and you don't get a
tribe of people who are, you
know, like in trying to engage
with the show, but there's
really, there's not, there's a
limit, you can't do much. I
mean, because it's really audio
only. And there's, there's
limited avenues for interaction
to come back to the podcast or
from that, excuse me back to the
radio host from that tribe.
Well, in this regard, you have
it's interact, it's it's
internet native. So it's
built into it, it's built into
it. And you know, and the
simplest of simple things like
tapping on Periscope and sending
hearts, or, you know, likes or
super chats on YouTube, which
involves actual money. These are
all interactive features that
have a playback feature as well,
which is really cool. And one
thing I know is should be
possible, is regardless of of
how the value was flowing, if
we're talking about the
lightning, network payments,
case and payments, it can be
compiled into something for
everyone to use as, like a
timeline. So no matter where
it's coming from, I should be
able to tell if someone has
boosted of certain segments on
my show, from any random app.
And I should be able to say, oh,
someone like this right here.
Whether whether an app will will
play that back for me, such as
the Sphinx chat, where you can
go back and you can start the
podcast and you see exactly
where everyone boasted. I mean,
these are very valuable
interactions between the
audience and the and the
Creator.
What I would love to say, I
don't know if you saw the Mitch
Downey from pod verse had some
comments on mastodon and he was
talking about sound bites, when
that's my next that's my next
thing. I'm gonna hound people
for to create those sound bite.
Yeah,
yeah. And he was talking about,
Well, why don't we just pull
the two chapters in sound bites?
I saw that I was like, Oh, well,
that's fucking smart. Because
you should do it anyway, just by
ending, but in tag right or
length
behind just put your just take,
just take your your sound bites
out of you know, and he just
published your sound bites as a
chapters file. And then it's
just like, boom, boom, you know,
you can have as many as you
want.
But could you also, could you
also publish your chapters file
as a sound bites file?
Those no sound bites file? It's
just,
yeah, it's just URLs and time or
time codes and duration. Yeah.
Right. So, but I guess what I'm
asking is, will it be
interchangeable?
Should be Yeah. Yeah. I mean, if
he had if he had, because you
can have as many sound bites as
you want. So if you had,
because I would, the reason why
I asked because I wouldn't mind
as an option, being able to
toggle the image off on a
chapter after X amount of time,
or at a certain time code.
Because after a while, it's just
you know, if the next chapter
Mark isn't, until 45 minutes
later, and I'm still looking at,
you know, at a Gina haspel. Dead
or Alive. I mean, that gets a
little annoying, I would maybe
could switch back to the default
image after you could set a just
as long as you can set an out
time. That's kind of cool.
Yeah, there's an end time in the
change bag. Oh, there is well,
then we're done. It's, it's
optional. But it makes most of
these systems are gonna be
automated. So it should be
fairly quick to put it in there.
And then the apps just as
they're consuming, and, you
know, they just, they just go
out at that point. I've done
something to wake up hyper
capture on my phone when I
looked at it earlier, because
it's just, it's sending me note
push notifications of bookmarks.
Like, as they're added, I guess,
also just hyper catch. Oh,
that's cool. you're logged in.
So it's sending you the
notifications that someone did a
chapter.
Yeah, and I got it. I got a push
notification that said John's
cream, sex. Evidently the title
of one of the bookmarks, and so
of course, I had to click on
that. Like there's
Yeah, I'm getting wait. So like
you're getting notification
notifications of podcasts. you
subscribe to this. No one puts a
chapter marker in. Yeah. Holy
fuck. Excuse me. That's
fantastic. I didn't know it did
that.
Yeah, I've got like, Oh,
shit. So you get notification
from the community. They've
added a bookmark. Evidently. Oh,
man. This is what I'm talking
about. All right, we're our work
is done here.
Of course. not stopping.
Alright, so good to know because
I'm gonna, I'm gonna see how I
was as this soundbite is
implemented, right that.
Okay. So is implemented it like,
yes, it's implemented and is
being used. I'm looking at the
tables on the exact
same JSON.
No, no, no sound standbys,
purely an XML tag? There isn't
there's no JSON component to it
at all. So it exists, it exists
in the feed. Whereas the Trent
transcripts and chapters, but
the tag references an external
JSON file.
Okay, ah, okay, so how are those
two interchangeable, then? Well,
if you had an if you, you could
come? Well, it'd be
interchangeable Not, not within
the feed itself. But you can you
do the conversion, you know, you
go back and forth in software.
It Like, like, what Mitch is
doing is he's putting as he's
pulling in sound bites. And as
people are creating sound bites
in pod verse. He outputs them as
a chapters file as a JSON file.
Oh, okay. I
get it. I got it. Yeah. So you
just
because they're roughly
equivalent in their
specifications, even though
they're not really intended for
the same purpose, right.
But the time codes all match up
if you want to?
Yes, that's right. Yeah. And you
and instead of doing a start
cut, start time and a duration,
you should just start timing in
in time, which is easy, because
you just add the duration to the
start time and there's your
income. And
user. Okay, so the conversion.
So if I had that in, in the
freedom controller, I could
start adding that manually
myself. the click of a button.
Okay. Well, I have to talk to my
my roadie, yeah. Don't Don't
bother. He's tuning guitars.
Yes.
He's really busy. There's 6785,
transcripts and database
currently in there, or just
clicking through here and
looking at stats. There's 30,600
chapter files in the database.
Okay. That's a good metric.
That's a good metric to look at
over time.
5946 sound bites? Not bad.
That's not bad at all. I
really didn't. I see someone had
an idea to create a feed or
something out of just the sound
bites.
Yeah. That was really cool. I
like
that idea. Has anyone did that
wind up getting done? Is that Is
there an end point for that?
No, no, there's an input for the
soundbite. Yeah, you can, you
can subscribe to the sound bytes
endpoint. And it just every time
there's a new one that pops up
in the system. Cool. You get it?
Oh, cool. That would be a great
virtual virtual feed to
subscribe to subscribe to it.
Yeah.
Yeah. You can just leverage how
do we do this? Is it done yet?
Yes. Does it work yet? Dave?
Over there. Yeah.
I was on. Frederick dormans.
podcast.
Yes. I was going to ask you how
that went. This is great. Yeah.
Now you're. I just want to say
yeah, you're real podcaster. No,
go. Yeah. Oh, yes. Your mo Yeah.
And certainly for a dude named
Ben. Man. You talk well.
Well, that is the dead. And you
smell less than you straddled
that so good.
No, you really do. You're a
natural podcaster. And you look,
you're the guy who has the
donation set. You got the clips.
I'm just like, I'm your roadie
here. No showing up to the
party.
I saw one. I think I know what I
saw. One is I saw
one. Okay.
Thank you. Um, and it's so
annoying.
What did you say the beginning?
I keep saying, um, and it's so
annoying.
Oh, back up. And it's so
I'm the king of that. It's just
a bridge.
I'm trying. I'm trying to do
better. I feel like I did better
on on Frederick's podcast it
was.
Tell me about Frederick's
podcast. That was great. Well,
it was it was the name of the
but it's not called Frederick's
podcast is it and
it is not called fresh cast. In.
embarrassingly, I
don't know what the title is.
But I can for purposes of this
show, it'll be known as
Frederick's podcast
is Frederick's podcast. I have
to put a link in the show notes.
So we'll look that up.
What I don't know this time. Got
it. Yeah, now I can't be Fred
draping it. Yeah, he's literally
looking at Frederick
flippin Frederick.
If only there was a place on the
internet, you could go to look
up podcasts.
Let me see. This is sad. Dave
Jones.
Okay, all right. I've got it I'm
now I'm redeeming myself because
this what we have in the index
is a thing called doormen calm
podcasts. That's the title of
it.
Really.
But that can't be right because
there's no episodes is Borman DJ
o r e. m A in Frederick. I'm
saying Bjorkman. Right that. And
I think that's the right
pronounce this
one episode from 2013. Yeah, but
that can't be right. can't be
right.
Oh, here it is. Okay, I got it.
It's called cut snack. That's my
Swedish. Cut. Yeah. Okay.
And how do you spell that?
KOD is in a ck.
cod snack. cod snack. This is
Swedish.
Is that hey, is that your cod
snack
and English?
Yeah, also the letter? Yes.
Okay. Dino Swedish.
I just said that the only thing
I know he else could
use a cousin Agnes.
caught that new two. I know two
things in Swedish now yellow sky
and cod snack and cousin egg. So
you're not on it. This is not on
yet. cod snack.
Now. He said it would drop on
No, no, it's gonna drop a nice
Oh, yes. Drop it like is hot.
What is this show about a
podcast by developers about
anything interesting to
developers. So let me guess.
Yeah, you talks about
developing. These are real
developers.
Okay, these are fake. These are
not
like the phoneys over podcast
indie. Yeah.
These aren't it guys. They
pretend to be. These are like
real ones. Oh, whoo. Okay. I was
out of my league.
I was gonna say you, you're
marrying up now. I see very
nice.
posnick like a punching above my
weight.
Yeah, that's it.
But it was a great talk. And it
was just me is is me and him.
And we were all over the map. I
mean, like, wait, yeah, we
talked about, you know,
obviously programming stuff and
index and all that stuff. But we
got into COVID. And the
difference between the mind and
the brain and Oh, my. Yeah.
Well, we were all over the map.
It was great. He's He's really
easy to talk to Craig.
It's nice. So weird.
Well, he's the developer of the
Mac chapters app.
Ah, right. Right. Right. Right.
Yeah. And we found each other,
reached out to him and got him
involved into into the
namespace. And we were able to
merge our chapter formats
together and right. I remember
beautiful, happy experience. And
it was great. Yes.
And they ever had a fight.
Yeah, not yet. Beautiful. But
but that gets that gets me Do we
get we get any more namespace?
Well, we get namespace stuff. We
don't talk about a Yes, I know.
This is the exciting part of the
show.
Yes, the pace. pays the day.
Hello.
Hello, ladies. Welcome to the
namespace corner with Adam and
Dave and we're gonna talk dirty
namespace to you
to female donors. Oh, over the
last 14 weeks. And we know for a
fact it's namespace abroad. No
doubt about it. Oh, man lady.
just heard them cancel their
subscriptions. Okay. Yes.
Well, yeah, any other nice day
like I because I've got the only
thing I've got on mine. Well,
people is still a thing. I mean,
this seems like a lingering
thing that hangs out there. And
then we get some energy and we
yap about it. And then it kind
of goes away. Where's people
because people is in trouble.
If people is in less trouble
than location.
Look, is last What can I say?
is off the radar? Nobody can
find it. People. I feel good.
Real good about people. I had a
phone call. Oh, God, When was
this? Well, we did. We talked
with it. Then. From the father
five or farside. Dan Benjamin.
Dan Benjamin last week. So it
was actually last week that I
had a call from the pot with the
pod chaser guys.
pod chaser.
Yeah, pod chaser. And if you
look, if you look at pod chaser,
they have a database. I think I
posted it the other day. In the
mastodons. Have a database of
appearances. Oh, yeah, shows.
Right. Right. Right. Right.
Right. Right. Okay. So this is
an external service and we're
trying to integrate with them or
be compatible.
Well, yeah, we're trying to make
sure that we're compatible
because I mean, if you think
about it, you got IMDb in places
like that.
You're This is this makes sense.
This is definitely the I didn't
even realize this is exactly
what I did. This is great. Okay,
yeah. Tell me what we're doing.
Yeah. So if you see, honestly
search for Adam Curry, there's
Adam Curry that guy, and it
lists all the pod fodder.
Let's see if it's any good. pod
father. And guess what? fail?
fail? Well, they clearly they
suck.
Obviously.
If you look at if you look at
Adam Curry there, there's you. I
mean, it shows all your
appearances. You see that?
I'm looking at him now. Let's
see. Oh, yeah. I appeared on no
agenda buzz cast Joe Rogan two
episodes. Very good. New Media
show one episode. I think I've
done two.
It's got you been on Adam
Carolla.
Yes, long, long time ago.
And on Austin sessions for 2013
possible Yeah.
Yes, no, of course, I know
exactly. When that was. I've
been on more since then. But
okay. Yeah, the people aren't
using the people, tech people
are people.
So this, like, what what this
would be is a, what we're going
to recommend in the namespace
tag for person is a URL link to
that, right there where so. So
if you have a person needs to
Adam Curry, and you also have a
URL, this is pod chaser.com,
slash creator slash Adam Curry,
blah, blah, blah. Okay. It's a
canonical sort of canonical
reference to insist there may be
more than one Adam Curry. This
is the differentiator, to say
I'm now I'm talking about this
Adam Curry. And then they can
vary. And then you also have the
built in verification that
they're doing on their back end,
which is sort of their bit, you
know, their whole business is to
do this type of stuff, where
they do verification, that
people when people say they've
been on a podcast that they
actually were on that episode,
okay? And alternatively, what
can you link to from the people
tag, you can link to anything
you want? It's really just comes
down to a matter of wording.
So if you had, what we're what
we're going to recommend is that
people link to the pod
chaser.com profile for the user
for the person there in
question. And then as fall
backs, you could link to
Wikipedia, their blog, you know,
a project, you could link to
anything as a fallback, just to
have something. But But if you
have the pod chaser Comm.
reference, it would be
considered, you know, better,
more authoritative because you
have their whole work behind it.
Right. And they're working with
good, they're working with
companies to provide this
service to ensure Sure.
Interesting, okay, so that's
just a people tag, and then
infinite number of names and
URLs. Yeah. And spelling and how
is that handled? If it's Adam
see curry Adam Clark curry.
As long as your link is cleared
to the purchase contract to the
Creator, then you can
report this. I support this 100%
actually 99% if pod chaser will
link my profile to pod father,
then I'm 100. I don't want to
spike anything. But how cool
would that be? I wouldn't pay
for like a like a custom domain
name.
So the vanity, your vanity?
Yeah.
vanity profile? Hell yeah.
Excuse me. Isn't that exactly
the same thing? vanity profile?
Well,
maybe it is. Yeah, that's
exactly right. pod, pod father
in there. And as long as it
links to
Adam Curry your goal? Cool. Very
good, sir. And this is nice.
Yes, I
think and there's also an extra
piece. There's optional stuff in
there, as well. And I think what
we settled on is the name,
clearly, link, whatever that
happens to be. And then you're
going to have a role and a type,
excuse me a role and a group.
And so the role would be like,
guest hosts, you know, co host,
producer blah, blah, blah. And
then the group is just very
optional, if that's even a thing
can add on if things can be very
optional, but group is as long
as
were we satisfying with this
group nonsense that you can't
explain.
satisfying the honest potential.
No, no, no, no, no, it's not
bad. The potential for people to
get very specific with who they
credit on their podcast. Yeah,
and I would think there are
probably Probably some people
out there, they want to get very
specific I do.
Yeah, I'm one of them. So I'm
very interested in wanted, they
want to think so I could say
executive producers as a group
and associate executive
producers as a group. And could
I also say, end of mixes as a
group, and your show mixes?
These the groups listed are the
official groups within the pod
cast taxonomy project. And
that's what we talked about
once. Yes. Okay. And this is
only a White House or something.
It is, yeah. And we're in it's
being finalized. Right, now that
I've got a preliminary list. So
that's why the group thing is
very optional, because like, the
way they listed out as they say,
you know, they give like a
group, producers. And then
there's, there's various sub
titles within producer and then
they may say, audio engineer, or
engineering, and then there's
various ones in there, and blah,
blah, blah, blah. So they're
these little groups. If you just
leave the group thing out all
together, in that, then it
assumes you're talking about
caste, which would give you host
ghost blah, blah, blah, almost
all the 19 Yeah, which is what
99% of people are going to use.
But then if you wanted to get
more specific, you could put the
group in there, and then say,
okay, audio engineer, a lighting
guy that, you know, that kind of
stuff.
There's no link to the podcast,
taxonomy project.
They have not officially
finalized. Okay, list. Yes, I
didn't link to it. Okay. We can
roll. We can roll it out without
that since the group. But I
think I don't think it's sacred.
I think they'll let us publish
it. And I don't, when I talked
to them the other day, they said
this is basically just
I have to see it to know if I
like it. Is that weird? No, not
at all. I could afford it. I'll
send you a code that mean
because I'm just looking at it
should be linked to the
namespace docs.
Yes. I just first whatever.
Yeah. And get that funny. They
I'm having some back and forth
with Ben slinger from pod chaser
and their bins slinger.
Yes. Great name.
Yeah. And meet his brother gun.
Sounds like a DJ. In a soft,
everybody been slinging around
the big w h Cz 100. That is a
great, great DJ name. I just
tested the ticket for a ride,
etc. etc.
Alright, so I get it this I
think this is very clear. Now we
just have to, you know, I think
we just need to know the, the
actual roles and groups, I'm
sure they've got it down. Yeah,
taxonomy means they took it
apart. So they understand. And
then the the last bastard child
of locate location.
Yeah, location is completely off
the rails. And it, we're, we're
gonna rewrite this thing. It's
funny, all the pieces are there,
it's just that trying to get
location, the really hard thing
is trying to get the
specification of how you want it
documented. You know, and I
mean, there's like 10 different
ways you can give a location.
Well, and so everybody's got
their everybody's got their
preference, and we're gonna
settle on something. I mean,
that you know what it does?
Ah,
let me think about this for a
second. Because I think what
appears to me the issue at the
core, besides How do you
document it, how do you write it
down? Is everybody has a
preferred way of location? Hmm.
And, you know, so I like the
Maidenhead locator, of course,
which is, you know, amateur
radio, satellite type. So I
think satellite people use it
too. Okay, because it's
footprint, I think. But then we
have GPS, you know, GNS s type
stuff. We have zip code country
codes. So there's all these
different ways latitude,
longitude, Latin long. It's
like, so what we don't really
have is a good example of a use
case, I would posit that that
drives that decision.
I think the problem is there's
two use cases, they compete with
one another. And they both have
total validity, like so. The
first use case would be a
podcast player that wants to
show you the location. And for
that, for the podcast, what
would be best for the podcast
app is if it's just a name, like
Stockholm, you know, or
Brussels. That would be the
simplest because I use rip it
out of the tag and put it right
into the to the to the user
interface. You don't have to do
any API lookups or any of that
kind of job. But then you have
this other use case. You're
talking about. gaiters and
indexes in directories where
they want to assemble a lot,
they want to start to do more
complex data where they figure
out who's in a region and help,
you know, interest in discovery
and all this kind of jazz. And
that's also a valid use case.
But for that flatline, maybe
better OpenStreetMap IDs may be
better, or blah, blah, blah,
blah, blah. So it seems like
there's two perfectly valid use
cases. One is simple ones
complex, and you want to be able
to support both in a single tag.
So dot dot, dot.
Yeah, I see the issue. But what
you didn't really give me is, is
a real use case example. I
understand. You know, why? Why
do you want just? What was your
example Brussels or whatever?
Why, why do you want that? What
is that? What is the point? What
are we using this for?
To find a local podcast for
Association? So and here's the
other issue is does the location
refer to where the podcast where
the podcast is recorded? Or what
is referred to what the podcast
is about? And I think 90% of the
time, it's going to be what it's
about. I mean, because nobody
cares where the podcast coming
from necessarily. I mean, I'm
here in Birmingham, Alabama,
but, I mean, that's not where
the podcast has nothing to do
with Birmingham, Alabama. And
the podcast is about every
summer melt. So I don't even
know what to put in podcasting.
2.0 as far as the location tag,
do we put Boston Birmingham?
Let's see, there's this other
class of or maybe we don't put a
location tag, there's other
classes. Go ahead. No, please
continue.
There's this other class of
podcasts where it's very
applicable. I mean, like, it's,
it's extremely important, you
know, relevant to the nature of
that show as to whether, where,
you know, like a location
specification. So, you know, I
don't know, what would you put
down? What would you put down
for no agenda?
Get mo nation? That's my
location. If you're looking from
podcasts, for podcasts from
Gizmo, nation, that's my
location. That's what I would
put in the feed. No joke.
Okay, well, okay, that that's,
that's great. That's, that's
important information, because
that means that that name, that
name tag, is, like it's
critical. Like just just a
straight string location. Is is
important. And the other stuff
is less so.
Well, all right, let me approach
this from an odd podcaster.
standpoint. Go, if I had any, I
agree with you that the only
reason for me to put a location
into my feed would be for search
purposes of people looking for a
particular podcast that either
was from or about a particular
place. And in my mind, that can
be fictional or nonfiction. And
I would say get mo nation. And I
would expect there to be many
other podcasts would be almost
like a tag. But why not say
moonbase? alpha is just as
valid. And we do want to build
for the future, actually.
So what's the last line of
moonbase? alpha?
You can't get that. It's not
important. I mean, hey, you ever
hear of Google Maps? bitch? Look
it up? That's my point. I think
we fixed it.
Yes. Okay. It's done. All right.
Next step.
So again, but it should I think
it should be. Yes, I understand
the documentation problem. I
totally get it. So maybe
approach it from the reverse and
say, This is a code that can be
used in search for a in a
geographic search. of podcasts.
It would be more podcast
content. Maybe that's maybe
that's your out instead of
podcast creation, say, you know,
based upon just like people, I
think you have to handle just
like people. You know, just like
a person is in this a place is
in this and that can be the
place that is made or the place
that it's about. Hmm.
And,
you know, that next level of
granularity? I don't know, I
think you have to know the
person has to do something
themselves at some point because
they have better AI than we can
build. Is this really about
Stockholm? Or is it from
Stockholm? Or is it both? But I
think I think you approach it
from it's it's a search code.
It's something that will be
searched. Prop likely, yeah, a
search. And when instead of
here's what you use it for, you
know, you get this information
and here's what you get. And
then you can do all kinds of
stuff with it. If you know stop
calm, you can get the lat long,
you can get the Maidenhead, you
can do all that stuff, you can
get the nearest airplane,
navigation beacon. Um, you can
do a million things.
At some of the the location tag
is suffering from from, from
Tech overthink? Yes, exactly.
Which is always going to be the
case. And some of it is is truly
kind of tricky to figure out.
But I think I'm falling down on
this on the scale. I think I'm
falling on the side of making it
more flexible. So he says, Sure.
It's always the right answer to
make to make your requirements
very, very small. And to make
everything else as optional as
possible.
Right. So that is, that's why
you have country locality lat
long and OS mid OSS, mid
OpenStreetMap. Id. So I could
choose what I want to put in
there. If I can, if I say okay,
just want to put in country.
Yeah, then I would use the
country code. Us I guess.
Yeah, that's right. Or gn forget
monition
gs sheet. Well, so here we go.
You've just no locality, human
readable place name is preferred
by the cod podcast publisher, or
display in an app valid values
are House of Parliament or North
Michigan. So yeah, so Stockholm
would be valid. And I could do I
guess, what is Sweden? s?
Oh, shoot.
se. I think it's se i think it's
se thing. Yours. That's
right. Yes. The se. Now you know
that this se
things I learned today? Okay, so
I could easily TLD Yeah, I could
use the country ISO 3166, one
alpha two country code. And I
could use the locality by saying
Stockholm and I could forego the
lat long and the awesome ID.
Yeah, it's fine. publish it.
Yes. I think that's fake,
because there's a recommendation
for having a type. And there are
Wait,
wait, wait, wait, this element
must contain at minimum a
country code na, when it goes my
get mo nation?
Well, I mean, you can have see
that that's where the type comes
in. So you get it's always you
always have a name. And the name
can be anything but then you can
also like, this is where we're
gonna have to rewrite it because
the the issue the comments that
we've been getting that we've
been plowing into that thing,
that the what you're seeing in
the spec doesn't match what the
current thinking in the comments
is. So the current thinking in
the comments is you have a type
identifier, where you say, okay,
you have a name, and that name
could be Stockholm, then you
have a type. And the type
specifies what location
information you're going to give
it. So this the type is country
code, then you give a country
code, and if the type is OSM ID,
then you give an OpenStreetMap,
Id type is this other, you know,
lat lon, and you get a latitude
longitude. So you can you can
leave all that out and just say,
oh, here's a name. Mm hmm. But
you can also put in type equals
whatever. And then you're
expected to give to give it what
you what you declared in the
time. You got it? That seems
fine to me. And, I mean, I think
that's where we're gonna end up
as a starting point. And I mean,
I don't see any other way to do
it. Honestly.
Yeah. Do you think that Who else
has a Who else has a dog in the
hunt?
As is five or six people in the
in the comment threads? So yeah,
and they're and none of them are
bad suggestions. They really
not. They're, they're all trying
to account for various things.
But I guess what I don't want to
end up with is just something
that's used pure. I don't want
to put a tag in there. It's only
going to be useful for metrics.
Right? Yeah, exactly. I agree. I
agree wholeheartedly.
Because who cares if somebody I
mean, ultimately, who cares if
there's some database somewhere
where a guy is enjoying looking
up? How many podcasts are in a
certain region? Because what you
really want to know if it's
useful for discoverability?
Let's do it was useful for user
happiness.
Yes, yes. Do it. Exactly.
Exactly. No,
but But no, I don't care about
database nerds. I just want to
know stuff. So anyway, that's my
thinking. But we're, we're
getting there.
Yes, yes. Ladies and gentlemen.
Oops. I was gonna play some porn
music and say this concludes our
our namespace segment. It wasn't
the right porn music
coming into the fancy namespace
I had this way, maybe this was
it. This is what I wanted to
play. I'm gonna get ahead,
dammit.
Yeah, you mess it up.
Yeah, no, I had that one all
queued up. But it was the it was
YouTube, man, those guys are so
out of inventory. They got to
put 15 ads in front of Ron
Jeremy. There we go. You're
sued by everybody in the course.
That is
namespace talk with Adam.
Casting 2.0. It's bigger than
ever before. Maybe.
Yeah, it can just jump into
shipment. And, yeah, so I mean,
I think we're getting okay to
wrap up namespace. I think we're
going I'm going to, I'm looking
at like at the end of January
like January 31. To close phase
two. But I mean, that's totally
flexible. I just want to get
through the holidays.
Yeah, we need extra time. Yeah.
Well, I'm excited. And value
will be in there.
As long as there's a lot of
discussion going on with value.
Yes, I've seen Brian of London.
He's doing a valiant effort to
get hive developers into using
the value block for their chain.
Yeah.
And web, the web monetization,
the web. monetization is an
interesting one. I let me tell
you about this. Because
I don't get any research on it.
Because I did a
little guy sent me an email,
someone reached out to me from
the web monetization project,
someone who works there. And,
and said, Hey, you know, we've
heard your podcast. It felt a
little for me to me. But I could
be wrong. It felt a little bit
of No, and the guy's high enough
from the I just haven't. I'm
glad we brought this up, because
I haven't replied to him yet. So
I said, so he said, I hear
Whitney, I heard the podcast I'm
listened to with a link I about
your project, but link to
podcast index. org, which to me
felt a little form form ish. And
he said, You know, this is this
is what we're doing. We're
creating a web monetization
standard. And this is the
company I forget the company
name coil coil. Thank you. And
you go look at coil and it. What
it seems to be is a couple of
one or more Silicon Valley,
people who made money, maybe in
PayPal, I'm not sure or they
were in
ripple.
There we go. See how good my
story is. Thank you ripple. So
that and it may be an offshoot
of ripple, I'm not quite sure
how connected those two are. And
they have a grant and the grant
is 100 million dollars. And to
be honest, my first impression
was Oh, okay, they want to
create a standard, the money, I
think the conversion runs
through them, or they have some
part of the fee to whatever web
monetization is, that wasn't
really clear from the consumer
marketing side. And they're, in
essence giving out hundred
thousand dollar grants to small
companies who either have
websites with content or content
creators, as long as they adopt
the standard, which is a
JavaScript meant to send
payments, micro payments in real
time to the creators through
this through this system. Do I
have that kind of right?
It's what it seems like to me.
Yeah.
So the part I don't like, is the
grant part.
Yeah. Yeah, it's this. I watched
three videos of Stephan Thomas,
I think is his name. He's the
CEO of coil. What three videos
of him explaining how
interledger works, which is
evidently the backbone of the
way the web monetization thing
work. Is
it is it quote, unquote, just
another blockchain? Or is it
something else?
It's different. And honestly, I
can't. I still don't know. I
still can't grasp entirely
what's happening there. I gave
it a valiant effort. And I'm
still not real sure. But you
know, the, the thing, the thing
that gives me pause about it
like, is that he, he's, he used
to be the CTO at ripple. And it
seems very tied to XRP. Mm hmm.
And I'm just not like i'm not
i'm not saying I'm not saying
it's a scam or anything. I don't
I don't think that that's the
case at all, but but I'm not
doing I guess what concerns me
is that it seems this web
monetization, quote unquote,
standard seems very tied to coil
the company.
Yes, that's what that's what I
introduced as well as like, all
the conversion goes through
them, and then everybody can use
it. But it Yeah, and I'm sure
that I'm sure this is some chain
and ledger that's open that
anyone can look at. I'm sure.
It's just adopting a standard.
And I've been a part of, well,
one, really, and you know, we're
doing some some additional work
on it on a standard now. But if
you drive it through incentives
of cash, to me, that's no
different than I'll pay you 1500
bucks to take the COVID vaccine,
you know, it's like, yeah, now,
it's like, people gotta want
this, they gotta want to do it.
And, and see, I mean, I'm sure
people see the benefit, but once
you're tied to any organization
with a grant, and grant is, you
know, it's not like, Here's your
money, enjoy. There's always
stuff tied to it one way or the
other. You have a master and,
you know, and with Bitcoin, no
Master, certainly, there's no
grants. I mean, I'm sure there's
grants, but you know, what I
mean? is like, write grants
shouldn't be tied to the, to
what your to the, to the
protocol, or whatever it is,
they're they're doing, I mean,
just who's driving that? Who
was, uh, who showed up and start
talking about you remember?
I think it was been forecast
upon, because we
may be way off base. We may. And
I and I don't, I'm just giving
you my impression, I think
you're doing the same.
Totally. And I'm totally just
speaking from first impressions.
And, and I could be completely
wrong about all of this. But I'm
having such a difficult time
understanding how it worked and
how it exists outside of the
outside of coil the company
that, I mean, based on what they
said in their presentations. It,
it should, like there should be
multiple people involved, other
companies can get involved in
it. But I'm not sure. Like, at
some point, you're going, you're
going fee, you're doing
conversions here. And so
somebody's got to pay fees
somewhere. And the only way I
can imagine that this works when
you're going from when you're
doing these micro transactions
across a ledger and then doing a
conversion back into Fiat is
that these things get batched
together in some way. And then
there's a convert, there's a
large batch conversion process
that happens, so that you get
the fee as low as possible. And
then there's an arbitrage
somewhere for the for the
company that's doing it to make
a profit. And, like, so. So this
sounds extremely difficult to
set up. I mean, and I don't
know, I guess it just strikes me
as one of those quote unquote,
standards that they kind of did
just kind of always limps along
and never gets beyond one
company. Hmm, yeah. Because I
think it's been around for a
couple years now. And I'm not
sure that it's like, Okay, well,
if coil folds, then the standard
folds, right? I don't know. And
let's just write the whole thing
sounds a little strange to me,
maybe somebody else can clear it
up? Well, um,
you know, really, with the,
since I dove into lightning, and
of course, I've been ramping up
to this for a couple of years
with my conversion to to really
be, you know, seeing the value
in Bitcoin, just by itself. And
as I dig deeper into the
material, I see that Bitcoin
still is the mama you know,
it's, it's, it's the Big Mama of
the whole kit and caboodle.
Everyone converts out of
Bitcoin, essentially, into the
secondary coins. But really,
we're just now and I think, and
this is just my view, and you
know, if you don't agree, fine,
you don't need to call me out.
Because I don't know what I'm
talking. Yes, you do. Yeah. You
must call.
Yeah, call me up. Because I
don't know what I'm talking
about. But my view is that we
needed this secondary layer,
which I see is lightning.
Because lightning is Bitcoin.
And it makes so much sense. So
we can, you know, write do all
these faster transactions, real
time transactions, write funky
contracts that can be handled at
execution layer. You know,
instead of doing it with yet
another blockchain with with,
you know, a conversion to XRP I
think everyone's trying to
incorrectly I think solve the
problem of all well, how are we
going to, you know, get people
to understand, you put your
credit card in here and then
you've got Bitcoin there. And to
me, I look at this from a
different perspective. Now, I
don't need the company to hold
my hand You know, with with some
web monetization that looks
official, I don't, I don't need
any of that. What I need is a
reason for Bitcoin to be fun to
me. So, if I go and get a
podcast app, it has a wallet in
there. Okay, well now I
understand at least when I'm
doing okay, I need to get some
kind of money into this. So I
can send money through this app
to podcasters. And I can boost
stuff and do other things. I
think podcasting will make
learning Bitcoin fun. For a lot
of people give them something to
do instead of changing money and
trying to figure out how did I
lose what what feels good to get
taken, you know, this is the
stuff that hangs people up,
because that's all you're doing.
We're not we underestimate the
excuse me, we overestimate the
onboarding problem, I think a
lot of times, because that's
where everybody gets hung up.
And Bitcoin is the onboarding
problem. But I mean, if you go
back, okay, think about 10 years
ago. Did you ever think that
your grandma will be downloading
chrome and installing it on a
Windows computer? Oh,
exactly. These things do take
time. They do take time. Yeah,
absolutely. I Yeah, of course.
Your grandma struggled more with
Web TV. If you remember that.
Crap. Oh, yeah. With the remote
control trying to try
to hit letters. That was
Microsoft when that Microsoft? I
think
they bought it. They bought
them. They bought them. I think
I think Chris Jacob was involved
in that deal.
Oh, that is a that's your buddy.
Yeah, yeah, I think okay, sir.
Chris, I think he was involved
in that.
Because that was all like their
big push was that it has MSN
network. You know, you can get
to
see how you can just look
towards history and see that
none of this is permanent. And
I'm looking at you Spotify.
Yeah, no, no. You want to hear
it the Spotify release. They're
like, shows. stash something as
my this pot podcast of 2020.
Oh, yeah. Now lists. Of course.
I'll have to ask devore act
explain again, how these lists
are made in corporate America.
It's hilarious. It's a lunch
basically.
If you Okay, so we had a we did
a one clip of this show last
week with Dan Benjamin. And if
we're out here on the outside,
we're outside of Spotify
ecosystem. We can't get to the
you know, we can't listen to the
Spotify exclusives. Yeah,
they're all locked behind the
silo past a wall. If you want a
taste of what you're missing, of
how good the quality of
exclusive shows is. Clip two as
a shoe is is a show with Addison
Ray, who is the number two
earning tik tok influencer.
Oh my,
I think she's like 1819 years
old, something like that.
That's according to yet another
list.
Yes, yes.
Yes. By the way, people these
lists are crap. You know that,
right? Like these lists are
compiled according to interests
involved in the list? People?
conception
Yeah, of course, this list is
very Yes. It's the list of
lists. Exactly.
By the way, the tick tock thing
is, and like when I should be
more specific, and not just a
thing, the TIC Tock culture
amongst top influencers is very
weird. Oh, it's gonna it's gonna
get old. Did you? Have you seen
this stuff where they have some
sort of like company that rents
mansions to top Tick tock, of
course. So that's their set. Man
that is? Oh, yeah. So whole
industry. Yeah. But it's all
based on one of the basic sins
vanity. Yeah.
So Oh, well, we'll then that
play clip too. So let's see
here. What you're what we're all
missing. Oh, Mom. Let's
fill everyone in on my 20th
birthday. So my 20th birthday.
Big number because 20 is no
longer a teenager. My friend
Bryant set up a kind of like a
little birthday dinner for me.
You know, it was really sweet.
And we went to a restaurant. We
all sat at like, small tables.
It was like four people at each
table. Really small event.
Probably there was like 12
people there. But there was only
four people at each table. Plus
my family. My mom and dad and
brothers were there. So it
wasn't really like a lot of
people.
This is some exclusive stuff
there.
But we all kind of just sat they
wrote little notes on like these
cards. I got to read them when I
got home. And then we cut the
cake. Oh, I do much besides eat
that was it. We weren't like
steaming up and like dancing or
anything. It was just like a
restaurant. You know? So we the
French Laundry with gaffers.
Yeah, the candles. I blew up my
birthday candles. I had so many
cakes on my birthday. The best
one was the one Courtney got me
to flower one from flower
I am just realizing we're doing
this podcast all wrong. Dave. We
should be talking more like
this. So when we talk about the
namespace, you know, it's just
namespace, but we didn't have a
you know, we have location
issues and issues problematic.
problematic the namespace
especially when it comes to
location.
It was so good the heart one
yeah, that was
really tastes like cream cheese
icing. Oh, but the entire cake
is cream cheese. Oh, wasn't it?
Yeah, it was mushy like it was
like fondant and cream cheese
icing mixed together into a mix
with a little bit of cake. So
good. It was so pretty. And it
was beautiful. Yeah. And I kind
of liked the crunchy outside of
the
day. Yeah, that
was the best cake ever. But the
view the view at your birthday
was amazing on that. I was so
pretty. Yeah. So my favorite
gift I got was probably either
the stage or stop. Really? Yeah,
it was a really good gift
actually. Because it was
thoughtful.
It was It
was great. I guess a
nice gift. Yes. Overall, it was
a really good birthday. I think
this is one of my best birthdays
yet.
Wait a minute. Wait a minute,
Dave. Let me just fix myself
here. Feel better now shot
myself.
Yeah, so after you go rinse your
brain out with soap. That is
okay. So I went through and
listened to some shows on there
over the last few weeks. And
they're all this way. They're
also boring. They're just
boring. Yeah. I can't explain it
any other way. So if you listen
to the same thing with Bernie
Brown, we played some of her
first shows before before she
went exclusive. So then I went
back and I listened to her
exclusive show. And it's boring.
And it's something about like,
there must be something
psychological about guaranteed
money, losing control of your
content script being scripted.
All this stuff that makes your
stuff boring.
Yep. Yeah.
What's the message to the way
your take your cake tastes?
I mean, this is why I have no
issue with what Spotify is
doing. Yeah, keep doing caitli
can't do more of it. I go back.
And look, there's a million
examples of this. I'm going to
give it one more time the
America Online example. It was a
safe, well protected, but you
can get a little risque here and
there. Oh, yes. This is a great
place to be You've Got Mail,
huh. But then people heard about
this thing called the internet.
And out there somewhere is all
the dangerous stuff, all the
cool stuff. We want that AOL and
AOL but grudgingly said, Well,
okay. But you have to click on
these five screens to say I
understand the risk of using a
browser. And people use the
browser and they found the porn,
and they never came back. And it
will became a dial up company.
If you took their son, so when
we get ready for this show you,
you know, we're like, okay, Hey,
what's up, blah, blah, blah,
alright, kick it in. And we just
start recording and everything
just comes out? Well, I mean, if
we were to take this show and
stick it into Spotify, and put a
Folgers commercial at the
beginning, and then a mid roll
for, you know, Prudential live,
I don't know, I'm just making
crap up. I mean, like, and then
you say, Okay, we have this
segment, we're gonna talk about
this. In this segment, we're
gonna talk about this. It's
like, it just loses any sense of
entertainment whatsoever.
Well, it's all subjective. And
I'm sure there's a there's a
market for the for these
podcasts, otherwise, they
wouldn't be investing in it. But
the world is big. And while
we're on that, there's two
things. Well, there's three
things we need to do. We thank
some people. But also we were
going to give some stat, why
don't we thank some people.
First, I want to run through
some stats with you, which will
take us into the final wrap up
of lightning and value block.
Yeah, sure.
See here. Okay. stack of paper,
get some good donations.
I'd like to remind everybody
that we operate under the value
for value system with the entire
podcast index.org project.
David, no one, none of the three
partners including Eric, we
don't take salary. We don't know
if it'll ever come to that. But
the index does run on the value
that we receive from the people
who have who perceive the value
of what we're doing. That is
sometimes developers it's fans
of podcasts as podcasters it's
people who understand and like
technology and like seeing
things move forward. And all we
ask is that you consider how
valuable this is to you. There's
no other charge for the use the
index shared, the API is open.
We're, we're clearly putting
time and effort and energy into
it. So all we ask for in return
is some value. It could be time
talent, treasure. Now you see
the developers, what they're
putting into it is, of course,
astronomical. But we also have
people who just need to support
us financially. And we love
thanking them because often a
recurring donation can mean an
entire server that runs to
complete the mission of
preserving podcasting as a
platform for free speech and
retooling it into a platform of
value for everyone,
like the pod pod, calculate the
value perception, their
reception for perception. I know
I just I just came up with that.
Yes. Yeah.
These are some little things
some value perception engineers,
how about today? You go,
we got a first donation is
anonymous. $200 aussage. Yeah,
it says no notes and no credit
wanted. just happy to
contribute.
Thank you very much anonymous.
Yeah. Yeah. Thank you very much.
very appreciated.
Yeah, absolutely. That was a
single donation. 200 bucks is
just, I mean, $200 is, that's a
third of our hosting fees for
the month. I mean, that's,
that's almost an entire month
right there.
It really is. It's fantastic.
It's awesome. Yeah.
I mean, they were out of order
here. I'm gonna get there's
another one that was a little
bit big. See if I can find Oh,
yeah, here it is. So I'll kind
of do these in a little bit
better order. This one is make
sure it's not anonymous note is
not. This one is Brian Pollack.
And he donated $100 Wow,
thank you, Brian.
Yeah, no, no. Yeah, no, he's got
a message says contributing the
value I can to support an
important project to help make
sure podcasting evolves in the
future as an open medium of
communications. I tm
it him to you my brother. Nice.
This is why I need the tag get
mo nation. Because I got I got
people who live there.
With this btn That one goes with
that one. Okay.
Here it is. I'm not hearing you
crumple them up and throw them
on the floor like he usually do.
Am I not? I didn't hear it.
No. Crumpler, okay.
folder, your risk cruncher.
Somebody gave us a donation.
This is this is a one time pick
paper crinkle sound donation. I
really enjoy the sound Keep up
the good work. As a podcast
listener, I would benefit from a
list of podcasts that are using
2.0 features and tags so that I
can check them out. Awesome to
every podcast that Adam is on at
one point to speed and I refuse
to stop. He says r&b dance.
All right, all right.
I'm not. I'm not trying to rush
through episodes. It just sounds
more natural to me how he
sounded Luke. Okay, so Luke,
where's Luke? Yeah, I'm just out
of control. Like
your code, actually.
Hey, that hurts. Okay. Luke gave
us $10 Luke Presley. Luke,
here's your
nice paper.
very satisfying. All right.
Then.
The next one we got here. Oh,
this is $20 donation from Yorn.
And he just have note. I don't
see one where now it looks like
it's just a $20 donation. All
right. Thank you. Yorn. Shar,
thank you. You're. And then we
have there's a good note here
from David Metis. He, he did a
$10 month subscription. And he
says, David Adam, hey, this is
Metis rounds. No, I'm sorry.
metus rounds. What he says
rounds with fetus. Yeah. Got it.
Okay. From this is a mitas from
Fun fact, Friday with Lila and
David. Oh, hello. And this is
great. He says I heard y'all
lost a $10 a month donor. So I
decided we should replace it for
you.
Ah, that's fantastic. In that
sweet?
Yeah, in my very long term goals
are to be a full time value for
value podcaster vow of poverty.
I know. I want to ensure that
there's a place for independent
podcasters and the big companies
don't set a lock us all out.
Well. Now I got to figure out
how to get all of this code
implemented in my feet weekend
project.
Fantastic. And if you were the
host, now we have to go to new
podcast. apps.com new podcast
apps calm. There's a list there
of apps that support the 2.0
features in you can search for
by function and also the hosting
companies who support this and
hosting applications because
cost apart I think, is there an
app application?
Yeah. And that was fun fact,
Friday looks like the name of
his podcast.
Nice. Get a roll and brother get
some SATs.
So here's a I guess this one was
out of order. This was a
Christopher Tomkinson gave us
$50 single time, one time
donation. Nice. And his message
was rock on gas.
back at you, right on. We commit
to rocking Yes. For those about
to rock We salute you.
And finally, we get a new
automatic, monthly subscription
from Kevin Rola for $5 a month
and I could not find a note from
Kevin.
Kevin, I think is a no agenda
guy.
I think his name sounds good.
Yeah, does.
Thank you, guys, very nice.
And that is it. So those are the
donors.
But listen, hold on a second.
I'm sorry. Because before it
scrolls off, I'm looking at the
no agenda troll room. And I see
people chatting, I use regex to
change season and episode stuff
on video files. And it's like,
well, it's because iTunes is
messed up and like, well, at
least they're working on a
namespace.
Yeah,
just talking about us right in
the chat room. And this is
completely unrelated. They're
not listening to us.
It's not on the stream. No, no,
no, not at all. Not at all.
That's funny. So that was the
donations from what we call
this. Fiat donations that
are made. These are all fee
donations that come through our
PayPal. Now we do have a
lightning widget a podcast
index.org. And you can use that
or just click on that big red
Donate button. It's red for a
reason, people. And if you're
listening to this show, and
you're listening right now,
still the Sphinx chat app, crank
up those value sliders, hundred
sets a minute, keep it common,
boom. 11 most most.
Okay, so we got lightning stats.
We've had almost a full month of
lightning.
Three weeks, or it's almost not
quite four weeks, I don't think
have we? Well, the report I ran
was for November, and we only
have three weeks in November.
Yeah. It started in the November
11. Mm hmm. So he Okay, that
makes it. Alright, so this for
three weeks from the 11th
through the end of the month,
what I found interesting, it'll
say, Well, if you just add up
the dollar value of all the SATs
from per minute, I didn't
include like, boosts or anything
like that. I just thought these
were more interesting. per
minute, SATs, they hit the index
node that's then as 1%. The
total dollar value of those SATs
is $7 and 50 cents.
That's without the boosts
without the boost. Yes. And with
the boosts because I think boost
is a part of it.
Yeah, I don't have in front of
me. for it, I
think it goes up to $11 11.
Okay, double digits. Well,
this is important because this
is so just to explain what we're
talking about here. On the
Sphinx chat app that have
implemented the value block with
the lightning nodes, lightning,
lightning IDs, and the splits,
please see the sexy namespace
for more details. It's very sexy
namespace of each minute
listened. 1% goes to the Sphynx
chat app, which will be our
standard default. For the app
that you're listening to
listening to the podcast on 1%
goes to the index, and 98% goes
to the podcast. And all of this
is voluntary, any podcaster can
change these, these splits and
these destinations at will in
their. In their RSS feed, we
suggest a portion for the app
and for the index because its
value for value. And all the
other stuff you can cut up
amongst your buddies, your
friends, your co host, whatever
you want. So when 100 satoshis
goes through 1% goes to the app
1% goes to the index. So the
overall value flow in three
weeks has been about $1,000 has
been transmitted while enjoying
podcasts, either playing them in
real time. Or, or enjoying extra
pieces in boosting. Am I saying
that right? Yeah,
I think so. So you could say
well, if you're only talking
about per minutes and not boost,
then roughly $750 has floated
flow through the system.
That's I mean, and that's what
six podcasts. Yeah,
well and Okay, so the more
interesting aspect of To me,
then they didn't even the money
part was the number of
transactions. Then there was
12,160 minutes of podcast
listening through Sphinx. In
three weeks, that translates
into 202 hours of listening,
which is how many days? Gosh,
four days?
Not me. 72 hours, three days, so
roughly
200 Yes, of course, almost eight
910 days. So holy crap
worth of worth of podcasts time
spent listening. Now, that's
what i said i excluded the
boost. So that's only per
minute. Split transactions. So
that's an accurate count of
there. There was 202 hours of
podcasts listens to through
Sphinx chat.
So we're gonna start surfacing
this number.
Yeah. On the side.
Yeah. Because that is so sexy
$1,000 has been running through
just a handful of podcasts.
Yeah, it's really only a, it's
just a few. I mean, like,
there's,
and, and, you know, so, okay,
here's my experience with this,
because this is blowing my mind.
It's, it's gotten so regular,
that and that, you know, I use
Thunder hub for the index
lightning node, and you can see
a running, you know, it's kind
of like a feed of when a payment
comes in. And it'll tell you
know, how many seconds ago how
many minutes ago how many hours
ago, and more often than not,
I'll see three payments. And
it's just the 1%, three payments
come in, at the same timestamp,
or within the same minute. But
it's always one always doesn't
matter. When I watch when I look
almost always and then all of a
sudden, the other day, I think
two days ago, all payments
stopped around 4pm Central Time,
and didn't really start again
until 11. And I got freaked out.
I'm like, something, something
cuz i, this is what I do. I
analyze trends. And I've kind of
a neural networking capability,
like, something's wrong
texted me, you're like what,
hey,
something went wrong. Now, we
think that a channel got full
and closed. And I do have some
evidence of that on my node. So
it might have been an outbound
outbound channel that just got
exhausted and wasn't, you know,
autopilot didn't do its job for
those who understand. And there
was no other route or something
like that. But that's how
regular these payments are. So
imagine you have an app, and you
just see money coming in, in the
form of satoshis every minute of
the day, multiple entries. And
then just imagine what we have
to do as a group to magnify that
and multiply it times 1000.
Yeah, well, now all of a sudden,
we're all in business. And,
again, I'll run through the
numbers. 100 million people in
America, listen to one hour of
podcasts a day, we convert 1% of
those hundred million people to
donate or pledge and use one of
the apps that were that are
lightning enabled. It's a
million dollars a day flowing to
the ecosystem gets your slice of
it today. And while stocks last.
And I'm very happy to say that
I've had ongoing conversations
with Roy scheinfeld from breeze
wallet. And those guys are a
heads down and they are they are
working on integrating
podcasting into their wallet. I
think I think they may even
release it just as a podcast app
that happens to have a wallet.
That would be the ultimate I
think
we we talked a little bit about
that in Frederick show they did
I understand correctly that they
have that they're going to do a
release like a skeleton app or
the source code for that.
Yeah, they will. Okay, yeah, the
integration for it so they've
already the the breeze wallet
code is already on GitHub and
available. So that gets they're
gonna create rappers and stuff.
And I believe they're all doing
it in HTML or maybe even react.
I don't know what the hell
they're using. I need
to get back with Paul and Evan
overs Thanks and see and we
can't talk to those guys. And
well, we need to, but he didn't
hook up and have a meeting with
them. And just see where
everything's at. What No, no,
no, no, no, no,
no. Dave What
are you talking about? We need
to bring him on the show. Oh,
yeah. Idiot. Yes. Boost boost.
You get a boost sound.
Verbal boost. Yeah. We need him.
Let me see if I can get a boost
to sound away.
There's There's got to be an
audible boost on the because
this is too fun.
Let's see boost sound effects
Hold on a second. Let me see
what I got here. Central.
mucking around anyway. Let's
just see if I got a boost in
this. I need to boost. Yes.
Boost baby. Yeah.
What was that? preview? Yeah,
yeah, we need we need to we need
to get Jennifer Buchanan to do a
boost sound at the top of it
you've boosted? Yes I'm like
that That's awesome.
Yes. So now the beauty of what
they're working on is they have
an app that is that is I think
it's a neutrino app. So it's a
very lightweight Bitcoin
lightning node that functions by
itself and has keys and outbound
enabled. So in order to receive
satoshis, you need to have
something that's online all the
time. But to send them you only
have to be connected to be able
to send to whatever the whatever
receiving node is programmed for
the for the value split. So this
scales infinitely, at least
until we break the lightning
network, but it scales
infinitely for people to use.
And, and yeah, so even if
you're, if you're a podcaster
maybe have a look@voltage.io or
raspy Blitz or Sphinx chat for
me, you can use that perfectly
fine to use a node that you have
over there to receive your
satoshis on
did a voltage node light node
this past week?
Yeah, experience was great.
Yeah, not fantastic.
Mm hmm. Once the light node
works fine. Yeah.
I got the full blown big note. I
didn't know at the time, just
like I'll just take the big note
because I figured we got big
stuff coming in. Well, I almost
wanted to I
almost did the big node then I
was like, you know, I want to
get the light neutrino node just
for a test run to see how it
works. Right. So far. It's been
good rock solid. Yeah,
excellent.
Yeah. Yeah. Good over there. I
like it.
By the way, you know, we were
talking about we talked a little
bit about substack. Last week.
We agreed, yeah.
How they felt like how they do
fees. Mm hmm. I found there's a
really good article called the
substack irati. From the
Columbia Journalism Review, and
it's says in here that they take
10% Yeah, it says the guys
devised, guys she's referring
Guys, guys, is the guys that
started. By the way, it's very
interesting article if you if
you're
putting it in the show notes
right now.
And it's worth a full res very
long, but it's worth reading it
for a lot of different reasons.
So the Clio,
the Clio Chang article.
Yes, exactly. Right. Now part of
the part of this article feels
feels different feels defensive
of the J squad. The It feels
like a journalist trying to
contain one. Yeah, yeah. But
there's also political Anyway,
there's this very interesting
article, but she she says that
this is the guys talking about
the founders of substack devised
a system of taking a 10% cut
from subscriptions. stripe, the
credit card service that
processes the fees would take an
X would take 2.9% plus 30 cents
per transaction, which they felt
tied down to the riders. Ah, so
I don't it's a little difficult
to decipher issue means 10% cut
and in stripe is an additional
2.9%. Or, I'm not sure how they
But anyways, 10% and then
minimum, perhaps 12.9%. So I
don't know. But that's not it,
so that you do that compared to
compared to the value block. And
there's there's potentially
nothing if you don't want it to
be or you know, if you're
stingy. Or if you want to you
know, if you're willing to split
out some for other things like
the podcast app, and the index
or, you know, all these other
things. There's there's other
ways to slice it, but it's
definitely well south of 10%.
Oh, no kidding. No kidding.
Oh, my good not to worry about
being d platformed. It's
cheaper, and you don't have to
worry about D platform.
And it helps create an
ecosystem. Yeah. Yep. It really
does. And I think if only if we
start with the, with lightning
payments for work that's being
done and for value splits and
credits, you know, it it's
priming the pump, and I'm just
seeing this the this machine is
rolling it Is it is just
running. It's like, as an
entrepreneur, there's different
moments in it. And I've started
several companies and taken one
public. And so there's all these
moments that you kind of come to
recognize. And when all of a
sudden, you spin the wheel and
the flywheel keeps going. And
this is an incredible moment,
and that's what's taking place
here. The flywheel is spinning
in perpetual motion by itself.
Okay, we had some kind of slow
down the other day between 4pm
and 11pm. But the thing is
spinning, it's really happening.
And all we need is just more
apps to support this. And the
podcasters. And everything will
come I mean, the Bitcoin guys,
they're having a ball. Yeah,
Bitcoin podcasts aren't the
jack, Jack's man. It's
fantastic. Yeah,
there's so I looked it up,
there's 10 podcasts total, with
a block enabled in the index so
far. So if he didn't match, you
just imagine, you know, if you
go, you know, if you multiply
that, that times, you know, if
you go up to 100, podcasts, we
know what they're doing, you're
talking about, all of a sudden,
you that's meaningful money that
begins to support, like, for our
standpoint, begins to support.
Let's just go up to 1000
podcasts. Now you're talking
about 70 $700 a month. Now
you're talking about being able
to cover all the hosting fees,
all of our stuff. Yep. All of
the infrastructure with 1000
podcasts. And that's, that's at
1%. And if the app takes 1% now
the app guys are getting paid.
Significant. Yeah. I mean, a
decent amount of money. I mean,
like, that's what, there's no,
if you take somebody like hyper
catcher, I'd love to he would
love to be getting $500 a month.
Sure. And he can get it he can
get it being worth his time.
Yeah. Yeah, exactly. Anyway, no,
so we'll publish that. I think
we also should add to the new
podcast apps, maybe someone we
have to surface I know you've
made an endpoint for it. We need
to surface the value block
enabled the shows
yet Trent is redoing the
website. Ah,
drug Play Doh to the rescue.
Yeah, I had a GSE meeting with
him the other day. And a great
guy, man.
Oh, no, I've had coffee with him
here in town. He's a fabulous
guy.
He's in Austin. Hester.
Yeah, he's, uh, he recently
moved here. You know, he's, he's
like, younger than my daughter.
But you wouldn't know it. I
mean, the guy is just like wood.
He's very worldly, super smart,
and very, very talented. He's,
he's an old soul.
Mm hmm. There you go. That's it.
Yeah, but he's, he's redoing the
website. And so he's just, it's
not gonna be a major change. But
he's just like restructuring it
and reformatting some stuff. So
I'm gonna let him finish that
first, before I make any big
changes to it. And then once he
gets that done, then I'm going
to put up the do the feats page
and all that.
So let's get you Paul on Evan
from Smith's chat for next week
if they can make it. Well, we
already got next week. Oh, who
do we have next week? next week.
Dave?
The guests from transistor. Oh,
cool.
Okay. All right. Don't do it
after them. Do we have another
week before Christmas?
We got to figure out what to do
about Christmas because
Christmas Friday falls on the
25th it is Christmas Day. So we
need to pre record something I
think.
Yeah, well, I don't know. Yeah,
we'll think of we'll think of
what to do. I wonder if we could
get James Cridland on for? Let's
see if it's Christmas for us.
It'll be New Year's in
Australia. So
yeah.
I'd love to have James on. I'd
very much want to have James.
Okay.
So let's say 6pm. His time isn't
known. 6pm Our time is 9am his
time?
Oh, well. We can do it at 6pm.
Yeah, the ethics. Especially if
it's an off day. Yeah, it is not
a Friday. Yeah, we can do that.
We'll work on James but so we
got a transistor next week. And
then can we do Paul and Evan, I
want to get ball on Amazon.
The week after? Yeah, yeah. If
you think and then
you mean my wine.
Okay, we can
talk namespace
when you have to clean your room
first. My room is clean as a
whistle. It is man. That picture
your studio was bombed.
Yeah. Yeah. I mean, I realized
later that people look at like,
oh, okay, it looks cool. But
they don't really understand.
This is custom made for me for
the way I set up my gear which
is portable. So I mean, it's,
it's, it's so perfect. I'm so
happy here.
Now. I like that they is this
LED string lights.
That's the cheapest addition to
my studio and I have little
remote control. So I like the
blue kind of purplish blue.
harem look when I'm doing now
often when I do show I'll, I'll
do a little orange to get it
because it gives you energy. And
you can do it all you can do it
all from from the remote
control. That was literally like
20 bucks before the stream in
there all the time all the time.
Yeah, I'm Uh, I'm the guy that
has the dark studio. I don't
want the outside in. So I can
totally my, my space right now
is the screen in front of me to
the left is where I see your
meter go up and down that
represents you. And to the right
is jingles or, you know, like
this stuff. And I'm just in my
little world, man. I don't see
anything outside of it. I
love it. That's perfect. I'm
currently podcasting from my
hallway. I'm in the flub sitting
in the floor.
This is one of your better
studios.
It
sounds very good. I'm very nice.
And I got a lot less of the fire
truck going by this time.
Yeah. I'm perfectly enclosed in
here now. It's it knows good.
Yeah. So like, and I've also got
Todd and I talked to Mike. Mike
from blueberry blueberry. Yeah,
and I've got Todd and Mike are
gonna be on with us in January.
Ah,
super. Oh, man. Now we're
cooking with gas. And we got to
get Martin on. Yes, absolutely.
Well, everybody, we need to get
everybody on. Party. Just like a
potty. Exactly. All right. Uh,
yeah. I think we've we've, we've
the board. We had a quorum, we
can close it out. Yes. Anything
else you need that I can conjure
out of air for you.
And I need to talk about the
Amazon outage. But another do
that today. We're gonna talk
about that in the next week. I
guess. Next time we have a non
guest we will talk about the
Amazon. There's a lot to learn.
Ah, okay. Well, that is
important to do. So let's let's
make sure we remember that
because I have my own theories
about the Amazon outage. Okay,
it may surprise you.
I have a printout of their post
mortem. Ooh, that is marked up,
but we'll save that for the next
show. Yeah, I think that's
great. All right. Dave. Have a
great weekend. My brother, you
too man. And everybody else.
This has been podcasting. 2.0
Episode Number 14. We'll see you
again next Friday. Take it easy.
Everybody. See you next time
podcasting 2.0
You have been listening to
podcasting 2.0 to visit podcast
in this Zack Hall. For more
information.